<?xml version="1.0"?>
<gameList>
	<game>
		<path>./King of Fighters '94, The (Japan, USA) (En,Ja) (Rev 1).chd</path>
		<name>The King of Fighters '94</name>
		<desc>This is the first game of the series that conquered legions of fighter fans from all over the world. The King of Fighters '94 joins together fighters from other SNK Corporation franchises: Art of Fighting (Ryo Sakazaki, Robert Garcia, Takuma Sakazaki, Yuri Sakazaki, King), Fatal Fury (Terry Bogard, Andy Bogard, Joe Higashi, Mai Shiranui, Kim Kaphwan) and Ikari Warriors (Ralf Jones, Clark Steel, Heidern), as well as totally new fighters such as Kyo Kusanagi, Benimaru Nikaido, and Goro Daimon (from the Japanese team).

The King of Fighters '94 is notable in that it is one of the first known fighting games that pits a team of fighters against each other in single combat. Each team consists of three fighters for each player, the winner being the player who is able to eliminate the other team first. Each active character can charge up "Art of Fighting" style in order to gain access to "Desperation Moves", or "DMs" (moves which operate very much like Street Fighter's Super Combos). Playing against the computer, the player must defeat all 8 teams in the game in order to reach the final boss, Rugal Bernstein.</desc>
		<releasedate>19941102T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>SNK</developer>
		<publisher>SNK</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./King of Fighters '95, The (Japan, USA) (En,Ja).chd</path>
		<name>The King of Fighters '95</name>
		<desc>The first sequel in the King of Fighters series picks up a year after the end of the first tournament. Once again, fighters from all over the world receive a mysterious invitation to a team-based fighting tournament. And just like last year, it appears that the notorious criminal Rugal Bernstein is behind it, apparently returning from the dead to raise havok once again...

The King of Fighters '95 introduces Kyo Kusanagi's rival Iori Yagami, and firmly places Kyo as the main character for the rest of the series. The gameplay of The King of Fighters '95 is essentially unchanged from the previous title, though it does introduce the "team edit" concept which would remain as a standard feature of the series. Using the "team edit" feature, it is possible to create a totally customized team using any of the available fighters, or use one of the default teams if you wish.</desc>
		<releasedate>19950929T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>SNK</developer>
		<publisher>SNK</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./King of Fighters '96, The (Japan, USA) (En,Ja).chd</path>
		<name>The King of Fighters '96</name>
		<desc>After the death of Omega Rugal, whose body could not withstand the power of Orochi, a new tournament is organised by a certain Chizuru Kagura. She introduces herself as the guardian of the mirror that seals the demon Orochi but feels that something is wrong. She asks Kyo and Lori to help her defend the seal in case of an attack. Indeed, Goenitz, Orochi's messenger, came to free his master. But Kyo and Lori gathered their strength to defeat him. When Goenitz died, Iori drank his blood and then began to behave strangely. He entered the Riot of the Blood and killed Vice and Mature who were at his side.The King of Fighters '96 is an important episode in the history of KOF. The legend of Orochi is more and more present and we get one of the toughest bosses in fighting games, Goenitz. As for the game itself, it has undergone a nice graphic evolution.</desc>
		<releasedate>19961025T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>SNK</developer>
		<publisher>SNK</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./King of Fighters '97, The (Japan) (En,Ja).chd</path>
		<name>The King of Fighters '97</name>
		<desc>Another year, another KOF. Additions this year come in the form of slightly improved graphics and sounds, new moves and a new game mode. Gameplay is much more plot-driven, as you have middle-bosses that can change depending on what team you select. In addition, there are several special endings which are only shown when certain "Edit Team" combinations are selected.

As of The King of Fighters '97, you can play in either the Extra or Advanced game modes. Extra Mode is the typical AOF/KOF scheme, in which your power gauge fills up as you defend yourself or charge yourself up. The new Advanced Mode, on the other hand, only allows you to charge your gauge as you perform special moves and attacks, similar to the Street Fighter series. Extra allows one to sidestep attacks while Advanced allows the character to roll past and dodge attacks; Advanced also allow a character to perform a potent "Super Desperation Move" (or SDM) at any time provided the character has at least two full bars of charged energy stored. In contrast, SDMs can only be performed in Extra when a character has less than a quarter of their health left.

New characters include the New Face Team, the Fatal Fury Outlaw Team (featuring the KOF debut of "Blue" Mary Ryan and Ryuji Yamazaki, and the return of Billy Kane), and Kyo's pupil Shingo Yabuki. In total, The King of Fighters '97 sports 29 separate characters (without counting the six Orochi-related boss characters, which are all accessible via a secret code).</desc>
		<releasedate>19971030T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>SNK</developer>
		<publisher>SNK</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./ADK World (Japan).chd</path>
		<name>ADK World</name>
		<desc>ADK World (ADK Special in Japan) is a mini-game video game developed by ADK and published by SNK in 1995 only in Japan and only on Neo-Geo CD.
The software allows you to access a menu in the form of a city map called ADK Town. The laboratory of the professor Brown allows to access to cards of the characters of World Heroes and to a drawing of World Heroes Perfect. The ADK Cafe provides access to information, covers and artworks on characters from the ADK universe: Magician Lord, Ninja Combat, Ninja Commando, Aggressors of Dark Kombat, Crossed Swords II, World Heroes, Blue's Journey and Rally Chase. The ADK Building is a fan questionnaire that ADK answers. ADK Corner, a discussion about ADK. Mysterious Shack allows to unlock hidden options.</desc>
		<releasedate>19951110T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>ADK</developer>
		<publisher>SNK</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Crossed Swords II (Japan) (En,Ja).chd</path>
		<name>Crossed Swords II</name>
		<desc>Crossed Swords II features the same gameplay from its predecessor (Crossed Swords on Neo Geo MVS and AES). The player is given a first-person view with a third-person silhouette/wire-frame view of the character similar to the Punch-Out!! arcade game. New to this sequel is the addition of a new button for jumping and dashing, giving the player more maneuverability and allowing him to dodge incoming attacks. By pressing the attack button after dashing the player will make a horizontal slash which stuns enemies briefly, and by pressing the attack button after jumping the player will make a powerful downward slash.</desc>
		<releasedate>19950502T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>ADK</developer>
		<publisher>ADK</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Bakumatsu Roman - Gekka no Kenshi ~ The Last Blade (Japan) (En,Ja,Es,Pt).chd</path>
		<name>The Last Blade</name>
		<desc>Choose one of several characters to play with, each with their own unique moves and special attacks. Each stage in the game has two battles, where the object of each is to drain your opponent's energy in order to complete the battle, and you will complete the stage if you do this twice. If there is a draw, then a third battle is then played. There is a time limit, and when this expires, the player with the most energy wins the battle.</desc>
		<releasedate>19980326T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>SNK</developer>
		<publisher>SNK</publisher>
		<genre>Fight</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Bakumatsu Roman Daini Maku - Gekka no Kenshi - Tsuki ni Saku Hana, Chiri Yuku Hana ~ The Last Blade 2 (Japan) (En,Ja,Es,Pt).chd</path>
		<name>The Last Blade 2: Heart of the Samurai</name>
		<desc>The Last Blade 2: Heart of the Samurai is a 2D fighting game which features anime-style characters that fight each other with swords, clubs, and even fishing poles. These characters pull off their special moves with that 'quarter-circle-to-half-circle' and 'double-half-circle' controller motions, reminiscent of Street Fighter.</desc>
		<releasedate>19990227T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>SNK</developer>
		<publisher>SNK</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Choutetsu Brikin'ger ~ Ironclad - Tesshou Rusha (Japan) (En,Ja).chd</path>
		<name>Ironclad</name>
		<desc>Ironclad is a side-scrolling shoot 'em up for the Neo Geo CD. Use your war ship to save the Kingdom of Chop from the Iron Mask Republic. You can use three main blast weapons, which are upgradable when you collect more items, a charged attack available when Iron Clad is attached to your ship, three melee weapons, a bomber that clears all enemy bullets, and varying shooting patterns. Stages are selectable, and there are multiple endings.</desc>
		<releasedate>19960920T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Saurus</developer>
		<publisher>SNK</publisher>
		<genre>Shoot'em Up</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Oshidashi Zintrick ~ ZinTricK (Japan) (En,Ja).chd</path>
		<name>Zintrick</name>
		<desc>Yet another puzzle game on Neo-Geo! Every four years to Asgard, the "Tournament Zintrick" occurs. During the competition, participants from around the world come to compete for the honor, glory and wealth.</desc>
		<releasedate>19960322T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>ADK</developer>
		<publisher>SNK</publisher>
		<genre>Puzzle-Game / Throw</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Real Bout Garou Densetsu ~ Real Bout Fatal Fury (Japan, USA) (En,Ja,Es,Pt).chd</path>
		<name>Real Bout Fatal Fury</name>
		<desc>The fourth title of fighting Fatal Fury series. Now, you can destroy fight scene objects and the "Fatal Fury 2" fighters are back forming this list: Terry Bogard, Andy Bogard, Joe Higashi, Franco Bash, Mai Shiranui, Bob Wilson, Geese Howard, Billy Kane, Hon-Fu, Ryuji Yamazaki, Sokaku Mochizuki, Blue Mary, Kim Kaphwan, Jin Chonrei, Jin Chonshu and Duck King.</desc>
		<releasedate>19960126T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>SNK</developer>
		<publisher>SNK</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Real Bout Garou Densetsu Special ~ Real Bout Fatal Fury Special (Japan, USA) (En,Ja,Es,Pt).chd</path>
		<name>Real Bout Fatal Fury Special</name>
		<desc>It was the sequel of Real Bout Fatal Fury, with which sixth delivery of the series was arrived at his, in this we had 20 characters (Terry Bogard, Andy Bogard, Joe Higashi, Mai Shiranui, Tung Fu Rue, Cheng Chinzan, Laurence Blood, Wolfgang Krauser, Duck King, Kim Kaphwan, Blue Mary, Hon-Fu, Bob Wilson, Mochizuki Sokaku, Franco Bash, Ryuji Yamazaki, Jin Chonshu, Jin Chonrei, Billy Kane and Geese Howard) and their aspects are 100% remodeled.
Also, the game maintains the capacity to destroy some things of the fight zone.</desc>
		<releasedate>19970330T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>SNK</developer>
		<publisher>SNK</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Samurai Spirits ~ Samurai Shodown (Japan) (En,Ja).chd</path>
		<name>Samurai Shodown</name>
		<desc>In early Japan, a man named Shiro Tokisada Amakusa preaches a heretic religion. Little does anyone know that Amakusa is really a servant of the evil Ambrosia, who took over Amakusa's body. Ambrosia wishes to shroud the world in darkness.
Now, choose between 12 warriors (and 3 bonus characters) to fight for the honor of destroying Amakusa, and fulfilling a mission.</desc>
		<releasedate>19940909T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>SNK</developer>
		<publisher>SNK</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Samurai Spirits - Amakusa Kourin ~ Samurai Shodown IV - Amakusa's Revenge (Japan, USA) (En,Ja,Es,Pt).chd</path>
		<name>Samurai Shodown IV: Amakusa's Revenge</name>
		<desc>Bringing a new breath to SNK's swordsman fighting series, this 4th installment marks the return of 3 classic characters (Yagyu Jubei, Charlotte and Tam Tam, now with updated stuff), introduces 2 newcomers for the pantheon (the brothers Sogetsu Kazama and Kazuki Kazama) and brings some new backgrounds.

In spite of these little improvements, the game preserved (and improved a lot) many elements that did the previous one (Samurai Shodown III: Blades of Blood) a quite popular title, like the dodge move and the chance to choose between two versions of the fighter: the standard one and an alternative dark-styled one (SLASH and BUST, respectively).

With the intention to provide more action in the battles, the "No Contest" Moves were introduced: working in similar way (and under certain conditions) to the many games of Mortal Kombat Series, your fighter will execute an ultimate-slaughter move in a stunned opponent.</desc>
		<releasedate>19961227T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>SNK</developer>
		<publisher>SNK</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Samurai Spirits - Zankurou Musouken ~ Samurai Shodown III (Japan, USA) (En,Ja,Es,Pt).chd</path>
		<name>Samurai Shodown III: Blades of Blood</name>
		<desc>The 12 samurai (and ninja) elite are back, this time to answer the threat of the demon Zankuro, Minazuki. The possessed swordsman has brutally slaughtered innocents in his path, yet could not raise his blade to the cries of an innocent baby. Vowing never to spill innocent blood again, he targets those who live by the way of the sword...but now the hunter becomes the hunted. The third series of Samurai Shodown introduces 2 different techniques for each character. The "Slash" techniques are the original moves of the most of the characters whereas the "Bust" techniques maybe the "darker" version of each character.</desc>
		<releasedate>19951229T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>SNK</developer>
		<publisher>SNK</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Shin Samurai Spirits - Haoumaru Jigokuhen ~ Samurai Shodown II (Japan, USA) (En,Ja).chd</path>
		<name>Samurai Shodown II</name>
		<desc>One of SNK's legendary fighting game series has made a return! In Samurai Shodown II, you can take on one of the roles of 15 warriors as you fight your way through the land to defeat the evil Mizuki! Slash, kick, and slice your opponents in half...do whatever it takes...live by the sword, and die by its blade.</desc>
		<releasedate>19941215T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>SNK</developer>
		<publisher>SNK</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Shinsetsu Samurai Spirits - Bushidou Retsuden (Japan).chd</path>
		<name>Samurai Shodown RPG</name>
		<desc>It's eighteen century, to japan, it's a peaceful region. The word "peaceful" are only applied to the social status, not the heart of the human. 
The greed, like the diseases, is spreading through the human heart. The devil within had awaken and worse, the devil below is risen... In case some people might not know, Samurai Spirits RPG are divided into 2 stories. One is based on Samurai Spirits 1 and the other are based on 2.</desc>
		<releasedate>19970627T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>SNK</developer>
		<publisher>SNK</publisher>
		<genre>Role playing games</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./King of Fighters '98, The - Dream Match Never Ends ~ The King of Fighters '98 - The Slugfest (Japan) (En,Ja).chd</path>
		<name>The King of Fighters '98: The Slugfest</name>
		<desc>The King of Fighters '98 takes a break from the Orochi plot line and instead is presented as a "Dream Match" game where the KOF roster duke it out for the top spot (similar to Ultimate Mortal Kombat 3, but without the storyline component). Most of the characters from the past four years return, thus providing the player with a very large roster containing 38 characters. Many of the characters have been altered in an attempt to make the game balanced regardless of the player's choice of fighter. Rugal Bernstein is provided as a non-secret character for the first time in KOF '98, and several regular characters have hidden "alternate" versions that may also be used in-game. 

KOF '98 uses the same gameplay system present in The King of Fighters '97, so players may still choose between Extra and Advanced modes. In addition to the Survival battle mode and the ability to choose between Single Play or Team Play, versions of the game on console systems that use CDs to contain their media (PSX, Neo-Geo CD) also include an Art Gallery one may look at.</desc>
		<releasedate>19981223T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>SNK</developer>
		<publisher>SNK</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./King of Fighters '99, The ~ The King of Fighters '99 - Millennium Battle (Japan, USA) (En,Ja,Es,Pt).chd</path>
		<name>The King of Fighters '99: Millennium Battle</name>
		<desc>It's time once again for the famous KOF Tournament! New faces and old alike join together to participate in the latest KOF tournament, but something seems wrong. Why was this year's tournament announced without fanfare? What could be up? That's for you to find out! Featuring classic KOF gameplay with a new twist: The Striker Match!</desc>
		<releasedate>19991202T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>SNK</developer>
		<publisher>SNK</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
</gameList>
