<?xml version="1.0"?>
<gameList>
	<game>
		<path>./Amped 2.iso</path>
		<name>Amped 2</name>
		<desc>Amped 2 is the ultimate freestyle experience, offering the largest, most varied trick library of any snowboarding game. Explore vast areas of wide-open, spectacularly rendered real mountains packed with terrain parks designed by world-famous snow park architect, Chris Gunnarson. Play head-to-head with friends in the various multiplayer modes. When you're ready to take it to the next level, connect to Xbox Live to check rankings and challenge the world's best virtual riders.</desc>
		<releasedate>20031028T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Microsoft</developer>
		<publisher>Microsoft</publisher>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
		<players>1-8</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Dead or Alive 3.iso</path>
		<name>Dead Or Alive 3</name>
		<desc>Dead or Alive 3 (Japanese: ?3 Hepburn: Deddo Oa Araibu Sur, abbreviated as DOA3 ) is a fighting game in the Dead or Alive series. It was released in 2001, exclusively on the Xbox as a launch title.</desc>
		<releasedate>20011115T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Team Ninja</developer>
		<publisher>Tecmo</publisher>
		<genre>Fight</genre>
		<players>1-4</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Forza Motorsport.iso</path>
		<name>Forza Motorsport</name>
		<desc>Racing sim from Microsoft, targeted at gamers who are passionate about cars and racing. Own, customize, and race your favorite cars in the most technologically advanced and realistic driving sim yet. Use race earnings to buy upgrades and aftermarket parts, so you can transform real production cars into high-performance racers. On the track, experience an impressively accurate simulation, while putting your performance-tuned creations to the test against the online gaming world on Xbox Live. Features car models from more than 60 top car manufacturers, customization via decals and team paint-schemes, and vehicle tuning that really affects performance.</desc>
		<releasedate>20050503T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Microsoft</developer>
		<publisher>Microsoft</publisher>
		<genre>Race, Driving</genre>
		<players>1-8</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Halo - Combat Evolved.iso</path>
		<name>Halo: Combat Evolved</name>
		<desc>Humanity is the midst of a long war against an alien alliance called the Covenant who have been wiping out colony after colony. You hero is Master Chief, who is given no name beyond his rank in the game itself. He is stationed on the Pillar of Autumn, a ship which, per protocol make a jump in a random direction to retreat to avoid revealing the location of Earth. They find themselves at the titular Halo, a planet-sized ring of mysterious origin and function with the Covenant on their heels. Master Chief must repel the Covenant assault and discover the secrets of Halo with the assistance of the female AI Cortana who lives in his suit and gives missions.</desc>
		<releasedate>20020314T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Bungie</developer>
		<publisher>Microsoft</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1-4</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Jade Empire.iso</path>
		<name>Jade Empire</name>
		<desc>Set in an ancient world inspired by mythical China, Jade Empire lets you train under your master's watchful eye as you learn powerful martial arts and mystical powers. When danger threatens, you'll travel across the world, from the harsh mountains of the Land of Howling Spirits to the lush gardens of the Imperial City. In your adventures, you must face powerful human and supernatural foes, learn the exotic and magical martial arts, and discover the darkest secrets of the world. Practice the greatest fighting styles and defeat the most powerful enemies to become a master of martial arts.</desc>
		<releasedate>20050412T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>BioWare</developer>
		<publisher>Microsoft Game Studios</publisher>
		<genre>Role playing games</genre>
		<players>1-10</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Ninja Gaiden Black.iso</path>
		<name>Ninja Gaiden Black</name>
		<desc>Ninja Gaiden Black and Ninja Gaiden Sigma. The game follows the fictional story of Ryu Hayabusa, a master ninja, in his quest to recover a stolen sword and avenge the slaughter of his clan.

Tecmo specifically targeted Ninja Gaiden at a non-Japanese audience, and despite difficulties in obtaining content ratings due to the game's graphic depictions of violence, it was generally well received, and 362,441 copies were sold in North America in the first month after its release. Nevertheless, the game had to be censored for release in some regions, and Japanese sales were poor, with only 60,000 in the four months following its release. Making use of the Xbox's internet connectivity, Ninja Gaiden was the focus of a series of online contests across North America, Europe and Japan. Record-breaking numbers of players took part, competing for places in the live final, which was held during the Tokyo Game Show (TGS) 2004.

Team Ninja continued to update the game after its release: two Hurricane Packs were made available as free downloadable content that added extra content, gameplay challenges, and game engine improvements.[1] These were incorporated into a reworked version, released in 2005 and entitled Ninja Gaiden Black, that was regarded by the game's creator Tomonobu Itagaki and many players as the definitive version. In 2007, Ninja Gaiden was graphically enhanced on the PlayStation 3, with extra content, in the form of Ninja Gaiden Sigma. This version was later released on the PlayStation Vita as Ninja Gaiden Sigma Plus.</desc>
		<releasedate>20050920T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Team Ninja</developer>
		<publisher>Microsoft</publisher>
		<genre>Beat'em Up</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Panzer Dragoon Orta.iso</path>
		<name>Panzer Dragoon Orta</name>
		<desc>The fourth installment of the Panzer Dragoon series has you playing Orta, a young girl who has been imprisoned by the Empire. Under a wave of attack, the prison camp is broken through by a mysterious dragon, and Orta takes it upon herself to ride the dragon, and destroy the Empire once and for all. Along the way, she will also discover her own destiny, and the mystery surrounding her new friend.

Simply put, you have limited control of the dragon for most of the game, as your trigger finger will be shooting non-stop at the enemies that fly around the area. Orta will be your main source of fire-power when you simply press the fire button, but by pressing and holding, the aim cursor will change, allowing you to fire a burst of power from the dragon at whatever the cursor aims at.

The dragon itself can change into three forms at a press of a button. Each form has a different style of attack and power ability.

A port of the original Panzer Dragoon is included.</desc>
		<releasedate>20030114T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Smilebit</developer>
		<publisher>SEGA</publisher>
		<genre>Shoot'em Up</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Phantom Dust.iso</path>
		<name>Phantom Dust</name>
		<desc>Xbox action game Phantom Dust is set in a post-apocalyptic world where strange dust has fallen from the sky wiping everyone's memory. A group of humans who have developed supernatural powers, the Espers, have discovered two bodies in hibernation pods. One of the two is named Edgar, and could hold crucial information on ghost dust. The other is you.</desc>
		<releasedate>20050315T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Microsoft</developer>
		<publisher>Microsoft</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1-4</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Project Gotham Racing 2.iso</path>
		<name>Project Gotham Racing 2</name>
		<desc>Project Gotham Racing 2 is a racing game released for Xbox. Drive through the streets of the world's most famous cities in automotive gems such as Ferrari, Porsche and Lotus to earn Kudos that unlock more cars.</desc>
		<releasedate>20031117T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Bizarre Creations</developer>
		<publisher>Microsoft</publisher>
		<genre>Race, Driving</genre>
		<players>1-8</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Conker Live and Reloaded.iso</path>
		<name>Conker : Live &amp; Reloaded</name>
		<desc>Conker: Live &amp; Reloaded is a combination of frantic online multiplayer action and a single-player mode, which is a remake of the original  Conker's Bad Fur Day for Nintendo 64 with more detailed and technologically advanced graphics, as well as re-recorded music. The single-player game plays very similarly to the original version, but a few gameplay-related changes have been made. Conker now uses a baseball bat instead of the frying pan (his default weapon in the original). A few particularly challenging sequences have been made slightly easier; for example, a crosshair has been added for the slingshot weapon. The remake also censors more swear words with "beeps" than the original release.</desc>
		<releasedate>20050621T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Rare Limited</developer>
		<publisher>Microsoft Game Studios</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1-16</players>
		<favorite>true</favorite>
	</game>
</gameList>
