<?xml version="1.0"?>
<gameList>
	<game>
		<path>./Wild_Guns_Reloaded.USA.xci</path>
		<name>Wild Guns Reloaded</name>
		<desc>Wild Guns is a fast-paced arcade-style shooter, mixing the Wild West with steampunk. Play as Clint, Annie, Doris, or Bullet the dog with his sentry drone.</desc>
		<releasedate>20180417T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Natsume</developer>
		<publisher>Natsume</publisher>
		<genre>Shooter</genre>
		<players>1-4</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Advance_Wars_1+2_Reboot_Camp.USA.nsp</path>
		<name>Advance Wars 1+2: Re-Boot Camp</name>
		<desc>Each CO affects your units in different ways, and they each possess a unique ability that can turn the tide of battle. Do you like to go toe-to-toe, or engage from a distance? Choose the CO that best complements your playstyle!</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20230421T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Wayforward</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Strategy</genre>
		<players>1-4</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Astral_Chain.Euro.xci</path>
		<name>Astral Chain</name>
		<desc>Master multiple combat styles in this synergetic action game!Humanity’s last chance against an interdimensional invasion is a special living weapon called the Legion. As a rookie officer in the elite police task force Neuron, you and your Legion will work together to solve cases and save humankind.The ASTRAL CHAIN game gives you full control over two characters at once for thrilling Synergetic Action, courtesy of PlatinumGames. Alternate between several Legion types and skills to save the world your way.</desc>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>20190830T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>PlatinumGames</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Baten_Kaitos_I_II_Remaster.xci</path>
		<name>Baten Kaitos I &amp; II HD Remaster</name>
		<desc>Two JRPG masterpieces return. Baten Kaitos: Eternal Wings and the Lost Ocean and Baten Kaitos Origins are back with improved graphics and new features to aid game progression, making them even easier to play!
A long time ago, there was a great conflict between the evil god and the people. After a fierce battle, the people managed to seal off the evil god, but what was left behind was only a desolate land. The people thus chose to abandon the land and live in the sky.
Such fairy tales were passed down as legends. At this time, people had wings called Wings of the Heart and lived a peaceful life. It was an era of long-lasting tranquility. ...But the collapse had quietly begun.
When a young man calls your name, the name of the spirit, the story begins to unfold. A story set on a floating continent in the sky, where thoughts and prayers intersect.
*Baten Kaitos: Eternal Wings and the Lost Ocean is available with subtitles in English, French, Italian, German and Spanish.
Baten Kaitos Origins is available with subtitles only in English.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20230914T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Logicalbeat</developer>
		<publisher>Bandai Namco</publisher>
		<genre>Role playing games</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Mario_vs_Donkey_Kong.USA.nsp</path>
		<name>Mario vs Donkey Kong</name>
		<desc>Solve all kinds of puzzles and test your platforming smarts as you try to recover the stolen Mini-Marios in Mario vs. Donkey Kong on Nintendo Switch.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20240216T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Octopath_Traveller.Euro.xci</path>
		<name>Octopath Traveler</name>
		<desc>Choose your fate. Eight stories await. Eight travelers. Eight adventures. Eight roles to play in a new world brought to life by Square Enix. Explore each traveler's story and use their abilities in and out of battle. Will you expand your horizons as the Merchant or track down a traitor as the Warrior? Where will you go? Who will join you? You alone can choose your path.</desc>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>20180713T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Square Enix</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Yoshis_Crafted_World.Euro.xci</path>
		<name>Yoshi's Crafted World</name>
		<desc>Jump into a new Yoshi adventure in a world made of everyday objects—like boxes and paper cups! As Yoshi, you'll leap up high, gulp down enemies, and set out on a treasure hunt to find all the different collectables. On the flip side, stages can be played backwards, providing new perspectives to explore and new ways to locate some of the more craftily hidden items!

It all started when Kamek and Baby Bowser set out to steal a gem-set stone. Legend has it that this fabled artifact can grant the bearer their wildest dreams! But when the artifact's gems are sent flying, it falls upon Yoshi and friends to find them. Luckily, saving the day can be cooperative and challenging. Pass a Joy-Con controller to a friend to team up as fellow Yoshis. Also, Mellow mode gives Yoshi wings for a breezier experience, which may come in handy! Finding all the flowers, coins, and Poochy Pups is no small feat! For extra protection, suit up in one of the handicraft costumes you can unlock in-game or by tapping select amiibo figures!</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20190329T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Good-Feel</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Final.Fantasy.II.Pixel.Remaster.nsp</path>
		<name>Final Fantasy II Pixel Remaster</name>
		<desc>The original FINAL FANTASY II comes to life with completely new graphics and audio as a 2D pixel remaster!
A remodeled 2D take on the second game in the world-renowned FINAL FANTASY series! Enjoy the timeless story told through charming retro graphics. All the magic of the original, with improved ease of play.

Our epic tale begins with four young souls orphaned during the struggle between the Palamecian Empire and the rebel army. On their journey, the youths join forces with the white wizard Minwu, Prince Gordon of Kashuan, Leila the pirate, and many others. Behold the beautiful and sometimes tragic twists of fate that await you on your adventure.

FFII introduced a unique skill level system that strengthens different attributes of the characters depending on their fighting style instead of leveling up. Use the key terms you learn in conversation to unlock new information and progress in the story.

This innovative game series takes an ambitious turn in this second installment in the FINAL FANTASY series!
</desc>
		<releasedate>20230419T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Square Enix</developer>
		<publisher>Square Enix</publisher>
		<genre>Role-Playing</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Final.Fantasy.III.Pixel.Remaster.nsp</path>
		<name>Final Fantasy III Pixel Remaster</name>
		<desc>The original FINAL FANTASY III comes to life with completely new graphics and audio as a 2D pixel remaster!
A remodeled 2D take on the third game in the world-renowned FINAL FANTASY series! Enjoy the timeless story told through charming retro graphics. All the magic of the original, with improved ease of play.

With the power of light nearly eclipsed by the power of darkness, only the crystals' four chosen adventurers can save the world.

Experience the iconic job changing system first introduced in FFIII - switch jobs at will and use various abilities as you progress in the game. Change into a variety of classes like Warrior, Monk, White Mage, Black Mage, Dragoon, Evoker, or even call monsters to do your bidding with as a Summoner.

Enjoy the exciting third installment in the FINAL FANTASY series!</desc>
		<releasedate>20230419T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Square Enix</developer>
		<publisher>Square Enix</publisher>
		<genre>Role-Playing</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Final.Fantasy.IV.Pixel.Remaster.nsp</path>
		<name>Final Fantasy IV Pixel Remaster</name>
		<desc>The original FINAL FANTASY IV comes to life with completely new graphics and audio as a 2D pixel remaster!
A remodeled 2D take on the fourth game in the world-renowned FINAL FANTASY series! Enjoy the timeless story told through charming retro graphics. All the magic of the original, with improved ease of play.

The Kingdom of Baron sent their elite airship fleet, the Red Wings, to attack the surrounding countries. Distressed by his mission, Cecil, a dark knight and captain of the Red Wings, decides to fight against the tyrannical Baron with his trusted friend and his paramour at his side. In his search for the crystals, Cecil must travel over land, under the ground, to the Land of Summons, and even to the moon. Join forces with Kain the dragoon, Rosa the white mage, Rydia the summoner, and many more skilled allies.

FFIV is the first title to introduce the dynamic "Active Time Battle" system, where time moves even during battle, giving the players an exciting sense of urgency.Thanks to the wide appeal of the game, this revolutionary system would be implemented in many future titles in the series.

WItness the dramatic story and dynamic battles in this fourth installment of the FINAL FANTASY series!</desc>
		<releasedate>20230419T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Square Enix</developer>
		<publisher>Square Enix</publisher>
		<genre>Role-Playing</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Final.Fantasy.Pixel.Remaster.nsp</path>
		<name>Final Fantasy Pixel Remaster</name>
		<desc>The original FINAL FANTASY comes to life with completely new graphics and audio as a 2D pixel remaster!
A remodeled 2D take on the first game in the world-renowned FINAL FANTASY series! Enjoy the timeless story told through charming retro graphics. All the magic of the original, with improved ease of play.

Earth, fire, water, wind... The light that once shone within the four Crystals was lost. Darkness covered the land, until the only hope for humanity rested in legends past. Become the Warriors of Light and embark on your own journey to restore power to the Crystals and save the world.

Switch between classes to improve your characters. Traverse the wide world with your airship and other vessels. Return to the game that started it all.</desc>
		<releasedate>20230419T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Square Enix</developer>
		<publisher>Square Enix</publisher>
		<genre>Role-Playing</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Final.Fantasy.V.Pixel.Remaster.nsp</path>
		<name>Final Fantasy V Pixel Remaster</name>
		<desc>The original FINAL FANTASY V comes to life with completely new graphics and audio as a 2D pixel remaster!

A remodeled 2D take on the fifth game in the world-renowned FINAL FANTASY series! Enjoy the timeless story told through charming retro graphics. All the magic of the original, with improved ease of play.

The King of Tycoon has sensed a disturbance in the wind. When the crystals that balance the powers of the world are threatened, the king hastens to the rescue...only to go missing. Somewhere a young man and his Chocobo find themselves drawn toward friends that will change their destiny.

Building on the job systems of previous games, FFV includes a diverse selection of jobs to try, and a unique ability system that lets you combine skills.

Develop your characters with free reign, and master your battle tactics in the fifth installment of the FINAL FANTASY series!

----------------------------------------------------------------------

■ Beautifully revived with new graphics and sound!
・Universally updated 2D pixel graphics, including the iconic FINAL FANTASY character pixel designs created by Kazuko Shibuya, the original artist and current collaborator.
・Beautifully rearranged soundtrack in a faithful FINAL FANTASY style, overseen by original composer Nobuo Uematsu.

■Improved gameplay!
・Including modernized UI, auto-battle options, and more.
・Switch the soundtrack between the rearranged version, created for the pixel remaster, or the original version, capturing the sound of the original game.
・Now possible to switch between different fonts, including the default font and a pixel-based font based on the atmosphere of the original game.
・Additional boost features to expand gameplay options, including switching off random encounters and adjusting experience gained multipliers between 0 and 4.
・Dive into the world of the game with supplemental extras like the bestiary, illustration gallery, and music player.</desc>
		<releasedate>20230419T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Square Enix</developer>
		<publisher>Square Enix</publisher>
		<genre>Role-Playing</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Final.Fantasy.VI.Pixel.Remaster.nsp</path>
		<name>Final Fantasy VI Pixel Remaster</name>
		<desc>FINAL FANTASY VI is a game that’s beloved by fans and critics alike.

That’s partly thanks to its incredible setting and story. It’s set in a land where magic has disappeared, and humanity has instead turned to iron, gunpowder, steam and other technology.

Actually, it would be more accurate to say that magic is mostly gone - a young woman enslaved by the evil Empire still has the power. When she encounters a powerful ancient being called an Esper, she sets off a chain of events that will have epic and terrible consequences.</desc>
		<releasedate>20230419T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Square Enix</developer>
		<publisher>Square Enix</publisher>
		<genre>Role-Playing</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Another_Code_Recollection.USA.xci</path>
		<name>Another Code: Recollection</name>
		<desc>The Nintendo DS game Trace Memory and its Wii sequel – which was never released in North America – are coming together, fully enhanced, on the Nintendo Switch system. A young girl named Ashley receives a letter from her father, who she thought had passed away. Seeking answers, she sets off for a solitary island in search of him. Once there, Ashley encounters puzzles and obstacles that threaten to hinder her investigation. Find the traces of her past and experience the full story for the first time in Another Code: Recollection,launching on Nintendo Switch Jan. 19, 2024. Pre-orders begin today in Nintendo eShop.</desc>
		<releasedate>20240119T000000</releasedate>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure, Puzzle</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Super_Mario_Bros_Wonder.xci</path>
		<name>Super Mario Bros. Wonder</name>
		<desc>Find wonder in the next evolution of Mario funClassic Mario side-scrolling gameplay is turned on its head with the addition of Wonder Flowers. These game-changing items trigger spectacular moments you have to see to believe...Witness pipes coming alive, wreak havoc as a giant spiky ball, and see even more unexpected events called Wonder Effects.Pick from heroic Super Mario™ characters and Power-UpsChoose from familiar characters including Mario, Luigi, Peach, Daisy, Yoshi and Toad. Transform into Elephant Mario to use your trunk to trounce enemies with a surprising new Power-Up!Share the wonder with friends and Mario fansTeam up with up to three friends locally* and gather around one Nintendo Switch™ system to experience the game-bending Wonder Effects together as you tackle courses as a team and help each other on your way to the goal.</desc>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>20231020T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Platform / Run Jump</genre>
		<players>1-4</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Contra_Operation_Galuga.USA.nsp</path>
		<name>Contra: Operation Galuga</name>
		<desc>A new entry in the legendary Contra series is here! Contra: Operation Galuga is a thorough reimagining of the classic run-'n'-gun action game from the '80s, featuring modern graphics and sound, new stages, new enemies and bosses, new play mechanics, an updated weapons system, and explosive co-op combat for up to two players in Story Mode or four players in Arcade Mode!
When the Red Falcon terrorist group takes over the Galuga Islands off the coast of New Zealand, elite Contra commandos Bill Rizer and Lance Bean springs into action, initiating an all-out war in which the fate of mankind hangs in the balance!
Run, jump, and shoot your way through eight levels using a devastating arsenal - including the spread shot, laser, and homing missiles - now with stackable upgrades and awesome Overload abilities! The intense action is customizable with three difficulty settings plus a variety of additional challenge options. The true Contra legacy begins now! Key </desc>
		<releasedate>20240312T000000</releasedate>
		<publisher>Konami</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1-4</players>
	</game>
</gameList>
