<?xml version="1.0"?>
<gameList>
	<game>
		<path>./Driver - You Are the Wheelman (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Driver : You Are the Wheelman</name>
		<desc>As Tanner, you're going undercover to be the wheelman for a crime syndicate in order to break open a big case. On the way, you'll eliminate competition, drive getaway cars, scare some people silly, evade plenty of police, dodge bad guys, smash through a few windows, save your love interest, and much more through four cities (Miami, San Francisco, Los Angeles, and New York).

Perform authentic manuevers like donuts, 180 spin, 360 spin, reverse 180 spin, and more as you cut through alley ways, across sidewalks and parks, smash park benches and and drive over traffic cones. Many different cars to try (most you'll recognize). Will you save the day?</desc>
		<releasedate>19990630T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Reflections</developer>
		<publisher>GT Interactive</publisher>
		<genre>Race, Driving</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Ehrgeiz - God Bless the Ring (US).chd</path>
		<name>Ehrgeiz : God Bless the Ring</name>
		<desc>An ancient weapon of unknown origin was found in a German castle some fifty years ago. Since it was obviously something of value, it was decided that it would be awarded to the best fighter in the world. After all, who would appreciate a weapon more than an experienced fighter? Eleven of the world's finest combatants (including Cloud Strife, Tifa Lockhart and Vincent Valentine) have set out to claim this prize.
 The mysterious artifact came to be known as Ehrgeiz, and the tournament that was built around it took on the very same name. Now rumors suggest that the door to a long-forgotten land can be unlocked with this weapon; a land that could reveal the secret of immortality. The tournament has taken on a whole new meaning!</desc>
		<releasedate>19990105T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Dreamfactory</developer>
		<publisher>Squaresoft</publisher>
		<genre>Fight</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Einhaender (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Einhänder</name>
		<desc>In 2192, a new city, Selene, is built on the moon. Over the years, Selene grows larger, more powerful, and more independent of the Earth - to the point that the moon and Earth battle in a war that winds down without a definite victory for either side. In 2242, war breaks out again - the Earth slowly begins to win... except for the efforts of an experimental Selene technology known as Einhänders: flying machines with a "hand" that allows them to change weaponry mid-battle.

On December 12, 2245, Selene sends down 3 Einhänders in a last attempt to turn the tide of the war. You get to choose the craft to pilot, and it's up to you to battle your way through the Earth's monstrous defenses and win the battle.

The game is a traditional side-scrolling shooter, with rendered 3D backgrounds and enemies. The atmosphere of the game is very "industrial", down to the German industrial music playing in the background (think Einsturzende Neubauten mixed with Lords of Acid). The weapon-switching and claiming is an integral part of the game, as weapons have limited shots. This forces a bit more strategy than the usual button-mashing shooters inspire.</desc>
		<releasedate>19980505T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Square Enix</developer>
		<publisher>Sony Computer Entertainment</publisher>
		<genre>Shoot'em Up</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Ghost in the Shell (US).chd</path>
		<name>Ghost in the Shell</name>
		<desc>3rd person action game based on the Ghost in the Shell original comic by Masamune Shirow rather than Mamoru Oshi's film. You take the role of a new member in Kusanagi's anti-terrorist squad and get to accomplish missions on your Fuchikoma, (a spider-like AI equiped tank) thanks to which you can jump, stick to walls and ceilings and shoot the hell out of terrorists, all from a 1st or 3rd person point of view. As the missions procede a plot starts to surface concerning a giant skyscrapper, the Aereopolis II, which will eventually be solved after 12 single player missions. Other features include a training sequence, 3D stereo sound and wide anamorphic screen mode for 16x9 TVs.</desc>
		<releasedate>19971031T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Sony Computer Entertainment</developer>
		<publisher>Sony Computer Entertainment</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Gran Turismo 2 (USA) (Arcade Mode).chd</path>
		<name>Gran Turismo 2 (Arcade Mode)</name>
		<desc>Gran Turismo 2 is fundamentally based on the racing game genre. The player must maneuver an automobile to compete against artificially intelligent drivers on various race tracks. The game uses two different modes: arcade and simulation. In the arcade mode, the player can freely choose the courses and vehicles they wish to use. However, the simulation mode requires the player to earn driver's licenses, pay for vehicles, and earn trophies in order to unlock new courses. Gran Turismo 2 features nearly 650 automobiles and 27 racing tracks.</desc>
		<releasedate>19991223T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Polyphony Digital</developer>
		<publisher>Sony Computer Entertainment</publisher>
		<genre>Race, Driving</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./In Cold Blood (USA).m3u</path>
		<name>In Cold Blood</name>
		<desc>In Cold Blood is adventure and infiltration on Playstation. Seven of the nine missions offered are in fact flashbacks. As John Cord, an MI6 agent with amnesia, you must avoid guards and cameras, defeat security systems and discover the identity of the person who betrayed you.</desc>
		<releasedate>20010530T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Revolution Software</developer>
		<publisher>Sony Computer Entertainment</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./No One Can Stop Mr. Domino (US).chd</path>
		<name>No One Can Stop Mr. Domino</name>
		<desc>No one can stop Mr. Domino! Get ready for some seriously addictive action in this wild style 3D-strategy puzzle game. Move out fast to keep those dominoes toppling! If you don't, the Dreaded Domino Effect will take hold and you will never want to stop! So go ahead. Try and stop Mr. Domino.</desc>
		<releasedate>19981031T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Artdink</developer>
		<publisher>JVC Music Europe</publisher>
		<genre>Puzzle-Game</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Oddworld - Abe's Oddysee (USA) (Rev 2).chd</path>
		<name>Oddworld : Abe's Oddysee</name>
		<desc>Abe's Oddysee begins with the eponymous protagonist as a prisoner in RuptureFarms, from which he narrates his story. He and many other Mudokons are slaves to Molluck the Glukkon, the owner of RuptureFarms: "the biggest meat-processing plant on Oddworld". Abe is a contented floor-waxer First Class and currently Employee of the Year.

At the time of the story, the ingredients of the corporation's three major "Tasty Treats" (Scrab Cakes, Paramite Pies, and Meech Munchies) are quickly running out, with the Meeches already extinct. While working late, Abe overhears Molluck's plan to use the Mudokon slaves as meat products called "Mudokon Pops!", which frightens Abe into escaping from the factory.</desc>
		<releasedate>19970919T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Oddworld Inhabitants</developer>
		<publisher>GT Interactive</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./PaRappa the Rapper (USA) (En,Fr,De,Es,It).chd</path>
		<name>PaRappa the Rapper</name>
		<desc>The rapping pup, PaRappa, dreams of impressing his friend, the beautiful Sunny Funny, and going out on a date with her.  But what he lacks is confidence - help PaRappa rap his way through learning Kung Fu, a driving test, cooking and more, all in order to get the girl.  And remember - You Gotta Believe!

PaRappa the Rapper is a game based on lyrics, music and rhythm.  The game itself is very basic - each stage has a 'teacher', that PaRappa must follow.  You'll see the teacher say some lyrics, and then PaRappa must copy the teacher by pressing the appropriate buttons to repeat those lyrics back.  Rap well, and you'll be able to continue; fudge up the lyrics, and the music will start to distort and the teacher will become displeased.  Continue to mess up and you'll fail the stage.

Of course, the goal is not to copy the teacher, but instead to outperform them - you can do this by improvising in the song's gaps.  Listen to how the song goes, and improvise in time to the music; if you perform well enough, the teacher will step aside, leaving you to freestyle on your own!

The PSP version of the game is a remake of the PlayStation original.  However, it includes a few upgrades, such as a 16:9 display, sharper graphics, game sharing, multiplayer support of up to four players, and the addition of song remixes, which can be downloaded via the internet onto your Memory Stick Duo.</desc>
		<releasedate>19971031T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nanaon-Sha</developer>
		<publisher>Sony Computer Entertainment</publisher>
		<genre>Music and Dance</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Parasite Eve (USA).m3u</path>
		<name>Parasite Eve</name>
		<desc>An ordinary day in New York for rookie police officer Aya Brea. Christmas Eve is the present day, and you've decided to visit the opera theater. Now this is where the fireworks begin. Suddenly audience members are set on fire, toasted completely, and it appears that the lead vocal is the source of this burning terror. Yet you appear to be immune, and as a police officer you're always on duty, so you must confront the danger.

There has to be some connection between the two of you, as that seems the only rational explanation. What if mitochondria are a species on its own, more advanced then humankind, and using them only to create environments and civilization for themselves? What if humankind are just hosts? What if mitochondria are the natural enemy of humankind? That would make Aya their natural enemy, so the battle for survival and uncovering the truth has already started.

The game is played over six days, each day bringing its own quest. Environments range from Central Park and the American Museum of Natural History to a police office and hospital, all of them modeled like realistic places and most of them crawling with bloodthirsty mutant animals. Combat is different from traditional RPGs, as while you still take turns attacking and/or using parasite powers, you'll be able to run across the battlefield and dodge enemy fire or even strike from a better angle or behind. As Aya levels up she will gain access to parasite powers, such as healing or supercharging a bullet with energy. These powers will deplete a recharging energy bar, although the bar will recharge slower the longer combat drags on. Aya will find many guns of various types throughout the game, and every gun can be modified with extra stats, either with special items, or by breaking down another gun to move over its bonus stats or special effects. The same is true for armor Aya finds.</desc>
		<releasedate>19980908T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Squaresoft</developer>
		<publisher>Squaresoft</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Parasite Eve II (USA).m3u</path>
		<name>Parasite Eve II</name>
		<desc>Aya Brea is back in a new game. This time there are fewer RPG elements than the first game, and the game plays more like Resident Evil. Battles are now in real-time, and a new range of weapons are available. Defeating enemies rewards money as well as points used to revive and power-up Aya's suppressed Parasite powers, like healing and igniting foes. Weapons and armor now have fixed stats, but attachments can be swapped in and out of them to modify their properties.

After surviving the events of Parasite Eve Aya left her job as a cop and became a member of MIST (Mitochondrion Investigation and Suppression Agency) in order to hunt down the remnant mutants spawned by Eve's awakening. In the year 2000 a new breed of Neo Mitochondrion takes over the Akropolis Tower in downtown LA. Aya is called in and uncovers a secret organization that threatens all humanity.</desc>
		<releasedate>20000902T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Squaresoft</developer>
		<publisher>Squaresoft</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./R4 - Ridge Racer Type 4 (USA).chd</path>
		<name>R4 : Ridge Racer Type 4</name>
		<desc>Powering beyond RIDGE and RAGE RACER, high-speed control and advanced dynamics accekerate the rush of a first class victory.

-In-depth Grand Prix Mode
-Incredible two-player action
-40+ unique car models with over 300 variations
-Hyper-evolved graphics for the supreme racing experience</desc>
		<releasedate>19990501T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Namco</developer>
		<publisher>Sony Computer Entertainment</publisher>
		<genre>Race, Driving</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Silent Hill (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Silent Hill</name>
		<desc>Silent Hill is a 1999 survival horror video game for the PlayStation. The first in a series about a mysterious town of the same name, Silent Hill generated a direct sequel, three indirect sequels, a prequel and a film adaptation. The game was included in Sony's Greatest Hits and Platinum Range of budget titles as a result of strong sales. A reinterpretation of the game was developed for the Wii, PlayStation 2 and PlayStation Portable.
The plot focuses on Harry Mason as he searches for his daughter, Cheryl, who has disappeared following a car accident which left Harry unconscious. He finds Silent Hill to be largely abandoned, shrouded in a thick fog, snowing out of season, filled with monsters and being over taken by a hellish otherworld. As Harry scours the town, he begins learning about the history of Silent Hill and stumbles upon a cult ritual undertaken to bring a god to Earth.</desc>
		<releasedate>19990131T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Team Silent</developer>
		<publisher>Konami</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Silhouette Mirage (US).chd</path>
		<name>Silhouette Mirage</name>
		<desc>In an apocalyptic future, the Edo computer has gone beserk, dividing the world's inhabitants into two mutant classes, Silhouette and Mirage. Now, the watchguard computer safety system has sent forth the Messenger of Justice to travel to Edo and repair the damage before the world is lost forever. As the Messenger, Shyna Nera Shyna, blast, beat, and bash your way through seven wild and bizarre stages using friendly parasite weapons to aid your advance against wacky enemies, huge fully-animated bosses, and devilishly difficult obstacles. Providing the utmost in playability and replayability, the game wizards at Treasure, the brilliant minds behinds such international hits as Gunstar Heroesâ„¢, Dynamite Headdyâ„¢, Mischief Makersâ„¢, and Guardian Heroesâ„¢ have come up with another sure-fire classic that pushes the 2-D capabilities of your PlayStationÂ® game console to its limit, and come up with a hit!</desc>
		<releasedate>20000105T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Working Designs</developer>
		<publisher>Treasure</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Spider-Man (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Spider-Man</name>
		<desc>Spider-Man is the first 3D game to star the popular web-slinger.  It is loosely based on Spider-Man: The Animated Series and Spider-Man Unlimited and features some of the voice cast from each and similar character designs.

Peter Parker is attending a demonstration of the reformed Dr. Otto Octavius's new invention when an imposter Spider-Man steals the device.  Spider-Man must work to clear his name and uncover the sinister motives behind the device's theft.

This game features appearances not only by most major Spider-Man characters, but cameos by numerous other characters from the Marvel Universe, such as the Human Torch, Punisher, Daredevil and Captain America.

Spider-Man's webs are greatly emphasized.  He can use them both for navigational purposes, like swinging or ziplining, and for offensive and defensive combat, such as tying up a villain, coating his fists with web for extra oomph, or building a protective shield.  His web supply is limited though and he must find new cartridges or risk running out.  The wall-crawling powers are also prominently features.  Spider-Man can cling to any wall or ceiling.  This is used for basic environmental navigation and for stealth as there are many sequences where you crawl over the heads of unsuspecting thugs, or drop down and catch them off-guard.

Combat is based around Spider-Man's ability to jump, kick, punch and web.  By combining these with direction and in various combinations, Spider-Man is able to throw objects such as furniture, hurl web balls, yank enemies into melee range and follow up with a flurry of hits, among other things.  There are a number of boss-battles as well, all of which are puzzle-based.

Missions vary from the fairly common fight-your way-to-the-goal or find-the-key-that-unlocks-the-door types to races to catch some or evade them or just trying to avoid the police.

There are several side goals in addition the main mission including multiple unlockable Spider-Man costumes and numerous hidden comic book covers to find.</desc>
		<releasedate>20000830T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Activision</developer>
		<publisher>Neversoft</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Tales of Destiny (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Tales of Destiny</name>
		<desc>A great swordsman named Stahn Aileron takes a ride on a giant dragon ship. During the flight, the ship is attacked by pirates. Looking for a weapon to defend himself, Stahn discovers a sword. Very soon he finds out it is not just an ordinary sword, but the legendary talking sword Dymlos, who has been sleeping for many years and who can be awakened only if the world is in grave danger. But what exactly is the danger that awakened Dymlos now? With the help of a few friends, Stahn decides to explore the world and to find out what is wrong. 
 "Tales of Destiny" is a follower of the SNES RPG Tales of Phantasia. The combat in this game is action-based. You control the main hero in real time and make him perform various attacks. Other party members are controlled by the game's AI, but you can pause the battle at any time and assign new combat style to any one of them.
 PLOT:
 In the past, a comet crashed into the world, throwing dust clouds into the sky and shrouding the world in cold and darkness. At about the same time, the inhabitants, the Aethers, discovered a new form of energy from the meteorite's core, which they named Lens. Combining this with further research, the people were able to create cities in the sky and live in them. Unfortunately, only a select few were chosen, leaving the rest of the people to remain on the bleak surface of the planet. These people became known as the Erthers.
 Over time, the sky's inhabitants became known as the Aetherians and their Aeropolis cities. They created a horrific weapon called the Belcrant that shot down any who dared oppose them. This caused full scale war to erupt between the two civilizations, now known as the Aeth'er Wars. However, regardless of their will and persistence, the Aetherians continued to have the power to dominate every engagement through the use of their superweapon.
 In their disgust of their civilization's elitist behavior, a group of Aetherian scientists went to the surface. There, with aid from the people, they were able to create special swords, called Swordians, that were sentient. Unlike other weapons, these swords chose their masters and were able to call upon the elements of nature to do their will. Using these weapons, the people of the surface finally had an edge against the Aetherians.
 Thanks in part to the Swordians and their masters, scores of Aeropolis were sunk to the depths of the ocean. In the end, the Erthers claimed victory over the Aetherians. Thousands of years later, this story has been mostly forgotten. In the meantime, the purposeless Swordians fell into a deep stasis sleep, only to awaken when grave threats rose once again.
 The story of the game begins when country-boy-turned-adventurer Stahn Aileron, who seeks fame and adventure, sneaks aboard the flying ship Draconis as a stowaway. He is found out by the crew and forced to work as a deckhand, but when a large hostile force attacks the ship, the crew is overwhelmed and Stahn breaks free during the ensuing chaos. Looking for a usable weapon to fend off the attackers, he gains access to a storeroom and discovers a "junk" sword. However, the sword starts talking to him, calling itself Dymlos and claiming to be a sentient Swordian from the Aeth'er Wars. Armed with Dymlos, Stahn fights his way to an escape pod, which he uses to escape the rapidly descending ship before it crashes into the ground.
 Dymlos becomes the key to the fame, fortune, and adventure Stahn seeks as the young man meets other Swordians, quickly becoming embroiled in a battle for a relic of the Aeth'er Wars: a huge, extremely powerful Lens called the Eye of Atamoni.
 GAMEPLAY:
 Tales of Destiny continues the trademark Linear Motion Battle System (LMBS) of the Tales series, with the E-LMBS (Enhanced Linear Motion Battle System), there are some graphical enhancements to the system as it was first implemented in Tales of Phantasia. Nevertheless, the combat is still very similar to the first game in the series, taking place on a 2-D plane where characters and enemies act in real time. Typical RPG conventions of HP, TP, experience, and leveling apply. Melee and ranged attacks are executed in real time, with spell casting requiring a chanting time that increases directly with the complexity of the spell being cast. When the chanting of a spell is complete, game-time temporarily stops as the spell animation is carried out and damage is assigned, so spells essentially act as interrupts. Special melee and ranged attacks do more damage or have more hits than normal attacks, but require technical points, or TP, to be consumed for use. Also, the battle system rewards the player with extra experience for stringing together multi-hit combos. The end result of this break from traditional turn-based RPG battle systems is a more fast-paced and reaction oriented system that behaves more like a fighting game and less like a typical Final Fantasy-esque title.</desc>
		<releasedate>19980915T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Namco</developer>
		<publisher>Namco</publisher>
		<genre>Role playing games</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Tales of Destiny II (USA).m3u</path>
		<name>Tales of Destiny II</name>
		<desc>Reid and Farrah are two friends who live together in a little town. One day, a mysterious young girl falls down from the sky and is found by the two friends. After a while, they discover that her name is Meredy and that she has come to prevent the collision of her world Celestia with Inferia, the planet on which Reid and Farrah live. The three decide to set out on a quest to collect elemental spiritual beings that alone can stop the terrible disaster.

Tales of Destiny II (Tales of Eternia in Japan) is an action RPG with a somewhat unusual battle system. Although there is a party, the battles occur in real time. The player physically controls only Reid, making him perform various attacks. The other party members are controlled by the game's AI, but it is possible to choose an overall strategy for their actions: for example, one should concentrate on healing while the other attacks physically, etc.</desc>
		<releasedate>20010910T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Namco</developer>
		<publisher>Namco</publisher>
		<genre>Role playing games</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Tekken 3 (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Tekken 3</name>
		<desc>An ancient evil force has reawakened, attacking in secret and feeding on the souls of mighty warriors. To lure it out of hiding will take the greatest fighting contest the world has ever seen... Tekken 3. Some are fighting for revenge, some for honor, ultimately, all are fighting for their lives and the fate of all mankind.</desc>
		<releasedate>19980429T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Namco</developer>
		<publisher>Namco</publisher>
		<genre>Fight</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Tenchu - Stealth Assassins (USA) (Rev 1).chd</path>
		<name>Tenchu : Stealth Assassins</name>
		<desc>After firing your grappling hook to the rooftop of a small house, you pull yourself up and notice a guard pacing back and forth on the ground. He doesn't see you as you begin to crawl and sneak around on the roof. If he detects your presence, you will be in a world of hurt; you will blow your mission and risk death. Patiently, you wait for the right time to jump down -- and end his life while his back is turned.
 Set in 16th century Japan, Tenchu: Stealth Assassins is a simulation of the ways of the stealthy ninja. You'll chose between two characters, Rikimaru and Ayame, with a main objective of remaining unseen throughout ten non-linear missions. You will move through the shadows, make your way across rooftops, dash through trees -- anything to cloak yourself from enemy sight. While completing the missions, you are judged on three levels that measure your success in the fields of elusiveness and effectiveness.
 Each mission is different in its design and goal. Your mentor will have you run secret errands to informants, kill evil merchants and thieves, and rescue captive ninjas. Along the way, the enemy resistance has set up traps and assigned guards to keep a watchful eye for any interference (that would be you). Because Tenchu is a simulation of sorts, running up and engaging an enemy combat is not advised -- that's not the way of the ninja. 
 A ninja is cunning and in order to uphold his duty, he must remain unseen. If you brazenly walk up to a group of enemies and try to kill them all, you may get through a couple, but you will ultimately fail and dishonor your people. As far as weaponry goes, make use of throwing stars and actual ninja assassin swords. For the truly cunning players, poisoned rice and smoke bombs are included as special items. If a guard will not go away, try putting some rice down for him to eat - he'll get sick and collapse.</desc>
		<releasedate>19980820T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Acquire</developer>
		<publisher>Activision</publisher>
		<genre>Action / Adventure</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Tenchu 2 - Birth of the Stealth Assassins (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Tenchu 2 : Birth of the Stealth Assassins</name>
		<desc>Before the events of Tenchu, the House of Gohda is rocked by betrayal. As shadow warriors Rikimaru, Ayame and Tatsumaru, you are called on to restore pride to the name of your master. For you have been born to a life of honor... a life of stealth. Discover even more ways to slay your foes with 21 new stealth kill techniques. Take on the role of three ninja assassins, each with their own story and fighting techniques. Strike from the shadows in 29 new day and night stealth missions. Utilize a variety of new ninja weapons and items, like flaming arrows and invisibility.</desc>
		<releasedate>20000807T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Acquire</developer>
		<publisher>Activision</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./The Misadventures of Tron Bonne (US).chd</path>
		<name>The Misadventures of Tron Bonne</name>
		<desc>Rather than focusing on the heroic protagonists of Mega Man Legends series, the game follows series anti-hero Tron Bonne, sister of the criminal Bonne family of air pirates. The Japanese counterpart included PocketStation support whereas the North American and European version did not. With a limited production run, the game is one of the rarest PlayStation games</desc>
		<releasedate>20000430T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Thunder Force V - Perfect System (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Thunder Force V : Perfect System</name>
		<desc>In a grim future where a once-benevolent alien technology has turned against humanity, only a ragtag group of ace pilots can save the Earth from total annihilation. Code name: Thunder Force! Witness the first 32-bit installment of the massively popular shooter series! Five spectacular weapons with multiple power-up levels let you blast through waves of metallic predators, and look good doing it. A constant barrage of innovative enemies keeps you intrigued while you struggle to stay alive. A speaker-imploding soundtrack has your foot tapping as your fingers are mashing. Unbelievable rendered cutscenes draw, no-DRAG you kicking and screaming into the action. Put simply, it's the ultimate hardcore gaming blast-o-rama!</desc>
		<releasedate>19980831T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Techno Soft</developer>
		<publisher>Working Designs</publisher>
		<genre>Shoot'em Up</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Tomba! 2 - The Evil Swine Return (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Tomba! 2 : The Evil Swine Return</name>
		<desc>Explore an all new 3D world. Use your trusty fire hammer, ice boomerang or or blackjack to turn the evil pigs into bacon. Throw on super-duds like a flying squirrel suit or high speed turbo pants. There's no limit to the stuff you can do.</desc>
		<releasedate>19991231T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Whoopee Camp</developer>
		<publisher>Sony Computer Entertainment</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Twisted Metal 2 (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Twisted Metal 2</name>
		<desc>Twisted Metal features destructive car combat, playable either as a complete tournament or a single match The action takes place in 8 different locations around the world, on differing surfaces, many featuring destructible buildings and landmarks.

Combat takes place between a wide array of vehicles ranging from a man strapped between two wheels to an ice cream truck. They have their own strengths and weaknesses,  using an eclectic arrangement of weaponry include bombs and missiles, and resulting in its own end sequence, complete with an ironic line in humour.</desc>
		<releasedate>19961031T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Sony Computer Entertainment</developer>
		<publisher>Sony Computer Entertainment</publisher>
		<genre>Race, Driving</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./WipEout 2097 (Europe).chd</path>
		<name>Wipeout XL</name>
		<desc>A breakneck speed racing game set in the year 2097 featuring anti-gravity hovercrafts. The vehicles can "pick up" weapons and power-ups by flying over the weapon grids marked on the track.</desc>
		<releasedate>19960930T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Psygnosis</developer>
		<publisher>Psygnosis</publisher>
		<genre>Race, Driving</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Soul Blade (USA) (Rev 1).chd</path>
		<name>Soul Blade</name>
		<desc>In the 16th century, a sword surfaces that is so powerful, so evil that warriors from all over the globe seek it out. It is Soul Edge, a demon blade. From America to Europe to Japan, these warriors fight each other for the chance to obtain it. Soul Blade is a 3D weapons fighting game that chronicles their story.

A complete 3D fighting game that allows for side steps, Soul Blade has twelve colorful fighters (ten standard, two hidden, plus additional costumes for a few fighters), each with various weapons and styles. The first ten can be used in all the combat modes, while the hidden two can only be used in versus and arcade mode.

Namco enhanced the arcade version (called Soul Edge) by adding a well done CGI intro, plus a story mode to the addition of the traditional team, survival, and time attack modes. The story mode goes into greater detail about each character, and is presented in an ancient book format. The story mode also allows you to unlock more of each characters' extra weapons. These weapons, which vary in lengths, stats, and durability, add to the options available players in the versus mode.

Soul Blade's sequel is SoulCalibur, both in the arcades and for the Sega Dreamcast</desc>
		<releasedate>19970101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Namco</developer>
		<publisher>Sony Computer Entertainment</publisher>
		<genre>Fight</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Tomba! (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Tomba!</name>
		<desc>Aside from sporting a wacky pink hairdo, Tomba! offers a long and brain twisting experience that mixes the traditional 2D side scrolling action/platformer with the elements of a role-playing game. The game starts out simple enough with the evil Koma Pigs stealing Tomba's bracelet, which was given to him by his grandfather. You assume the role of Tomba and begin your adventure. Little do you know that the quest for your bracelet will turn into so much more.

Because of its role-playing elements, in Tomba!, your character will gain experience points, develop new skills and learn new things. He has seven abilities that can be learned throughout the duration of the game. Once all three experience meters reach level ten (in order to do this, Tomba must do certain things), he will unlock and learn an ability.</desc>
		<releasedate>19980630T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Whoopee Camp</developer>
		<publisher>Sony Computer Entertainment</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
</gameList>
