<?xml version="1.0"?>
<gameList>
	<game>
		<path>./airwlkrs.zip</path>
		<name>Air Walkers</name>
		<desc>Air Walkers is an unreleased basketball game by Data East on the Sega Model2 hardware. Thankfully, a prototype was dumped to prevent this game from being completely forgotten.</desc>
		<releasedate>19970101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Data East</developer>
		<publisher>Data East</publisher>
		<genre>Sports / Basketball</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./doa.zip</path>
		<name>Dead or Alive</name>
		<desc>Dead or Alive is a fighting game and the first entry in the long-running Dead or Alive series. The gameplay of Dead or Alive was unique at the time of its debut because it featured different choices in gameplay than other 3D fighting games (at least at the time).</desc>
		<releasedate>19960101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Tecmo</developer>
		<publisher>Tecmo</publisher>
		<genre>Fight</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./desert.zip</path>
		<name>Desert Tank</name>
		<desc>Desert Tank is a 3-D tank simulator.</desc>
		<releasedate>19940101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>SEGA</developer>
		<publisher>SEGA</publisher>
		<genre>Shoot'em Up</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./dynabb.zip</path>
		<name>Dynamite Baseball</name>
		<desc>Dynamite Baseball is a 3-D baseball game.</desc>
		<releasedate>19960101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>SEGA</developer>
		<publisher>SEGA</publisher>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./dynabb97.zip</path>
		<name>Dynamite Baseball 97</name>
		<desc>Dynamite Baseball '97 is a 3-D baseball game, sequel to the original "Dynamite Baseball", which was released in 1996. 

The music is very identical to the songs from the Sega Model 3 game, "Harley-Davidson &amp; L.A. Riders", and an earlier Sega Model 2 game, "Sega Ski Super-G".</desc>
		<releasedate>19970101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>SEGA</developer>
		<publisher>SEGA</publisher>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./dynamcop.zip</path>
		<name>Dynamite Cop</name>
		<desc>Dynamite Cop is a 3D beat 'em up for up to two players in which players play as either Bruno Delinger, Jean Ivy, or Eddie Brown and fight through levels on board a cruise ship and on a deserted island to save the President's daughter from a band of modern-day pirates led by Wolf "White Fang" Hongo, the main antagonist from the first game. The classic Sega arcade game Tranquilizer Gun (1980) is included as a bonus game on the Dreamcast version. Clearing all missions will enable you to play Tranquilizer Gun an unlimited number of times.</desc>
		<releasedate>19980101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>AM1</developer>
		<publisher>SEGA</publisher>
		<genre>Beat'em Up</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./fvipers.zip</path>
		<name>Fighting Vipers</name>
		<desc>City of Armstone, year unknown. The mayor has decided to organise a fighting tournament, with the grand finale to be held on top of the city tower. The Vipers, young urban warriors, decide to fight each other, each with their own goal in mind. The eight Vipers come from different backgrounds, such as hard rocker Raxel, the orphan who longs to meet his father Bahn, former gang leader Tokyo, catwalk queen Grace, the giant with an unknown past Sanman, construction worker and former marine apprentice Jane, aspiring fashion designer Candy and skateboarder Picky, not to mention Mahler, who has a score to settle with the mayor.
Fighting Vipers featured a wall surrounding the battle area and equipping each fighter with two-piece armour that can only be broken by powerful blows. Once the armour is destroyed, the unlucky fighter is more vulnerable to the opponent's blows, and damage can also be collected after hitting the wall or the ground after a throw.</desc>
		<releasedate>19950101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>SEGA</developer>
		<publisher>SEGA</publisher>
		<genre>Fight / Versus</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./indy500.zip</path>
		<name>Indy 500 Twin</name>
		<desc>Ladies and Gentlemen, Start Your Engines!!</desc>
		<releasedate>19950101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Sega AM1</developer>
		<publisher>SEGA</publisher>
		<genre>Race, Driving</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./lastbrnx.zip</path>
		<name>Last Bronx</name>
		<desc>Nine gang leaders battle it out for control over Tokyo city in this AM3 developed arcade fighting game. It was the first motion captured fighting game released back in May 1996 to Arcades in Japan.</desc>
		<releasedate>19960101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>SEGA</developer>
		<publisher>SEGA</publisher>
		<genre>Fight / Versus</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./manxtt.zip</path>
		<name>Manx TT SuperBike</name>
		<desc>This game is a motorcycle race with the standard schema "gone last, finish first". It was based on the real-life Isle of Man Trophy race. Only 2 tracks are available, a short and a long version of the course.
The arcade cabinet provided a life-size bike on which to sit, which was really fun. However, it aged more badly than other similar games.</desc>
		<releasedate>19950101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>SEGA</developer>
		<publisher>SEGA</publisher>
		<genre>Motorcycle Race, 1st Pers.</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./motoraid.zip</path>
		<name>Motor Raid</name>
		<desc>Motor Raid (c) 1997 Sega.  - TECHNICAL -  Sega Model 2A hardware.  Main CPU : i960KB, 68000 Sound Chips : SCSP  Players : 2 Buttons : 4  This was a rom swap upgrade for "Manx TT Superbike".  - TRIVIA -  Released in October 1997.  Marvelous Entertainment r</desc>
		<releasedate>19970101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>SEGA</developer>
		<publisher>SEGA</publisher>
		<genre>Motorcycle Race, 3rd Pers.</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./overrev.zip</path>
		<name>Over Rev</name>
		<desc>Over REV is a 1997 racing game developed by Jaleco for Sega's Model 2 arcade board. It features four nicely rendered tracks across the Greater Tokyo Area. Although it has some serious issues with driving and collision physics, if you stick with the game long enough to overcome its intricacies, it can be pretty rewarding. Like Jaleco's other Model 2 racer, Super GT 24h, you'll want to use an automatic transmission.</desc>
		<releasedate>19970101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Jaleco</developer>
		<publisher>Jaleco</publisher>
		<genre>Race, Driving</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./pltkids.zip</path>
		<name>Pilot Kids</name>
		<desc>A cutesy horizontal shooter where you play a kid in an airplane shooting at awesome bosses like an attack dog.</desc>
		<releasedate>19980101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Psikyo</developer>
		<publisher>Psikyo</publisher>
		<genre>Shoot'em up / Horizontal</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./srallyc.zip</path>
		<name>Sega Rally Championship</name>
		<desc>Sega Rally Championship gameplay is both accessible and technical. The game provides 4 tracks of increasing difficulty, and 3 rally cars. The tracks are very detailed, and provide numerous challenges, as well as various track surfaces, side animations, and environments.</desc>
		<releasedate>19950101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>SEGA</developer>
		<publisher>SEGA</publisher>
		<genre>Race, Driving</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./skisuprg.zip</path>
		<name>Sega Ski Super G</name>
		<desc>In Sega Ski Super G, the objective is to race against other opponents under a time limit. The game has two modes: World Series and Time Attack.</desc>
		<releasedate>19960101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>SEGA</developer>
		<publisher>SEGA</publisher>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./stcc.zip</path>
		<name>Sega Touring Car Championship</name>
		<desc>Sega Touring Car Championship is a Sega Model 2C CRX arcade racing game developed by Sega AM5 in 1996. It is similar to Sega Rally Championship in design, but uses touring cars instead of rally cars. Unlike Sega Rally Championship, Sega Touring Car Championship has never seen a sequel, and it considered a far less successful game for a variety of reasons, most notably the steep difficulty curve and often awkward car handing.</desc>
		<releasedate>19960101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>SEGA</developer>
		<publisher>SEGA</publisher>
		<genre>Race, Driving</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./segawski.zip</path>
		<name>Sega Water Ski</name>
		<desc>The objective of this game is similar to the last game, "Top Skater". Except you're water-skiing, instead of skateboaring.</desc>
		<releasedate>19970101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>SEGA</developer>
		<publisher>SEGA</publisher>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./schamp.zip</path>
		<name>Sonic Championship</name>
		<desc>Sonic Championship is a 3D fighting game, featuring characters from the Sonic the Hedgehog franchise. The background story is that Doctor Eggman built the Death Egg II, a new version of his facility that appeared in previous games. Stopping him requires Chaos Emeralds, and various individuals including heroes like Sonic the Hedgehog and Miles "Tails" Prower participate in a fighting tournament to gather them. In total there are eight playable characters (nine in later console releases) and two bosses (Metal Sonic and Doctor Eggman).
Gameplay is mostly typical for a versus fighter, it is a one-on-one fight on a best two out of three basis. Players use jumps, punches, kicks and special weapons. Bean the Dynamite for example, a duck-like character who makes his debut in the Sonic universe, uses bombs. Blocking is done by making use of a limited supply of barriers. The whole action is illustrated in a comical fashion though, like one would expect from a Sonic game.</desc>
		<releasedate>19960101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>SEGA</developer>
		<publisher>SEGA</publisher>
		<genre>Fight</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./sgt24h.zip</path>
		<name>Super GT 24h</name>
		<desc>1996 arcade racing game. Work your way to the top spot within 5 laps</desc>
		<releasedate>19960101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Jaleco</developer>
		<publisher>Jaleco</publisher>
		<genre>Race, Driving</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./topskatr.zip</path>
		<name>Top Skater</name>
		<desc>The first high tech skateboard simulator hits the streets with full body racing action! Perform difficult moves like the pros, without breaking your appendages. Players can use their entire body to maneuver through ultra-challenging skateboarding courses... this is not a video game its a spectator sport! Choose from six unique characters with individual style and personality. Includes all the hard-core skateboard moves: kick flips, 180-degree turns, 360 flips, indy nose bones, Oilies and more!</desc>
		<releasedate>19970101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>SEGA</developer>
		<publisher>SEGA</publisher>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./vf2.zip</path>
		<name>Virtua Fighter 2</name>
		<desc>Virtua Fighter 2 is a fighting game developed by Sega. It is the sequel to Virtua Fighter and the second game in the Virtua Fighter series. It was created by the Sega's Yu Suzuki-headed AM2 and was released in the arcade in 1994. VF2 was known for breakthrough graphics at the time. It used Sega's Model 2 arcade hardware to run the game at 60 frames per second at a high resolution with no slowdown.

The arena size could be adjusted up to a very small platform or all the way to 82 meters, which in the genre is considered very large; this is the only game in the series—other than Virtua Fighter Remix—that could have such size adjustments. The physical energy meter could also be adjusted to infinity as well, giving you the advantage when beating opponents in the game or practicing moves against the computer player. Incidentally, players discovered that adjusting the arena to a smaller size and giving the characters infinite health could lead to mock sumo matches, wherein victory is achieved by knocking the other player out of the ring.</desc>
		<releasedate>19950101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>SEGA</developer>
		<publisher>SEGA</publisher>
		<genre>Fight</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./vstriker.zip</path>
		<name>Virtua Striker</name>
		<desc>Virtua Striker is the first three-dimensional computer graphic soccer gameby Sega, bringing extreme competition to the arcades.

State of the art texture mapping provides sophisticated reproduction of the World Cup atmosphere, with incredibly immersive game action and realistic backgrounds. It uses the same architecture as Virtua Fighter 2.</desc>
		<releasedate>19940101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>SEGA</developer>
		<publisher>SEGA</publisher>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./waverunr.zip</path>
		<name>Wave Runner</name>
		<desc>WaveRunner is a jet-ski racing game. This game features three courses, and up to four cabinets can be linked for multiplayer racing.</desc>
		<releasedate>19960101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>SEGA</developer>
		<publisher>SEGA</publisher>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./zerogun.zip</path>
		<name>Zero Gunner</name>
		<desc>In the future date of 2016, worldwide martial law is initiated when a widespread terrorist organization overthrew and took control of the world's military authorities. A group of ace helicopter pilots are secretly amassed in a special forces squadron called ZERO to travel around the world and destroy the occupied terrorist forces.</desc>
		<releasedate>19970101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Psikyo</developer>
		<publisher>Psikyo</publisher>
		<genre>Shoot'em Up</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./daytona.zip</path>
		<name>Daytona USA</name>
		<desc>Daytona USA is an excellent checkpoint-style racing game.</desc>
		<releasedate>19930101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>SEGA</developer>
		<publisher>SEGA</publisher>
		<genre>Race, Driving</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
</gameList>
