<?xml version="1.0"?>
<gameList>
	<game>
		<path>./Adventures of Batman and Robin, The (USA).chd</path>
		<name>The Adventures of Batman &amp; Robin</name>
		<desc>In The Adventures of Batman and Robin, Robin and Commissioner Gordon have both gone missing. The Dark Knight suspects that one or more of the usual suspects might be involved, including Poison Ivy, Riddler, and The Joker. He sets out in his trusty Batmobile to set the situation right. Much of the game consists of 3D driving action behind the wheel of the Batmobile. There are also levels in which the Caped Crusader must stage an aerial assault using the Batwing. In between levels, the player is treated to a series of cutscenes which comprise nearly an entire exclusive episode of Batman: The Animated Series, upon which the game is based.</desc>
		<releasedate>19951201T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Clockwork Tortoise</developer>
		<publisher>SEGA</publisher>
		<genre>Race, Driving</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Final Fight CD (Japan) (Rev A).chd</path>
		<name>Final Fight CD</name>
		<desc>The game is set in the metropolis of Metro City, a town constantly plagued by crime and violence. When the mayor, Mike Haggar, promises to clean up the city, the Mad Gear gang kidnaps his daughter Jessica and warns him not to interfere. Haggar responds going on a battle across the city to free her, bringing along her boyfriend Cody, and the ninjitsu master Guy to assist him.

</desc>
		<releasedate>19920101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>SEGA</publisher>
		<genre>Beat'em Up</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Lunar - Eternal Blue (USA) (RE).chd</path>
		<name>Lunar : Eternal Blue</name>
		<desc>Come back to the enchanting world of Lunar! Join Hiro and Ruby 1,000 years after the first adventure, as they work to unlock the secrets of the Blue Spire and the strange young girl they found within it! But be careful! Forces are at work trying to revive the evil Zophar and immerse Lunar in darkness forever! Journey to distant lands in search of the Goddess Althena, who may be the only one powerful enough to stop Zophar. Along the way, you'll meet exciting new characters, fight fully animated monsters, traverse snow-covered peaks, and crawl through slimy dungeons as you work towards the terrifying climax!</desc>
		<releasedate>19950101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Game Arts</developer>
		<publisher>Working Designs</publisher>
		<genre>Role playing games</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Lunar - The Silver Star (USA) (RE).chd</path>
		<name>Lunar : The Silver Star</name>
		<desc>Welcome to the world of Lunar, where dragons yet live and magic is valued above all else. Join Alex, the young adventurer as he begins a quest with his friends to save their land from the crushing advances of the Magic Emperor. Explore dungeons, fight terrifying monsters, and gather information from the locals as you advance toward the explosive confrontation with the Magic Emperor himself! Exciting, menu-driven combat will keep you challenged until the last. And thanks to the storage power of the CD, Lunar contains awesome animation sequences that'll get you involved in the story -- fast! Get ready for the ride of your life...</desc>
		<releasedate>19931201T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Working Designs</developer>
		<publisher>Working Designs</publisher>
		<genre>Role playing games</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Popful Mail (USA) (RE).chd</path>
		<name>Popful Mail</name>
		<desc>In this platform action game, you play as a cute bounty hunter known as Popful Mail. While you might think that a cute Anime chick would have no trouble making a living slashing bad guys with her sword, Popful is having a hard time making ends meet.  One day, however, Popful learns about a magician who has gone rogue and has a hefty bounty on his head. So, her adventure begins as Popful fights her way through a new adventure, and makes new friends along the way.

Primarily this is an action game with very slight RPG elements. As you make your way through the plethora of levels, you will have to collect money from slain foes. You use this money in the shops to buy weapons, armor, health, and so on. Also, this game features interaction with many, many characters through both on-screen dialog and fully animated sequences. Some of these characters become playable as you progress through the game.

This release has the same story and general gameplay style as the  earlier version, but otherwise was made from scratch, having entirely different graphics, locations, enemies, challenges, etc.</desc>
		<releasedate>19950223T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Working Designs</developer>
		<publisher>SEGA</publisher>
		<genre>Role playing games</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Robo Aleste (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Robo Aleste</name>
		<desc>Overhead Shooter based in Japan. The bloodthirsty Chugoko Warlords of the west have ruled and ravaged the once-supreme Oda Clan. Time to get your revenge. This is an overhead shooter with large bosses and massive power-ups.</desc>
		<releasedate>19930101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Compile</developer>
		<publisher>SEGA</publisher>
		<genre>Shoot'em Up</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Snatcher (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Snatcher</name>
		<desc>A.D. 2047. Neo Kobe City, Japan, a place of madness and decadence... A mysterious Bio-roid life form has appeared. Its true nature and purpose are unknown. Is it some country's secret weapon, or an alien from another world? They slay their victims and take their place, earning them the nickname "SNATCHERS." A new police division - J.U.N.K.E.R.s - has been formed. They are trained specifically to combat the SNATCHERS. The fate of mankind hangs in the balance. The war between the SNATCHERS and J.U.N.K.E.R.s has begun!</desc>
		<releasedate>19941130T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Konami</developer>
		<publisher>Konami</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Sonic The Hedgehog CD (Japan).chd</path>
		<name>Sonic the Hedgehog CD</name>
		<desc>This is a standard Sonic the Hedgehog side-scrolling action game. Dr. Robotnik has taken over the Little Planet, captured Amy, and created Metal Sonic with the goal of collecting all the Time Stones to be able to manipulate time and conquer the world.  It is up to Sonic to stop him, by rushing through levels set in different time periods, collecting Time Stones.

Sonic CD has features that take advantage of the CD format such as CD audio, video clips, and more levels (over 50 in total).</desc>
		<releasedate>19931119T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Sonic Team</developer>
		<publisher>SEGA</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
</gameList>
