<?xml version="1.0"?>
<gameList>
	<game>
		<path>./Actraiser (Japan).zip</path>
		<name>Actraiser</name>
		<desc>ActRaiser (BS) is byte-for-byte (sans header) identical to the Japanese retail version (Although it seems it's saving system is not as functional on a real hardware setup.  The player plays as "The Master," the main protagonist of the game. Although the Master is never directly controlled, the player interacts with the world by controlling an angel and an animated statue. The player plays as an angel during the simulation sequences of the game, and as the statue during the action sequences.

The overhead-view simulation mode involves protecting and guiding the Master's new civilization towards prosperity, beginning with two humans. This portion of the game requires the player to take actions that encourage the growth of the population, including road planning and using lightning, rain, sunlight, wind, and earthquakes as miracles. The Angel can interact with the monsters in the area by shooting them with arrows as well as aid the Master by indicating where to build and use miracles.

Each area has two side-scrolling action sequences, one before the building simulation and near the end. In the action sequences, the player controls a human-shaped statue brought to life by the Master. The player must jump from platform to platform while defeating monsters to accrue a score. At the end of each action sequence, the player must defeat a boss. 

Among many things, the game is recognized for its score, which was composed by Yuzo Koshiro. Its release within six months of the launch of the console demonstrated the compositional potential it represented to future projects, underscoring its ability to use and manipulate comparatively high quality samples.</desc>
		<releasedate>19911101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Quintet</developer>
		<publisher>Enix</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Albert Odyssey (Japan).zip</path>
		<name>Albert Odyssey</name>
		<desc>Albert Odyssey is a tactical role-playing video game developed and published by Sunsoft and originally released in Japan in March 1993. The game features strategy-based combat in addition to traditional role-playing game elements in two-dimensional environments. The game was later re-released for Satellaview in March 1998. Players assume the role of Albert, the young heroic swordsman who lives in a fantasy world filled with monsters and mythical creatures. While much of the world remains in relative peace following a great war many years before, a military faction led by the dark magician Globus has emerged to conquer the newly pacified nations and expand their empire. With the help of Albert's friends as well as hired mercenaries, the player must travel the world and eventually confront Golbus and his forces to prevent another large-scale conflict.</desc>
		<releasedate>19980329T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Sunsoft</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Role playing games</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Arkanoid - Doh It Again (Japan).zip</path>
		<name>Arkanoid - Doh It Again</name>
		<desc>Arkanoid: Doh It Again was broadcast between August 21, 1997 and March 31, 1998. The player controls a ship using either a standard controller or the Super NES Mouse. Rounds are completed when all the color and silver blocks on the screen have been eliminated. Enemies enter from the doors at the top of the play area. Every eleven rounds a boss enemy will have to be fought. Some of the blocks contain power-ups that you must catch with your paddle to use. The game has a total of 99 levels, an edit mode in which users can create their own levels, power-ups, and two-player capabilities.</desc>
		<releasedate>19970821T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Taito</developer>
		<publisher>Taito</publisher>
		<genre>Action / Breakout games</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Bokujou Monogatari - Dai-2-wa (Japan) (SoundLink).zip</path>
		<name>Bokujou Monogatari</name>
		<desc>BS Bokujou Monogatari is a Downloadable 4-part Soundlink game for the Satellaview that was broadcast in at least 2 runs between September 2, 1996 and November 30, 1996. The game is a life-simulation game and it comes as a pseudo-sequel to the earlier-broadcast (July 1996)/retail release Bokujou Monogatari commonly known internationally as "Harvest Moon"; this has given the series the fan-nickname "BS Harvest Moon" as a result. Together with the game (typically immediately before and after), 10-minute broadcasts of a related nature were released entitled BS Bokujou Monogatari Torisetsu (a digital instruction manual) and Bokujou Monogatari no Kekka (a score/results program).</desc>
		<releasedate>19960902T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>St.GIGA</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Simulation</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Bokujou Monogatari - Dai-4-wa (Japan) (SoundLink).zip</path>
		<name>Bokujou Monogatari</name>
		<desc>BS Bokujou Monogatari is a Downloadable 4-part Soundlink game for the Satellaview that was broadcast in at least 2 runs between September 2, 1996 and November 30, 1996. The game is a life-simulation game and it comes as a pseudo-sequel to the earlier-broadcast (July 1996)/retail release Bokujou Monogatari commonly known internationally as "Harvest Moon"; this has given the series the fan-nickname "BS Harvest Moon" as a result. Together with the game (typically immediately before and after), 10-minute broadcasts of a related nature were released entitled BS Bokujou Monogatari Torisetsu (a digital instruction manual) and Bokujou Monogatari no Kekka (a score/results program).</desc>
		<releasedate>19960902T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>St.GIGA</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Simulation</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./BS Dragon Quest I (Japan) (SoundLink).zip</path>
		<name>BS Dragon Quest</name>
		<desc>BS Dragon Quest is essentially the same as Dragon Quest I from the Dragon Quest I+II Reprise with several Satellaview specific peculiarities. For instance, quests are time-limited, unlike the original. The quests mostly originate from of Dragon Quest I, with a few originals. Fans of the Dragon Quest/Dragon Warrior series will certainly appreciate experiencing the variation on the original, although it's generally considered inferior to the Reprise. The game consisted of four one-hour scenarios which players would download on a weekly schedule. Players are tasked with leveling their character, collecting medals and completing scenario-specific conditions with special events designed to occur under specific conditions in real-time.</desc>
		<releasedate>19960204T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Chunsoft</developer>
		<publisher>Enix</publisher>
		<genre>Role playing games</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./BS F-Zero Grand Prix - Dai-1-shuu - Knight League (Japan) (11-3) (SoundLink).zip</path>
		<name>Bs F-zero Grand Prix</name>
		<desc>BS F-Zero Grand Prix was a four-part Soundlink game to the original F-Zero. It was launched only in Japan for the Satellaview attachment for the Super Famicom. BS F-Zero Grand Prix contained four different playable vehicles and four new tracks near the end of each broadcast, as well as the 15 tracks from the original game. Commentary was provided by Bucky Koba, Tsutomu Tareki, and Seiichi Hirai. A follow-up to the game was later distributed as BS F-Zero Grand Prix 2.</desc>
		<releasedate>19961229T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Race, Driving</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./BS F-Zero Grand Prix - Dai-2-shuu - Queen League (Japan) (SoundLink).zip</path>
		<name>Bs F-zero Grand Prix</name>
		<desc>BS F-Zero Grand Prix was a four-part Soundlink game to the original F-Zero. It was launched only in Japan for the Satellaview attachment for the Super Famicom. BS F-Zero Grand Prix contained four different playable vehicles and four new tracks near the end of each broadcast, as well as the 15 tracks from the original game. Commentary was provided by Bucky Koba, Tsutomu Tareki, and Seiichi Hirai. A follow-up to the game was later distributed as BS F-Zero Grand Prix 2.</desc>
		<releasedate>19961229T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Race, Driving</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./BS F-Zero Grand Prix - Dai-3-shuu - King League (Japan) (SoundLink).zip</path>
		<name>Bs F-zero Grand Prix</name>
		<desc>BS F-Zero Grand Prix was a four-part Soundlink game to the original F-Zero. It was launched only in Japan for the Satellaview attachment for the Super Famicom. BS F-Zero Grand Prix contained four different playable vehicles and four new tracks near the end of each broadcast, as well as the 15 tracks from the original game. Commentary was provided by Bucky Koba, Tsutomu Tareki, and Seiichi Hirai. A follow-up to the game was later distributed as BS F-Zero Grand Prix 2.</desc>
		<releasedate>19961229T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Race, Driving</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./BS F-Zero Grand Prix - Dai-4-shuu - Ace League (Japan) (SoundLink).zip</path>
		<name>Bs F-zero Grand Prix</name>
		<desc>BS F-Zero Grand Prix was a four-part Soundlink game to the original F-Zero. It was launched only in Japan for the Satellaview attachment for the Super Famicom. BS F-Zero Grand Prix contained four different playable vehicles and four new tracks near the end of each broadcast, as well as the 15 tracks from the original game. Commentary was provided by Bucky Koba, Tsutomu Tareki, and Seiichi Hirai. A follow-up to the game was later distributed as BS F-Zero Grand Prix 2.</desc>
		<releasedate>19961229T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Race, Driving</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./BS F-Zero Grand Prix 2 - Practice (Japan) (12-6).zip</path>
		<name>BS F-Zero Grand Prix 2</name>
		<desc>BS F-Zero Grand Prix 2 is the direct sequel to the original F-Zero game released for the Super Famicom via the Satellaview. Two versions were released - a non-SoundLink game and a SoundLink game. The original non-SoundLink version was released as BSF-Zero 2 Practice on June 1, 1997 (although the title screen remained the same). It contained the four courses first seen throughout BS F-Zero Grand Prix (a Satellaview remake of the original), along with a new course called Mute City IV. Little is known about the later SoundLink version outside of surviving videos, but it was distributed in two halves in August 1997 and had a similar announcer and redone soundtrack as the previous Satellaview entry. At least the first week rearranged a few courses, and replaced two with new locations called "Forest I" and "Forest II". Presuming no areas were repeated, this likely means the SoundLink version had twice as many courses total. In addition, it can be seen that the player cannot choose between Grand Prix and Practice modes in the SoundLink version; as it was a live broadcast, the player is forced to play each course in a timed Practice mode, and then the Grand Prix race.</desc>
		<releasedate>19970601T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>St.GIGA</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Race, Driving</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./BS Fire Emblem - Akaneia Senki Hen - Dai-1-wa - Palace Kanraku (Japan) (9-29) (SoundLink) [T-En by Darrman v1.01] [req BS-X bios].zip</path>
		<name>Bs Fire Emblem - Akaneia Senki</name>
		<desc>BS Fire Emblem: Akaneia Senki is a Downloadable 4-part Soundlink game for the Satellaview that was broadcast in at least 3 distinct runs between September 28, 1997 and May 1, 1999. BS Fire Emblem's four chapters were each set in the same universe as Fire Emblem: Ankoku Ryu to Hikari no Tsurugi and Monshou no Nazo. Each segment was set prior to the events of Chapter 1 of both games.</desc>
		<releasedate>19970928T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Intelligent Systems</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Role playing games</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./BS Fire Emblem - Akaneia Senki Hen - Dai-2-wa - Akai Ryuu Kishi (Japan) (SoundLink) [T-En by Darrman v1.01] [req BS-X bios].zip</path>
		<name>Bs Fire Emblem - Akaneia Senki</name>
		<desc>BS Fire Emblem: Akaneia Senki is a Downloadable 4-part Soundlink game for the Satellaview that was broadcast in at least 3 distinct runs between September 28, 1997 and May 1, 1999. BS Fire Emblem's four chapters were each set in the same universe as Fire Emblem: Ankoku Ryu to Hikari no Tsurugi and Monshou no Nazo. Each segment was set prior to the events of Chapter 1 of both games.</desc>
		<releasedate>19970928T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Intelligent Systems</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Role playing games</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./BS Fire Emblem - Akaneia Senki Hen - Dai-3-wa - Seigi no Touzokudan (Japan) (SoundLink) [T-En by Darrman v1.01] [req BS-X bios].zip</path>
		<name>Bs Fire Emblem - Akaneia Senki</name>
		<desc>BS Fire Emblem: Akaneia Senki is a Downloadable 4-part Soundlink game for the Satellaview that was broadcast in at least 3 distinct runs between September 28, 1997 and May 1, 1999. BS Fire Emblem's four chapters were each set in the same universe as Fire Emblem: Ankoku Ryu to Hikari no Tsurugi and Monshou no Nazo. Each segment was set prior to the events of Chapter 1 of both games.</desc>
		<releasedate>19970928T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Intelligent Systems</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Role playing games</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./BS Fire Emblem - Akaneia Senki Hen - Dai-4-wa - Hajimari no Toki (Japan) (4-28) (SoundLink) [T-En by Darrman v1.01] [req BS-X bios].zip</path>
		<name>Bs Fire Emblem - Akaneia Senki</name>
		<desc>BS Fire Emblem: Akaneia Senki is a Downloadable 4-part Soundlink game for the Satellaview that was broadcast in at least 3 distinct runs between September 28, 1997 and May 1, 1999. BS Fire Emblem's four chapters were each set in the same universe as Fire Emblem: Ankoku Ryu to Hikari no Tsurugi and Monshou no Nazo. Each segment was set prior to the events of Chapter 1 of both games.</desc>
		<releasedate>19970928T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Intelligent Systems</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Role playing games</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./BS Fuurai no Shiren - Surara o Sukue - Dai-2-shuu (Japan) (SoundLink).zip</path>
		<name>Bs Fuurai No Shiren - Surara Wo Sukue</name>
		<desc>BS Furai no Shiren: Surara wo Sukue is a Downloadable 4-part Soundlink game for the Satellaview that was broadcast in at least 3 runs between April 28, 1996 and August 2, 1997. The gameplay is substantially similar to the earlier roguelike, Fushigi no Dungeon 2: Furai no Shiren, a game released for the SFC on December 1, 1995 and subsequently localized for English markets in March 2008 as Mystery Dungeon: Shiren the Wanderer for the Nintendo DS. It also bears similarities to other Mystery Dungeon games including Dragon Quest Yangus, The Nightmare of Druaga, and Pokemon Mystery Dungeon. Like other Mystery Dungeon games, it is set in a fantasy land based on feudal Japan, and it falls into the roguelike genre. The titular hero of the game, Shiren the Wanderer, moves in a turn-based fashion through a series of maps filled with monsters, traps, and items. The maps, referred to as dungeons, take a variety of forms including traditional dungeons, caves, forests, etc. When a player is slain, he begins at the start again with stats at the base level, however he can regain items that had previously been stored a warehouse.</desc>
		<releasedate>19960428T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Enix</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Action / Adventure</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./BS Fuurai no Shiren - Surara o Sukue - Dai-4-shuu (Japan) (SoundLink).zip</path>
		<name>Bs Fuurai No Shiren - Surara Wo Sukue</name>
		<desc>BS Furai no Shiren: Surara wo Sukue is a Downloadable 4-part Soundlink game for the Satellaview that was broadcast in at least 3 runs between April 28, 1996 and August 2, 1997. The gameplay is substantially similar to the earlier roguelike, Fushigi no Dungeon 2: Furai no Shiren, a game released for the SFC on December 1, 1995 and subsequently localized for English markets in March 2008 as Mystery Dungeon: Shiren the Wanderer for the Nintendo DS. It also bears similarities to other Mystery Dungeon games including Dragon Quest Yangus, The Nightmare of Druaga, and Pokemon Mystery Dungeon. Like other Mystery Dungeon games, it is set in a fantasy land based on feudal Japan, and it falls into the roguelike genre. The titular hero of the game, Shiren the Wanderer, moves in a turn-based fashion through a series of maps filled with monsters, traps, and items. The maps, referred to as dungeons, take a variety of forms including traditional dungeons, caves, forests, etc. When a player is slain, he begins at the start again with stats at the base level, however he can regain items that had previously been stored a warehouse.</desc>
		<releasedate>19960428T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Enix</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Action / Adventure</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./BS Ihatovo Monogatari - Dai-2-wa (Japan) (SoundLink).zip</path>
		<name>Ihatovo Monogatari</name>
		<desc>A Satellaview port of the Super Famicom game Ihatovo Monogatari, not to be confused with its sequel BS Ihatovo Monogatari which was broadcast on the Satellaview earlier. 
Ihatovo is a magical land created by the Japanese author Kenji Miyazawa. In the game, you are a stranger who arrives at Ihatovo and has to find seven missing notebooks by Miyazawa, to complete his stories, such as for example The Fire Stone, and others.
This is an adventure game in which you can freely navigate your character through the top-down world, in a console RPG-like fashion. There are no battles in the game and also no puzzles, although at some points you'll have to collect and to use items. The game mainly progresses thanks to conversations with various characters you encounter in Ihatovo.</desc>
		<developer>HectorSoft</developer>
		<publisher>HectorSoft</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./BS Marvelous - Camp Arnold Course - Dai-1-shuu (Japan) (SoundLink) [b].zip</path>
		<name>Bs Marvelous - Camp Arnold Course</name>
		<desc>BS Marvelous: Camp Arnold is a Downloadable 4-part Soundlink game for the Satellaview that ran between November 3, 1996 and November 29, 1996. The game was broadcast as a rerun in January, 1997. It serves as a sequel to the earlier-broadcast BS Marvelous: Time Athletics and a direct prequel to Marvelous: Mouhitotsu no Takara-jima. Aside from the other games in the Marvelous series, the gameplay of BS Marvelous: Camp Arnold is most comparable to that of Zelda no Densetsu: Kamigami no Triforce. Indeed, the game's engine and gameplay elements were taken directly from Kamigami no Triforce. Unlike Kamigami no Triforce, however, the themes embodied in BS Marvelous: Camp Arnold are much more down-to-earth. The game plays like a Boy Scouts-esque survival game with environmental interactions. From an overhead perspective, the player controls characters as they walk across the land. Whenever the player encounters an important object or NPC, a command window pops open to allow the player to select between several options relating to the object or NPC. These include such things as picking up objects, talking to NPCs, or reading signs, etc.</desc>
		<releasedate>19961103T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Role playing games</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./BS Marvelous - Camp Arnold Course - Dai-2-shuu (Japan) (SoundLink) [b].zip</path>
		<name>Bs Marvelous - Camp Arnold Course</name>
		<desc>BS Marvelous: Camp Arnold is a Downloadable 4-part Soundlink game for the Satellaview that ran between November 3, 1996 and November 29, 1996. The game was broadcast as a rerun in January, 1997. It serves as a sequel to the earlier-broadcast BS Marvelous: Time Athletics and a direct prequel to Marvelous: Mouhitotsu no Takara-jima. Aside from the other games in the Marvelous series, the gameplay of BS Marvelous: Camp Arnold is most comparable to that of Zelda no Densetsu: Kamigami no Triforce. Indeed, the game's engine and gameplay elements were taken directly from Kamigami no Triforce. Unlike Kamigami no Triforce, however, the themes embodied in BS Marvelous: Camp Arnold are much more down-to-earth. The game plays like a Boy Scouts-esque survival game with environmental interactions. From an overhead perspective, the player controls characters as they walk across the land. Whenever the player encounters an important object or NPC, a command window pops open to allow the player to select between several options relating to the object or NPC. These include such things as picking up objects, talking to NPCs, or reading signs, etc.</desc>
		<releasedate>19961103T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Role playing games</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./BS Marvelous - Camp Arnold Course - Dai-3-shuu (Japan) (SoundLink) [b].zip</path>
		<name>Bs Marvelous - Camp Arnold Course</name>
		<desc>BS Marvelous: Camp Arnold is a Downloadable 4-part Soundlink game for the Satellaview that ran between November 3, 1996 and November 29, 1996. The game was broadcast as a rerun in January, 1997. It serves as a sequel to the earlier-broadcast BS Marvelous: Time Athletics and a direct prequel to Marvelous: Mouhitotsu no Takara-jima. Aside from the other games in the Marvelous series, the gameplay of BS Marvelous: Camp Arnold is most comparable to that of Zelda no Densetsu: Kamigami no Triforce. Indeed, the game's engine and gameplay elements were taken directly from Kamigami no Triforce. Unlike Kamigami no Triforce, however, the themes embodied in BS Marvelous: Camp Arnold are much more down-to-earth. The game plays like a Boy Scouts-esque survival game with environmental interactions. From an overhead perspective, the player controls characters as they walk across the land. Whenever the player encounters an important object or NPC, a command window pops open to allow the player to select between several options relating to the object or NPC. These include such things as picking up objects, talking to NPCs, or reading signs, etc.</desc>
		<releasedate>19961103T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Role playing games</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./BS Marvelous - Camp Arnold Course - Dai-4-shuu (Japan) (SoundLink) [b].zip</path>
		<name>Bs Marvelous - Camp Arnold Course</name>
		<desc>BS Marvelous: Camp Arnold is a Downloadable 4-part Soundlink game for the Satellaview that ran between November 3, 1996 and November 29, 1996. The game was broadcast as a rerun in January, 1997. It serves as a sequel to the earlier-broadcast BS Marvelous: Time Athletics and a direct prequel to Marvelous: Mouhitotsu no Takara-jima. Aside from the other games in the Marvelous series, the gameplay of BS Marvelous: Camp Arnold is most comparable to that of Zelda no Densetsu: Kamigami no Triforce. Indeed, the game's engine and gameplay elements were taken directly from Kamigami no Triforce. Unlike Kamigami no Triforce, however, the themes embodied in BS Marvelous: Camp Arnold are much more down-to-earth. The game plays like a Boy Scouts-esque survival game with environmental interactions. From an overhead perspective, the player controls characters as they walk across the land. Whenever the player encounters an important object or NPC, a command window pops open to allow the player to select between several options relating to the object or NPC. These include such things as picking up objects, talking to NPCs, or reading signs, etc.</desc>
		<releasedate>19961103T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Role playing games</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./BS Marvelous - Time Athletic Course - Dai-1-shuu (Japan) (SoundLink) [b].zip</path>
		<name>Bs Marvelous - Time Athletic Course</name>
		<desc>BS Marvelous: Time Athletics is a Downloadable 4-part Soundlink game for the Satellaview that ran between January 1, 1996 and January 31, 1996. The game was broadcast in as a rerun in April, 1996. A sequel to BS Marvelous: Time Athletics entitled BS Marvelous: Camp Arnold was released in November, 1996 as a direct prequel to Marvelous: Mohitotsu no Takarajima which was not broadcast via Satellaview but instead released in hard copy as a SFC cartridge. From an overhead perspective, the player controls characters as they walk across the land. Whenever the player encounters an important object or NPC, a command window pops open to allow the player to select between several options relating to the object or NPC. These include such things as picking up objects, talking to NPCs, or reading signs, etc.</desc>
		<releasedate>19960107T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Role playing games</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./BS Marvelous - Time Athletic Course - Dai-2-shuu (Japan) (SoundLink) [b].zip</path>
		<name>Bs Marvelous - Time Athletic Course</name>
		<desc>BS Marvelous: Time Athletics is a Downloadable 4-part Soundlink game for the Satellaview that ran between January 1, 1996 and January 31, 1996. The game was broadcast in as a rerun in April, 1996. A sequel to BS Marvelous: Time Athletics entitled BS Marvelous: Camp Arnold was released in November, 1996 as a direct prequel to Marvelous: Mohitotsu no Takarajima which was not broadcast via Satellaview but instead released in hard copy as a SFC cartridge. From an overhead perspective, the player controls characters as they walk across the land. Whenever the player encounters an important object or NPC, a command window pops open to allow the player to select between several options relating to the object or NPC. These include such things as picking up objects, talking to NPCs, or reading signs, etc.</desc>
		<releasedate>19960107T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Role playing games</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./BS Marvelous - Time Athletic Course - Dai-3-shuu (Japan) (SoundLink) [b].zip</path>
		<name>Bs Marvelous - Time Athletic Course</name>
		<desc>BS Marvelous: Time Athletics is a Downloadable 4-part Soundlink game for the Satellaview that ran between January 1, 1996 and January 31, 1996. The game was broadcast in as a rerun in April, 1996. A sequel to BS Marvelous: Time Athletics entitled BS Marvelous: Camp Arnold was released in November, 1996 as a direct prequel to Marvelous: Mohitotsu no Takarajima which was not broadcast via Satellaview but instead released in hard copy as a SFC cartridge. From an overhead perspective, the player controls characters as they walk across the land. Whenever the player encounters an important object or NPC, a command window pops open to allow the player to select between several options relating to the object or NPC. These include such things as picking up objects, talking to NPCs, or reading signs, etc.</desc>
		<releasedate>19960107T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Role playing games</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./BS Marvelous - Time Athletic Course - Dai-4-shuu (Japan) (SoundLink) [b].zip</path>
		<name>Bs Marvelous - Time Athletic Course</name>
		<desc>BS Marvelous: Time Athletics is a Downloadable 4-part Soundlink game for the Satellaview that ran between January 1, 1996 and January 31, 1996. The game was broadcast in as a rerun in April, 1996. A sequel to BS Marvelous: Time Athletics entitled BS Marvelous: Camp Arnold was released in November, 1996 as a direct prequel to Marvelous: Mohitotsu no Takarajima which was not broadcast via Satellaview but instead released in hard copy as a SFC cartridge. From an overhead perspective, the player controls characters as they walk across the land. Whenever the player encounters an important object or NPC, a command window pops open to allow the player to select between several options relating to the object or NPC. These include such things as picking up objects, talking to NPCs, or reading signs, etc.</desc>
		<releasedate>19960107T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Role playing games</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./BS Nichibutsu Mahjong - Mahjong Taikai (Japan) (10-27).zip</path>
		<name>Bs Nichibutsu Mahjong</name>
		<desc>BS Nichibutsu Mahjong is a Downloadable 2-part Soundlink game for the Satellaview that was broadcast between January 26, 1997 and April 12, 1997.</desc>
		<releasedate>19970126T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>St.GIGA</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Mahjong</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./BS Nichibutsu Mahjong - Renshuu Mahjong - Ichimantou (Japan) (SoundLink).zip</path>
		<name>Bs Nichibutsu Mahjong</name>
		<desc>BS Nichibutsu Mahjong is a Downloadable 2-part Soundlink game for the Satellaview that was broadcast between January 26, 1997 and April 12, 1997.</desc>
		<releasedate>19970126T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>St.GIGA</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Mahjong</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./BS Nichibutsu Mahjong - Renshuu Mahjong - Nimantou (Japan) (SoundLink).zip</path>
		<name>Bs Nichibutsu Mahjong</name>
		<desc>BS Nichibutsu Mahjong is a Downloadable 2-part Soundlink game for the Satellaview that was broadcast between January 26, 1997 and April 12, 1997.</desc>
		<releasedate>19970126T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>St.GIGA</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Mahjong</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./BS Parlor! Parlor! - Dai-2-shuu (Japan) (5-13) (SoundLink).zip</path>
		<name>Bs Parlor! Parlor!</name>
		<desc>BS Parlor! Parlor! is a Downloadable 2-part Soundlink game for the Satellaview that was broadcast between March 1, 1998 and March 14, 1998. At various times throughout 1995, the game was accompanied by full-day broadcasts of a strategy magazine entitled BS Parlor! Parlor! Kouryaku Magazine.</desc>
		<releasedate>19980301T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Telenet</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Casino</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./BS Sim City - Scenario 3 (Japan) (SoundLink).zip</path>
		<name>BS Sim City: Machi Tsukuri Taikai</name>
		<desc>This is a modified version of SimCity, with the scenario decided by the episode rather than chosen by the player. The game was voiced over by Eisduke Yoda, Madame Marie, Yoshio Kanetake, Masaaki Sekine, and Tsutomu Tareki.

The gameplay is restricted by about 50 minutes real time, and it is impossible to slow down or speed up time. Also added are three advisers who run a loan feature exclusive to this version.</desc>
		<releasedate>19960804T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>St.GIGA</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./BS Super Mario Collection - Dai-3-shuu (Japan) (3-17) (SoundLink).zip</path>
		<name>Bs Super Mario Collection</name>
		<desc>BS Super Mario Collection is a remix of Super Mario Collection (the Japanese name for Super Mario All-Stars) for the Satellaview, an add-on for the Super Famicom. The game was released in four installments. As the game played, streamed audio would enhance the gameplay experience with special music and voice acting featuring Japanese celebrities. Its "companion title" is BS Super Mario USA. A Fire Flower icon represents Nae's house, which is hosted by a Satellaview Radio Personality Nae Yūki. Here, Mario can choose to activate ghost mode which allows him to become Fire Mario once he exits the level if he is Small or Super Mario. This in turn disables players from participating in rankings. A Treasure Ship icon, which is unlocked when Mario finishes all available levels in the World. Toad's House is now just a screen where the player selects the treasure chest, rather than having Mario actually walk to the chest and open it. There is a timer in the bottom left of the screen that counts down to the end of a World cycle. At the beginning of each world, there is a list of all the levels, and a picture with dialog underneath it.</desc>
		<releasedate>19971228T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo EAD</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./BS Super Mario USA - Power Challenge - Dai-1-kai (Japan) (SoundLink).zip</path>
		<name>Bs Super Mario Usa Power Challenge</name>
		<desc>BS Super Mario USA Power Challenge is an ura- or gaiden-version of Super Mario Bros. 2 for the Satellaview system featuring graphical enhancements similar to its Super Mario All-Stars version. While the underlying gameplay itself is largely similar, some content has been rearranged and new content has been added. The game was released in four installments, in each of which the player is sent to a different SMB2 "World" to collect the Gold Mario Statues located in each level, defeat the boss, and then find and beat Wart, who can be battled in any world when going down in any vase while the player is in Subspace. The player can select the levels in any order and return to the levels as often as desired until the "episode" ends at around 50 minutes on the clock. The player starts the game as Mario, and character changing is forced in timed events. A points system was added. Points can be gained, among other things, by defeating enemies in various ways.</desc>
		<releasedate>19960101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo EAD</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./BS Super Mario USA - Power Challenge - Dai-2-kai (Japan) (SoundLink).zip</path>
		<name>Bs Super Mario Usa Power Challenge</name>
		<desc>BS Super Mario USA Power Challenge is an ura- or gaiden-version of Super Mario Bros. 2 for the Satellaview system featuring graphical enhancements similar to its Super Mario All-Stars version. While the underlying gameplay itself is largely similar, some content has been rearranged and new content has been added. The game was released in four installments, in each of which the player is sent to a different SMB2 "World" to collect the Gold Mario Statues located in each level, defeat the boss, and then find and beat Wart, who can be battled in any world when going down in any vase while the player is in Subspace. The player can select the levels in any order and return to the levels as often as desired until the "episode" ends at around 50 minutes on the clock. The player starts the game as Mario, and character changing is forced in timed events. A points system was added. Points can be gained, among other things, by defeating enemies in various ways.</desc>
		<releasedate>19960101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo EAD</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./BS Super Mario USA - Power Challenge - Dai-3-kai (Japan) (SoundLink).zip</path>
		<name>Bs Super Mario Usa Power Challenge</name>
		<desc>BS Super Mario USA Power Challenge is an ura- or gaiden-version of Super Mario Bros. 2 for the Satellaview system featuring graphical enhancements similar to its Super Mario All-Stars version. While the underlying gameplay itself is largely similar, some content has been rearranged and new content has been added. The game was released in four installments, in each of which the player is sent to a different SMB2 "World" to collect the Gold Mario Statues located in each level, defeat the boss, and then find and beat Wart, who can be battled in any world when going down in any vase while the player is in Subspace. The player can select the levels in any order and return to the levels as often as desired until the "episode" ends at around 50 minutes on the clock. The player starts the game as Mario, and character changing is forced in timed events. A points system was added. Points can be gained, among other things, by defeating enemies in various ways.</desc>
		<releasedate>19960101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo EAD</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./BS Super Mario USA - Power Challenge - Dai-4-kai (Japan) (SoundLink).zip</path>
		<name>Bs Super Mario Usa Power Challenge</name>
		<desc>BS Super Mario USA Power Challenge is an ura- or gaiden-version of Super Mario Bros. 2 for the Satellaview system featuring graphical enhancements similar to its Super Mario All-Stars version. While the underlying gameplay itself is largely similar, some content has been rearranged and new content has been added. The game was released in four installments, in each of which the player is sent to a different SMB2 "World" to collect the Gold Mario Statues located in each level, defeat the boss, and then find and beat Wart, who can be battled in any world when going down in any vase while the player is in Subspace. The player can select the levels in any order and return to the levels as often as desired until the "episode" ends at around 50 minutes on the clock. The player starts the game as Mario, and character changing is forced in timed events. A points system was added. Points can be gained, among other things, by defeating enemies in various ways.</desc>
		<releasedate>19960101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo EAD</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./BS Tantei Club - Yuki ni Kieta Kako - Chuuhen (Japan) (6-20) (SoundLink).zip</path>
		<name>Bs Tantei Club - Yuki Ni Kieta Kako</name>
		<desc>BS Tantei Club: Yuki ni Kieta Kako (also known by the shorthand BS Tan or even B Tan) is a Downloadable 3-part Soundlink game for the Satellaview that was broadcast in at least 2 distinct runs between February 9, 1997 and May 3, 1997. It is a pseudo-sequel to Tantei Club: Kieta Kokeisha and is followed by Tantei Club Part II: Ushiro ni Tatsu Shojo. BS Tantei Club is a detective story. The game is a text-based point-and-click-style adventure game where still images are presented to the player and the player may guide a hand-shaped icon around the screen to select objects in the image to investigate further. A number of icons in a side-bar present the player with options such as taking notes, speaking, or placing telephone calls. Similar gameplay was used in other games from the FDS era including the popular Shadowgate (1989).</desc>
		<releasedate>19970209T000000</releasedate>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure / Point and Click</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./BS Tantei Club - Yuki ni Kieta Kako - Kouhen (Japan) (SoundLink).zip</path>
		<name>Bs Tantei Club - Yuki Ni Kieta Kako</name>
		<desc>BS Tantei Club: Yuki ni Kieta Kako (also known by the shorthand BS Tan or even B Tan) is a Downloadable 3-part Soundlink game for the Satellaview that was broadcast in at least 2 distinct runs between February 9, 1997 and May 3, 1997. It is a pseudo-sequel to Tantei Club: Kieta Kokeisha and is followed by Tantei Club Part II: Ushiro ni Tatsu Shojo. BS Tantei Club is a detective story. The game is a text-based point-and-click-style adventure game where still images are presented to the player and the player may guide a hand-shaped icon around the screen to select objects in the image to investigate further. A number of icons in a side-bar present the player with options such as taking notes, speaking, or placing telephone calls. Similar gameplay was used in other games from the FDS era including the popular Shadowgate (1989).</desc>
		<releasedate>19970209T000000</releasedate>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure / Point and Click</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./BS Tantei Club - Yuki ni Kieta Kako - Zenpen (Japan) (SoundLink).zip</path>
		<name>Bs Tantei Club - Yuki Ni Kieta Kako</name>
		<desc>BS Tantei Club: Yuki ni Kieta Kako (also known by the shorthand BS Tan or even B Tan) is a Downloadable 3-part Soundlink game for the Satellaview that was broadcast in at least 2 distinct runs between February 9, 1997 and May 3, 1997. It is a pseudo-sequel to Tantei Club: Kieta Kokeisha and is followed by Tantei Club Part II: Ushiro ni Tatsu Shojo. BS Tantei Club is a detective story. The game is a text-based point-and-click-style adventure game where still images are presented to the player and the player may guide a hand-shaped icon around the screen to select objects in the image to investigate further. A number of icons in a side-bar present the player with options such as taking notes, speaking, or placing telephone calls. Similar gameplay was used in other games from the FDS era including the popular Shadowgate (1989).</desc>
		<releasedate>19970209T000000</releasedate>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure / Point and Click</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./BS Zelda no Densetsu - Dai-2-wa (Japan) (SoundLink).zip</path>
		<name>Bs Zelda No Densetsu - Map 2 - Dai-1-wa</name>
		<desc>BS The Legend of Zelda ( BS Zeruda no Densetsu) was a remake of the NES game The Legend of Zelda, released for the Satellaview attachment for the Super Famicom in Japan.
The gameplay was identical to its predecessor, but the maximum Rupees was increased to allow you more than a thousand (rather than 255 as in The Legend of Zelda), the overworld was heavily altered, and dungeons were completely different. This game was broadcasted in two versions, Map 1 and Map 2. Map 1 is sometimes referred to as a "Third Quest", in reference to The Legend of Zelda's Second Quest, and Map 2 would therefore be a Fourth Quest.
The game was divided into four weekly episodes, this is the first episode</desc>
		<releasedate>19950809T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>St.GIGA</publisher>
		<genre>Action / Adventure</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./BS Zelda no Densetsu - Dai-3-wa (Japan) (SoundLink).zip</path>
		<name>Bs Zelda No Densetsu</name>
		<desc>BS Zelda no Densetsu is a Downloadable 4-part Soundlink game for the Satellaview that was broadcast in at least 5 distinct runs between August 6, 1995 and January 4, 1997. A program called BS Zelda no Asobikata was also broadcast in the half-hour prior to broadcasts of BS Zelda. This program seems to have been a radio tutorial teaching players how to play BS Zelda. The gameplay draws directly from The Legend of Zelda. The plot of BS Zelda varies considerably from the plot of the original due in great part to the fact that the hero of the game is not Link (the hero of The Legend of Zelda). Instead, BS Zelda is closely associated with the story presented in the BS-X interface cartridge, with the Hero of Light actually representing the BS-X avatar according the the BS Zelda storyline. Another major factor in the plot of BS Zelda is the fact that the story is most closely related to the story given in The Legend of Zelda: A Link to the Past. Both plots take up after the conclusion of Kamigami no Triforce - a fact that for Inishie no Sekiban produces one of the many plot inconsistencies/contradictions for which the series has become noted.</desc>
		<releasedate>19950806T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Action / Adventure</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./BS Zelda no Densetsu - Inishie no Sekiban - Dai-1-wa (Japan) (SoundLink).zip</path>
		<name>Bs Zelda No Densetsu - Inishie No Sekiban</name>
		<desc>BS Zelda no Densetsu: Inishie no Sekiban is a Downloadable 4-part Soundlink game for the Satellaview that was broadcast in at least 4 distinct runs between March 30, 1997 and May 30, 1999. The game has in the past been commonly referred to as "BS Zelda no Densetsu: Kodai no Sekiban", however the current fan consensus is that the term, is more appropriately written as "Inishie no Sekiban" due to the in-game SoundLink pronunciation of the game's title as heard on period VHS recordings of live game-play.</desc>
		<releasedate>19970330T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>St.GIGA</publisher>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./BS Zelda no Densetsu - Inishie no Sekiban - Dai-2-wa (Japan) (SoundLink).zip</path>
		<name>Bs Zelda No Densetsu - Inishie No Sekiban</name>
		<desc>BS Zelda no Densetsu: Inishie no Sekiban is a Downloadable 4-part Soundlink game for the Satellaview that was broadcast in at least 4 distinct runs between March 30, 1997 and May 30, 1999. The game has in the past been commonly referred to as "BS Zelda no Densetsu: Kodai no Sekiban", however the current fan consensus is that the term, is more appropriately written as "Inishie no Sekiban" due to the in-game SoundLink pronunciation of the game's title as heard on period VHS recordings of live game-play.</desc>
		<releasedate>19970330T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>St.GIGA</publisher>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./BS Zelda no Densetsu - Inishie no Sekiban - Dai-3-wa (Japan) (SoundLink).zip</path>
		<name>Bs Zelda No Densetsu - Inishie No Sekiban</name>
		<desc>BS Zelda no Densetsu: Inishie no Sekiban is a Downloadable 4-part Soundlink game for the Satellaview that was broadcast in at least 4 distinct runs between March 30, 1997 and May 30, 1999. The game has in the past been commonly referred to as "BS Zelda no Densetsu: Kodai no Sekiban", however the current fan consensus is that the term, is more appropriately written as "Inishie no Sekiban" due to the in-game SoundLink pronunciation of the game's title as heard on period VHS recordings of live game-play.</desc>
		<releasedate>19970330T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>St.GIGA</publisher>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./BS Zelda no Densetsu - Inishie no Sekiban - Dai-4-wa (Japan) (SoundLink).zip</path>
		<name>Bs Zelda No Densetsu - Inishie No Sekiban</name>
		<desc>BS Zelda no Densetsu: Inishie no Sekiban is a Downloadable 4-part Soundlink game for the Satellaview that was broadcast in at least 4 distinct runs between March 30, 1997 and May 30, 1999. The game has in the past been commonly referred to as "BS Zelda no Densetsu: Kodai no Sekiban", however the current fan consensus is that the term, is more appropriately written as "Inishie no Sekiban" due to the in-game SoundLink pronunciation of the game's title as heard on period VHS recordings of live game-play.</desc>
		<releasedate>19970330T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>St.GIGA</publisher>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./BS Zelda no Densetsu - Map 2 - Dai-1-wa (Japan) (SoundLink).zip</path>
		<name>Bs Zelda No Densetsu - Map 2 - Dai-1-wa</name>
		<desc>BS The Legend of Zelda ( BS Zeruda no Densetsu) was a remake of the NES game The Legend of Zelda, released for the Satellaview attachment for the Super Famicom in Japan.
The gameplay was identical to its predecessor, but the maximum Rupees was increased to allow you more than a thousand (rather than 255 as in The Legend of Zelda), the overworld was heavily altered, and dungeons were completely different. This game was broadcasted in two versions, Map 1 and Map 2. Map 1 is sometimes referred to as a "Third Quest", in reference to The Legend of Zelda's Second Quest, and Map 2 would therefore be a Fourth Quest.
The game was divided into four weekly episodes, this is the first episode</desc>
		<releasedate>19950809T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>St.GIGA</publisher>
		<genre>Action / Adventure</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./BS Zelda no Densetsu - Map 2 - Dai-4-wa (Japan) (SoundLink) [b].zip</path>
		<name>Bs Zelda No Densetsu</name>
		<desc>BS Zelda no Densetsu is a Downloadable 4-part Soundlink game for the Satellaview that was broadcast in at least 5 distinct runs between August 6, 1995 and January 4, 1997. A program called BS Zelda no Asobikata was also broadcast in the half-hour prior to broadcasts of BS Zelda. This program seems to have been a radio tutorial teaching players how to play BS Zelda. The gameplay draws directly from The Legend of Zelda. The plot of BS Zelda varies considerably from the plot of the original due in great part to the fact that the hero of the game is not Link (the hero of The Legend of Zelda). Instead, BS Zelda is closely associated with the story presented in the BS-X interface cartridge, with the Hero of Light actually representing the BS-X avatar according the the BS Zelda storyline. Another major factor in the plot of BS Zelda is the fact that the story is most closely related to the story given in The Legend of Zelda: A Link to the Past. Both plots take up after the conclusion of Kamigami no Triforce - a fact that for Inishie no Sekiban produces one of the many plot inconsistencies/contradictions for which the series has become noted.</desc>
		<releasedate>19950806T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Action / Adventure</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Chou Aniki - Bakuretsu Rantou Hen (Japan).zip</path>
		<name>Cho Aniki : Bakuretsu Rantou Hen</name>
		<desc>A demo of the Super Famicom game of the same name. Botei has returned for the 11th Galaxy Bodybuilding Competition after his defeat to Idaten, Samson and Adon, and is aiming for victory to become the greatest bodybuilder in the Galaxy. Idaten must train his body and mind, to get chiseled, oiled and muscular to prove he is the true king of protein and the Galaxy's greatest body.</desc>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Chrono Trigger - Character Zukan (Japan).zip</path>
		<name>Chrono Trigger : Jet Bike Spécial</name>
		<desc>BS Chrono Trigger: Character Library is essentially a bestiary containing not only all of the playable characters, but all of the enemies as well. The game was released for the Japan only Satellaview in 1995, and was developed by Squaresoft and published by Nintendo. The game is nothing more than an addon to Chrono Trigger, containing every sprite for each character and enemy, as well as a brief description of each one. BS Chrono Trigger: Character Library is also included in Final Fantasy Chronicles.</desc>
		<releasedate>19950816T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Squaresoft</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Race, Driving</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Chrono Trigger - Jet Bike Special (Japan).zip</path>
		<name>Chrono Trigger : Jet Bike Spécial</name>
		<desc>BS Chrono Trigger: Character Library is essentially a bestiary containing not only all of the playable characters, but all of the enemies as well. The game was released for the Japan only Satellaview in 1995, and was developed by Squaresoft and published by Nintendo. The game is nothing more than an addon to Chrono Trigger, containing every sprite for each character and enemy, as well as a brief description of each one. BS Chrono Trigger: Character Library is also included in Final Fantasy Chronicles.</desc>
		<releasedate>19950816T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Squaresoft</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Race, Driving</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Chrono Trigger - Music Library (Japan).zip</path>
		<name>Chrono Trigger : Jet Bike Spécial</name>
		<desc>BS Chrono Trigger: Character Library is essentially a bestiary containing not only all of the playable characters, but all of the enemies as well. The game was released for the Japan only Satellaview in 1995, and was developed by Squaresoft and published by Nintendo. The game is nothing more than an addon to Chrono Trigger, containing every sprite for each character and enemy, as well as a brief description of each one. BS Chrono Trigger: Character Library is also included in Final Fantasy Chronicles.</desc>
		<releasedate>19950816T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Squaresoft</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Race, Driving</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Cock-A-Doodle-Do (Japan).zip</path>
		<name>Cock-a-doodle-do</name>
		<desc>Cock-A-Doodle-Do is about the misadventures of an alcoholic boy named Nicole (unfortunately for him), who recently lost all his fortune, and his last possession, a pet chicken named Pal. Pal fights animal poachers, befriends a cat and a fairy, and perhaps later on in the game does actual JRPG-like heroic deeds.</desc>
		<releasedate>19960404T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Super Dante</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Role playing games</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Daibakushou Jinsei Gekijou (Japan).zip</path>
		<name>Daibakushou Jinsei Gekijou</name>
		<desc>Daibakushou Jinseigekijou: Ooedo Nikki is a view-limited Downloadable game for the Satellaview that was broadcast in at least 4 runs between March 2, 1997 and February 21, 1998. From November 15, 1998 and onward, the game dropped its subtitle to become simply Daibakushou Jinseigekijou.</desc>
		<developer>Taito</developer>
		<publisher>Taito</publisher>
		<genre>Board game</genre>
		<players>1-4</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Darius Force (Japan).zip</path>
		<name>Darius Force</name>
		<desc>For countless millennia, the space tyrant Belser and his cosmic marauders have terrorized this once peaceful galaxy. Now, no sector remains safe from these stellar mercenaries and their evil empire. The Galactic Federation has finally called on two of its ace pilots and their sleek Silver Hawk warships to do battle with Belser's malicious metal menaces and reclaim the beloved planet Darius. Climb into the pilot's seat for a solo mission against Belser's forces; or engage the enemies with a fellow Federation pilot in a two-player simultaneous team attack. The future of the galaxy rests on the success of this perilous quest.</desc>
		<genre>Shoot'em up / Horizontal</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./DerbyStal 96 - Taiou 97-nendo Ban (Japan) (Data Pack).zip</path>
		<name>Derbystal 96 - Taiou 97-nendo Ban</name>
		<desc>The final set of data, with updated statistics for the year 1997, of this Satellaview version of the Super Famicom game Derby Stallion 96</desc>
		<releasedate>19971101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>ASCII Entertainment</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Horses race</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Dezaemon BSX Version - BS-X Shooting (Japan) (En).zip</path>
		<name>Dezaemon Bsx Version - Bs-x Shooting</name>
		<desc>The first of the three “Satella-shooting trilogy” games, this little Dezaemon-engine shmup is short, yet crazy and chaotic. Launch 8M Packs at your enemies! Face the likes of surfing dog and kissing shark! Beware the enemies with weird quasi-realistic faces plastered on them!</desc>
		<releasedate>19940101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Athena</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Shoot'em up / Vertical</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Dezaemon BSX Version - Sugoi STG 2 - Crystal Guardian (Japan) (En).zip</path>
		<name>Dezaemon BSX Version - Sugoi STG 2 - Crystal Guardian</name>
		<desc>The third in a series of user-created games, Crystal Guardian uses the Dezaemon engine, a shoot'em up creation tool for the Super Famicom. A winner of an official game-creation contest, the technically impressive game sets a robotic angel against an army of monsters, bosses with gigantic sprites and enormous explosions.</desc>
		<releasedate>19940101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Athena</developer>
		<genre>Shoot'em up / Vertical</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Dokapon Gaiden - Honoo no Audition (Japan).zip</path>
		<name>Dokapon Gaiden - Honoo No Audition</name>
		<desc>Dokapon Gaiden: Honoo no Audition is a view-limited Downloadable game for the Satellaview that was broadcast in at least 2 runs between February 1, 1998 and November 28, 1998. Prior to February 1, 1998, the game was simply called Dokapon Gaiden.</desc>
		<releasedate>19980201T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Asmik</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Dr. Mario BS (Japan) (6-3).zip</path>
		<name>Dr. Mario</name>
		<desc>Dr. Mario BS Version is a Satellaview video game released in 1997 for the Super Famicom. It's an altered version of the popular Dr. Mario video game and was released only in Japan. It was the last game to be broadcast over the Satellaview.

It is a puzzle game where the objective is to defeat different colored germs using vitamins of the same color. It is basically four in a row just like Tetris (row or column counts) or to put it another way, to defeat each germ, three halves of the same color must be next to the germ. These halves do not need to be on the same pill. The germs will multiply as the levels progress.</desc>
		<releasedate>19970330T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Puzzle-Game</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Dragon Slayer - Eiyuu Densetsu (Japan).zip</path>
		<name>Dragon Slayer - Eiyuu Densetsu</name>
		<desc>Unlike the previous Dragon Slayer games, which were all side-scrolling action RPGs, The Legend of Heroes is a far more straightforward turn-based RPG of the Dragon Quest mold. It allowed for a party of up to four characters and had a few modern upgrades, such as allowing the player to distribute stats after a level up, target separate monsters and restart a battle if their party gets wiped out.

It received one direct sequel, Dragon Slayer: The Legend of Heroes II, before the series would drop the Dragon Slayer prefix and continue as a separate Falcom property.</desc>
		<releasedate>19970831T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nihon Falcom</developer>
		<publisher>Epoch</publisher>
		<genre>Japanese RPG</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Dynami Tracer (Japan).zip</path>
		<name>Dynami Tracer</name>
		<desc>Dynami Tracer is a mischievous mÃ©lange of RPG exploration and racing. It was released exclusively for Nintendo's Satellaview system, which sent games to the Super Famicom via satellite signals, requiring a special adapter to receive and decode the data. This means that Dynami Tracer was never released in cartridge form, and as such, you can't purchase it anywhere, ever. The RPG aspect primarily involves your character going from star to star, interacting with the flamboyant locals and acquiring information. Every once in a while, you'll somehow get yourself involved in a race</desc>
		<releasedate>19960127T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Square</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Role playing games</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Excitebike - Bunbun Mario Battle - Stadium 1 (Japan) (6-30) (SoundLink).zip</path>
		<name>Excitebike - Bun Bun Mario Battle</name>
		<desc>BS Excitebike Bun Bun Mario Stadium was the a game released in four downloadable versions on the Satellaview download service. The game is also known as Mario Excitebike. It was released for the Satellaview in 1996 only in Japan, and is the obscure sequel to the NES game Excitebike. Each version added a number of new characters, eventually adding up to six characters in all. The game plays similarly to Excitebike on the NES, although it does have a couple differences. One difference is the fact that the player can pick up coins along the racetrack (which do nothing besides adding to the score). The only other change was an added SUPER mode, which gave the player infinite boost.</desc>
		<releasedate>19970101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Race, Driving</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Excitebike - Bunbun Mario Battle - Stadium 2 (Japan) (7-6) (SoundLink).zip</path>
		<name>Excitebike - Bun Bun Mario Battle</name>
		<desc>BS Excitebike Bun Bun Mario Stadium was the a game released in four downloadable versions on the Satellaview download service. The game is also known as Mario Excitebike. It was released for the Satellaview in 1996 only in Japan, and is the obscure sequel to the NES game Excitebike. Each version added a number of new characters, eventually adding up to six characters in all. The game plays similarly to Excitebike on the NES, although it does have a couple differences. One difference is the fact that the player can pick up coins along the racetrack (which do nothing besides adding to the score). The only other change was an added SUPER mode, which gave the player infinite boost.</desc>
		<releasedate>19970101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Race, Driving</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Excitebike - Bunbun Mario Battle - Stadium 3 (Japan) (2-8) (SoundLink).zip</path>
		<name>Excitebike - Bun Bun Mario Battle</name>
		<desc>BS Excitebike Bun Bun Mario Stadium was the a game released in four downloadable versions on the Satellaview download service. The game is also known as Mario Excitebike. It was released for the Satellaview in 1996 only in Japan, and is the obscure sequel to the NES game Excitebike. Each version added a number of new characters, eventually adding up to six characters in all. The game plays similarly to Excitebike on the NES, although it does have a couple differences. One difference is the fact that the player can pick up coins along the racetrack (which do nothing besides adding to the score). The only other change was an added SUPER mode, which gave the player infinite boost.</desc>
		<releasedate>19970101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Race, Driving</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Excitebike - Bunbun Mario Battle - Stadium 4 (Japan) (2-18) (SoundLink).zip</path>
		<name>Excitebike - Bun Bun Mario Battle</name>
		<desc>BS Excitebike Bun Bun Mario Stadium was the a game released in four downloadable versions on the Satellaview download service. The game is also known as Mario Excitebike. It was released for the Satellaview in 1996 only in Japan, and is the obscure sequel to the NES game Excitebike. Each version added a number of new characters, eventually adding up to six characters in all. The game plays similarly to Excitebike on the NES, although it does have a couple differences. One difference is the fact that the player can pick up coins along the racetrack (which do nothing besides adding to the score). The only other change was an added SUPER mode, which gave the player infinite boost.</desc>
		<releasedate>19970101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Race, Driving</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./F-Zero (Japan).zip</path>
		<name>F-zero</name>
		<desc>F-Zero is a futuristic racing game where the characters control flying cars and compete in an intergalactic tournament.
In total there are four characters with their own vehicle, each one having different characteristics. A race consists of giving five laps along a track, being mandatory to complete each one of them in one of the first places to avoid being disqualified. When a lap is completed the player is rewarded with a power called "Super Jet", which lasts for six seconds or so.
The objective of the game is to defeat the other characters by crossing the finish line at the end of a race, avoiding certain damage zones within the tracks. Each vehicle has its own energy meter, which works as a way of measuring the durability of the machines; this in turn decreases each time the player passes through a sandy area or collides, and energy can be recharged while driving over a pit stop.</desc>
		<releasedate>19961201T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Race, Driving</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Firemen, The (Japan).zip</path>
		<name>The Firemen</name>
		<desc>The fire is alive - and it's racing straight towards you!
A fire has broken out in a high-tech chemical factory, where a highly explosive chemical, MDL, is being developed. It's up to you and your fire-fighting team to save the people trapped in the building, and stop the fire from reaching the MDL. Because if it does, the whole building is going to blow...

-An action shooting game with a gripping storyline and 2D overhead perspective.
-Evade sudden hazards and save survivors.
-Multi-level action - crawl along the ground to advance, and hose the fire from both high and low levels.</desc>
		<releasedate>19970202T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo EAD</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Gambler Jiko Chuushinha 2 - Dorapon Quest (Japan) (12-20).zip</path>
		<name>Gambler Jiko Chuushinha 2 - Dorapon Quest</name>
		<desc>A Satellaview version of the Super Famicom game of the same name. A mahjong game based on Katayama Masayuki's manga Gambler Jiko Chuushinha. Like the first Super Famicom game subtitles Super Zugan, which was also based on a manga created by Katayama Masayuki, Dorapon Quest frames its various mahjong games as "battles" in an RPG.</desc>
		<developer>Bits Laboratory</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Mahjong</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Golf Daisuki! O.B. Club (Japan).zip</path>
		<name>Golf Daisuki! O.b. Club</name>
		<desc>Golf Daisuki! O.B. Club is a view-limited Downloadable golfing game for the Satellaview initially running between August 10, 1997 and August 23, 1997. The game was rebroadcast for at least 4 runs ending in March 30, 1998.
Electronic Gaming Monthly magazine produced a preview of this game. Their preview had an English-language logo even though the game was never released in the USA in any form.</desc>
		<releasedate>19970810T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nippon Computer Systems Corp.</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Sports / Golf</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Heisei Gunjin Shougi (Japan).zip</path>
		<name>Heisei Gunjin Shougi</name>
		<desc>Heisei Gunjin Shougi is a traditional Japanese game. We start by choosing a place in the city in which the game will take place, then after a short cutscene, we place small characters on the boxes. Then the game begins. The game board consists of the chosen decor which is divided into boxes. We move these "pawns" in turn, respecting the rules for moving the Shougi and when 2 pieces meet, a small scene shows their "fight".
</desc>
		<releasedate>19960126T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Carrozzeria</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Shougi</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Ikari no Yousai (Japan).zip</path>
		<name>Ikari No Yousai</name>
		<desc>Ikari no Yousai is a view-limited Downloadable game for the Satellaview that was broadcast in at least 2 runs between February 1, 1998 and December 19, 1998.</desc>
		<releasedate>19980201T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Jaleco</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Jewel of Live (Japan).zip</path>
		<name>Jewel Of Live</name>
		<desc>Jewel of Live is the first part of the broadcast of RPG Tsukuru, known in the West as RPG Maker, on the Satellaview. Both a RPG-creation software and a video game, it features a rich story and nice graphics.</desc>
		<developer>ASCII Entertainment</developer>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Jewel of Live II (Japan) (Memory Pack).zip</path>
		<name>Jewel of Live II</name>
		<desc>Jewel of Live II is the second part of the broadcast of RPG Tsukuru, known in the West as RPG Maker, on the Satellaview. Both a RPG-creation software and a video game, it features a rich story and nice graphics.</desc>
		<developer>ASCII Entertainment</developer>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Jissen Pachi-Slot Hisshouhou! Twin (Japan).zip</path>
		<name>Jissen Pachi-slot Hisshouhou! Twin</name>
		<desc>Jissen Pachi-Slot Hisshouhou! Twin ("Combat Pachi-Slot Winning Strategy! Twin") is a pachi-slots game from Sammy Corporation. It is the first of two "Twin" spin-offs of the long-running Jissen Pachi-Slot Hisshouhou! series, both of which were released in 1997 for the Super Famicom. There was also a Jissen Pachi-Slot Hisshouhou! Twin for Saturn, but it used different machines and might be considered a separate game.

The game features two popular pachi-slots mascots in Japan: the Pink Panther, the popular feline character that originated in the 1960s Peter Sellers Inspector Clouseau movies, and Cranky Condor.</desc>
		<releasedate>19970315T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Sammy Studios</developer>
		<publisher>Sammy Studios</publisher>
		<genre>Casino</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Kaizou Choujin Shubibinman Zero (Japan).zip</path>
		<name>Kaizou Choujin Shubibinman Zero</name>
		<desc>A sequel to the Shubibinman Turbografx action platformers developed exclusively for the SNES.

A new gang of cyborg-enhanced goons threatens peace in the city, so "Doc" decides to test his newest creations: Raita and Azuki, by sending them to destroy all the baddies and restore peace.

The game plays as an 2D action platformer as previous entries in the series, in which you proceed through each stage pummeling enemies and collecting power-ups to enhance your powers. Now for the first time each character has unique abilities and attacks, furthermore each character has a charging attack that can be used to energize your partner thus encouraging teamplay in the two-player cooperative mode.
</desc>
		<releasedate>20170630T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Masaya Games</developer>
		<publisher>Columbus Circle</publisher>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Kessen! Dokapon Oukoku IV - Densetsu no Yuusha-tachi (Japan).zip</path>
		<name>Kessen! Dokapon Oukoku 4 - Densetsu No Yuusha-tachi</name>
		<desc>Kessen! Dokapon Okukoku IV: Densetsu no Yuusha Tachi ("Decisive Battle! Dokapon Kingdoms IV: Legend of Heroes") is a mix of an RPG and a multiplayer board game. Players move their heroes around the board, gaining levels and finding equipment, and eventually saving a kingdom from encroaching monsters. The goal is to beat the target monsters before the other players.</desc>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Kid Klown no Crazy Chase (Japan).zip</path>
		<name>Kid Klown No Crazy Chase</name>
		<desc>Kid Klown in Crazy Chase is a platform video game developed and published by Kemco for the Super Nintendo Entertainment System. It was released in North America in September 1994, Japan on October 21, 1994 and in Europe in 1994. The game features the Kid Klown, the player character who is tasked with rescuing the Princess Honey from the villain Black Jack. Players view gameplay from an isometric perspective as Kid Klown pursues a lit fuse in order to stop it from reaching a spade bomb. The game was re-released for the Game Boy Advance and features 11 new levels, four mini-games, and a multi-player mode.</desc>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Kiki Kaikai - Nazo no Kuro Manteau (Japan).zip</path>
		<name>Kikikai-kai - Nazo No Kuro Manteau</name>
		<desc>This is the Japanese version of Pocky and Rocky. A shrine maiden and a Nopino goblin investigate why the other goblins are acting badly. This is a really good and fun shoot-em-up.</desc>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Kirby no Omochabako - Arrange Ball (Japan).zip</path>
		<name>Kirby no Omochabako - Arrange Ball</name>
		<desc>The player is given the goal of launching spherical Kirbys into the nine holes occupied by Mr. Frostys. The player is given a certain number of Kirbys to launch, and the game ends when he/she runs out of Kirbys to shoot. The player can choose how much power to put into each shot. Points are awarded if the player lands three Kirbys in a row—the more rows the player completes, the more points he/she will earn.</desc>
		<releasedate>19960208T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>HAL Laboratory</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Puzzle-Game / Throw</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Kirby no Omochabako - Baseball (Japan) (2-9).zip</path>
		<name>Kirby No Omochabako - Baseball</name>
		<desc>Kirby's Toy Box is the translated name of a small series of Kirby sub-games titled (Kabi no Omochabako, meaning Kirby's Toy Box) in Japan. The Kirby's Toy Box series was broadcast over Nintendo's first form of digital distribution, the Satellaview satellite network, and, depending on when the player connected to the network, different games were available at different times. These could be downloaded to the Satellaview base unit, or an 8-megabit rewritable "Memory Pak" ROM cartridge compatible with the Satellaview. As these games did not use the SoundLink live audio streaming technology utilized by other Satellaview games, after being downloaded, they could be played at any time after the broadcast as long as they were not deleted or overwritten.</desc>
		<genre>Sports / Baseball</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Kirby no Omochabako - Cannon Ball (Japan).zip</path>
		<name>Kirby No Omochabako - Cannon Ball</name>
		<desc>Kirby no Omochabako: Cannonball is one of the Kirby no Omochabako (Kirby's Toy Box) minigames for the Satellaview service. The player controls a giant robot aimed at destroying another giant robot, using Kirbys as ammunition. Similar to the Worms franchise, there is terrain which can be destroyed in a way that can help the player (i.e. by giving them more space to fire).</desc>
		<developer>HAL Laboratory</developer>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Kirby no Omochabako - Guruguru Ball (Japan).zip</path>
		<name>Kirby No Omochabako - Baseball</name>
		<desc>Kirby's Toy Box is the translated name of a small series of Kirby sub-games titled (Kabi no Omochabako, meaning Kirby's Toy Box) in Japan. The Kirby's Toy Box series was broadcast over Nintendo's first form of digital distribution, the Satellaview satellite network, and, depending on when the player connected to the network, different games were available at different times. These could be downloaded to the Satellaview base unit, or an 8-megabit rewritable "Memory Pak" ROM cartridge compatible with the Satellaview. As these games did not use the SoundLink live audio streaming technology utilized by other Satellaview games, after being downloaded, they could be played at any time after the broadcast as long as they were not deleted or overwritten.</desc>
		<genre>Sports / Baseball</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Kirby no Omochabako - Hoshi Kuzushi (Japan).zip</path>
		<name>Kirby No Omochabako - Hoshi Kuzushi</name>
		<desc>A breakout style game in which the player controls Kirby with Rick-like characters holding the paddle. There are six stages, with King Dedede as the boss of Stage 6.</desc>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Kirby no Omochabako - Pachinko (Japan).zip</path>
		<name>Kirby No Omochabako - Pachinko</name>
		<desc>The game involves sending Kirby through a machine similar to a pachinko machine. The player must land Kirby in specific pockets, and there are bonus points available for hitting the large Kirby in the middle of the room.</desc>
		<genre>Casino</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Kirby no Omochabako - Pinball (Japan).zip</path>
		<name>Kirby No Omochabako - Pinball</name>
		<desc>A pinball game themed around Kirby, with various characters from the series appearing like King Dedede, Mr. Frosty and Kracko. Players controls Kirby as the ball, and the player must keep him in the pinball machine at most three times until the game is over.</desc>
		<genre>Pinball</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Kodomo Chousadan Mighty Pockets - Chousa 1 - Junk-ya Black no Ie (Japan) (SoundLink) [b].zip</path>
		<name>Kodomo Chousadan Mighty Pockets</name>
		<desc>Kodomo Chousadan Mighty Pockets is a board game with a detective motif similar to the game of Clue. The rules of the game, however, are considerably different. Throughout the game, SoundLink narration is used including rapping over Michael Jackson sound samples and remixes of 1950′s American Television.</desc>
		<releasedate>19970907T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Board game</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Kodomo Chousadan Mighty Pockets - Chousa 2 - Hanzai Toshi Big Apple (Japan) (SoundLink) [b].zip</path>
		<name>Kodomo Chousadan Mighty Pockets</name>
		<desc>Kodomo Chousadan Mighty Pockets is a board game with a detective motif similar to the game of Clue. The rules of the game, however, are considerably different. Throughout the game, SoundLink narration is used including rapping over Michael Jackson sound samples and remixes of 1950′s American Television.</desc>
		<releasedate>19970907T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Board game</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Kodomo Chousadan Mighty Pockets - Chousa 3 - Kyakusen Queen Patra no Nazo (Japan) (SoundLink).zip</path>
		<name>Kodomo Chousadan Mighty Pockets</name>
		<desc>Kodomo Chousadan Mighty Pockets is a board game with a detective motif similar to the game of Clue. The rules of the game, however, are considerably different. Throughout the game, SoundLink narration is used including rapping over Michael Jackson sound samples and remixes of 1950′s American Television.</desc>
		<releasedate>19970907T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Board game</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Koi wa Balance - Tatoeba K-kun no Tabou na Ichinichi Hen (Japan).zip</path>
		<name>Koi wa Balance - Tatoeba K-kun no Tabou na Ichinic</name>
		<desc>Koi wa Balance: Tatoeba K-kun no Tabou na Ichinichi Hen is a Downloadable game for the Satellaview that was first broadcast on January 27, 1996. The game is a board game and it features, among other characters, both Gaspar and Johnny from the earlier Square title, Chrono Trigger.</desc>
		<releasedate>19960101T000000</releasedate>
		<publisher>Square</publisher>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Konae-chan no Dokidoki Penguin Kazoku (Japan).zip</path>
		<name>Konae-chan No Dokidoki Penguin Kazoku</name>
		<desc>Konae-chan no DokiDoki Pengin Kazoku is a Downloadable Event Game developed by Pax Softnica for the Satellaview. It stars Konae and was distributed as a tie in to the Radio Program "If Tomorrow Comes...".</desc>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Kouryaku Casino Bar Mokuyoubi - Poker (Japan).zip</path>
		<name>Casino Bar Mokuyoubi</name>
		<desc>A gambling game allowing, among other things, to play poker using your Satellaview avatar.</desc>
		<genre>Casino / Cards</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Kouryaku Casino Bar Nichiyoubi - Roulette + Game Tora no Ooana Special (2-24) (Japan) [b].zip</path>
		<name>Kouryaku Casino Bar Nichiyoubi - Roulette  G</name>
		<desc>A casino game, split into two Satellaview broadcasts. This is the Roulette version of the game.</desc>
		<genre>Casino / Cards</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Kouryaku Casino Bar Suiyoubi - Poker + Kouryaku Casino Bar Kinyoubi - Slots (Japan) [b].zip</path>
		<name>Kouryaku Casino Bar Nichiyoubi - Roulette  G</name>
		<desc>A casino game, split into two Satellaview broadcasts. This is the Roulette version of the game.</desc>
		<genre>Casino / Cards</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Lemmings (Japan) (En).zip</path>
		<name>Lemmings</name>
		<desc>Thousands of Lemmings are on the loose, marching towards extinction unless you can save them. Without minds of their own, they are completely helpless, faithfully following their leader through 125 levels of blazing fires, endless canyons, deadly tunnels and ancient ruins. You or you and a friend can command the Lemmings to dig, climb, tunnel, float and build their way to safety. But you have to move fast, because each moment you hesitate, more Lemmings may drop from above!</desc>
		<genre>Puzzle-Game</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Let's Pachinko Nante Gindama 1 (Japan).zip</path>
		<name>Let's Pachinko Nante Gindama</name>
		<desc>Let's Pachinko: Nante Gindama is a view-limited Downloadable game for the Satellaview that was broadcast in at least 2 runs between February 1, 1998 and November 28, 1998. Pachinko is a japanese tradition, a gambling game involving small metallic balls that fall down a playing board and can earn the player some prizes.</desc>
		<releasedate>19980201T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Telenet Japan</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Casino</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Let's Pachinko Nante Gindama 2 (Japan) (11-8).zip</path>
		<name>Let's Pachinko Nante Gindama</name>
		<desc>Let's Pachinko: Nante Gindama is a view-limited Downloadable game for the Satellaview that was broadcast in at least 2 runs between February 1, 1998 and November 28, 1998. Pachinko is a japanese tradition, a gambling game involving small metallic balls that fall down a playing board and can earn the player some prizes.</desc>
		<releasedate>19980201T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Telenet Japan</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Casino</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Let's Pachinko Nante Gindama 3 (Japan) (9-15).zip</path>
		<name>Let's Pachinko Nante Gindama</name>
		<desc>Let's Pachinko: Nante Gindama is a view-limited Downloadable game for the Satellaview that was broadcast in at least 2 runs between February 1, 1998 and November 28, 1998. Pachinko is a japanese tradition, a gambling game involving small metallic balls that fall down a playing board and can earn the player some prizes.</desc>
		<releasedate>19980201T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Telenet Japan</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Casino</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Let's Pachinko Nante Gindama 4 (Japan).zip</path>
		<name>Let's Pachinko Nante Gindama</name>
		<desc>Let's Pachinko: Nante Gindama is a view-limited Downloadable game for the Satellaview that was broadcast in at least 2 runs between February 1, 1998 and November 28, 1998. Pachinko is a japanese tradition, a gambling game involving small metallic balls that fall down a playing board and can earn the player some prizes.</desc>
		<releasedate>19980201T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Telenet Japan</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Casino</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Logos Panic Goaisatsu BS Ban (Japan).zip</path>
		<name>Logos Panic Goaisatsu Bs Ban</name>
		<desc>A puzzle game which relies on the player's knowledge of kanji and the Japanese language : the player must form phrases with a list of kanji. The characters were designed by Kotobuki Shiriagari, a mangaka known for his dark humor and social criticism.</desc>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Lord Monarch (Japan).zip</path>
		<name>Lord Monarch</name>
		<desc>Lord Monarch is a real-time strategy game. In this very complete game, you will have to manage an entire kingdom. Whether it's harvesting resources, creating new buildings or managing the kingdom's money, you will have to take care of your flock. Beyond the borders of your kingdom, there are obviously other kingdoms that are also developing. You must therefore be ready to defend your country and why not even choose to take them by surprise, by going to confront them to extend the limits of your kingdom. It was downloadable in a limited time for the Satellaview and was released at least twice between 20 December 1997 and 31 March 1998.</desc>
		<releasedate>19971220T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Aim Software</developer>
		<publisher>Epoch</publisher>
		<genre>Strategy</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Mario Paint - BS Ban (Japan).zip</path>
		<name>Mario Paint - Bs Ban</name>
		<desc>Mario Paint BS Ban is a Downloadable Game for the Satellaview that ran between August 3, 1997 and August 30, 1997, 1998. The game is a painting tool and it functions as a pseudo-sequel to the 1992 game, Mario Paint. Between November 2, 1997 and November 22, 1997, the "Mario Paint BS Ban Contest" was held and broadcasts of the game were accompanied by a digital magazine related to the contest. The results of the contest were broadcast between December 28, 1997 and January 31, 1998 in the form of a second digital magazine accompanying the release of Mario Paint BS Ban - Yuushou Sakuhin Naizou Version.</desc>
		<releasedate>19970803T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Mario Paint - Yuushou Naizou Ban (Japan).zip</path>
		<name>Mario Paint - Yuushou Naizou Ban</name>
		<desc>A modified version of the original Mario Paint BS Ban that includes the winning design from a contest that happened in Japan in 1997. The winning picture was designed by a Tokyo-based gamer named Hiroko Mizota and is entitled "Dreaming of the Moon."</desc>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Monopoly 2 BS - Red Cup (Japan).zip</path>
		<name>Monopoly 2 Bs - Red Cup</name>
		<desc>Monopoly (Japan) is a Miscellaneous game, developed and published by Tomy Corporation.</desc>
		<genre>Board game</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Monopoly 2 BS - Yellow Cup (Japan).zip</path>
		<name>Monopoly 2 Bs - Yellow Cup</name>
		<desc>Monopoly (Japan) is a Miscellaneous game, developed and published by Tomy Corporation.</desc>
		<genre>Board game</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./New 3D Golf Simulation - Waialae no Kiseki (Japan).zip</path>
		<name>New 3d Golf Simulation - Waialae No Kiseki</name>
		<desc>Master the Winds of Waialae!
Step up to the first tee and feel Hawaii's trade winds. This is Waialae-18 holes of championship action, played against the glittering backdrop of the Pacific.
Every stroke tests your golf strategy. Should you hit big off the tee or lay up with an iron? Add backspin for bite? Chip-and-roll from the fringe? True Golf lets you perfect every stroke in your game.
Each hole appears in perfect detail. Discover Waialae's deep-pitched bunkers on marble-slick greens. Unsure about strategy? Look for tips from the club pro.
Every round serves up a new challenge. Compete with pros, or line up a foursome of friends. Check the wind, scope out the new pin placements. In True Golf, every round is a whole new game.</desc>
		<releasedate>19910101T000000</releasedate>
		<publisher>T&amp;E Soft</publisher>
		<genre>Sports / Golf</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./New Yatterman - Nandai Kandai Yajirobee (Japan).zip</path>
		<name>New Yatterman - Nandai Kandai Yajirobee</name>
		<desc>New Yatterman: Nandai Kandai Yajirobee is a multiplayer-focused game for the Super Famicom that is based on the 1970s Yatterman anime franchise.

Yatterman features a team of three heroes, all called Yatterman, who attempt to beat the supervillain team Doronbo (also a group of three) to a set of skull coins which will reveal the way to a giant treasure horde. The heroes often use toys and mechs to defeat their incompetent opponents, such as the male protagonist's kendamagic.

The game is similar to First Star's Spy vs. Spy series, in that both teams are attempting to reach the treasure first. They can trip up their opponents via a number of traps, some of which have conditional uses. By burying mines and setting off missiles, the player can whittle down the health of their opponents as well as keep them off their tracks. If the two teams meet, they fight each other in a three-on-three tag team battle with the losing side taking a large hit to their health. The game can be played single-player (as either the Yatterman team or the Doronbo team) or multiplayer.</desc>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Nintama Rantarou 2 (Japan).zip</path>
		<name>Nintama Rantarou 2</name>
		<desc>Nintama Rantaro 2 is a Downloadable game for the Satellaview that was broadcast in at least 2 runs between March 29, 1998 and November 28, 1998.</desc>
		<releasedate>19960329T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Culture Brain</developer>
		<publisher>Culture Brain</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Nintama Rantarou Special (Japan).zip</path>
		<name>Nintama Rantarou Special</name>
		<desc>Nintama Rantarou Special ("Ninja Boy Rantarou Special") is an action-platformer game with a few different modes. It is also the fourth Super Famicom game to be based on the Nintama Rantarou manga and anime license, and most closely resembles the first game.

The game's story mode has the player move from character to character while cutscenes play, with some gameplay sequences to break it up. Shinbei's first sequence starts as an adventure game, and segues to a runaway horse sequence, while Rantarou and Kirimaru progress through side-scrolling levels. Rantarou can use a grappling hook to cross large gaps, while Kirimaru can climb mossy walls.</desc>
		<releasedate>19960809T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Culture Brain</developer>
		<publisher>Culture Brain</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Panel de Pon - Event '98 (Japan) (12-28).zip</path>
		<name>Panel De Pon - Event '98</name>
		<desc>Panel de Pon Event '98 is a Downloadable game for the Satellaview that was broadcast on January 31, 1998, it is a slightly modified event version of the game Panel de Pon.</desc>
		<releasedate>19971228T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Intelligent Systems</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Puzzle-Game</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Radical Dreamers - Nusume Nai Houseki (Japan) (2-3) (Memory Pack) [b].zip</path>
		<name>Radical Dreamers</name>
		<desc>This text-based adventure (with some interesting background graphics) was originally released in Japan over the Satellaview system. The game is a spin-off from the Chrono Series, and was the precursor to Chrono Cross. It tells the story of Serge (travelling musician), Kid (thief), and Magil (wizard) as they attempt to steal the Frozen Flame from Viper Manor.  Contains multiple, often humorous endings. An interesting game for Chrono Trigger/Cross fans, as this was the game that Chrono Cross was essentially a remake of.

Gameplay is something between a standard text adventure and a Choose Your Own Adventure book.  Rather than having a full array of possible actions, players are limited to the several options it presents at any time.  With newly discovered items and information, new areas can be reached.  Occasionally battles will occur during the exploration, which are also handled by displaying several possible actions to choose between, such as "Run" or "Jump back as it swings!"
</desc>
		<releasedate>19960601T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Square Enix</developer>
		<publisher>Square Enix</publisher>
		<genre>Role playing games</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Ryouma de Yuku (Japan) (Data Pack).zip</path>
		<name>Ryouma De Yuku</name>
		<desc>A role-playing game that is a parody of “Ryōma ga Yuku”, which seems to be a highly renowned piece of japanese literature, using RPG Tsukuru (RPG Maker) and written by Hikari Ōta of the Bakushō Mondai comedy duo.</desc>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Satella Walker 2 - Dai-1-wa - Mokumoku Kemuri Panic (Japan) (SoundLink).zip</path>
		<name>Satella Walker 2 - Sate Bou o Sukuidase!</name>
		<desc>SatellaWalker (also known by its shorthand, SW) is a Downloadable 2-part Soundlink game for the Satellaview that was broadcast between June 29, 1997 and January 2, 1998. The game's January broadcast was the result of having been the first winner of the third Player's Choice vote. SatellaWalker was followed by a sequel, SatellaWalker 2 in February 1998.</desc>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Satella Walker 2 - Sate Bou o Sukuidase! (Japan) (SoundLink).zip</path>
		<name>Satella Walker 2 - Sate Bou o Sukuidase!</name>
		<desc>SatellaWalker (also known by its shorthand, SW) is a Downloadable 2-part Soundlink game for the Satellaview that was broadcast between June 29, 1997 and January 2, 1998. The game's January broadcast was the result of having been the first winner of the third Player's Choice vote. SatellaWalker was followed by a sequel, SatellaWalker 2 in February 1998.</desc>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./SD Gundam G Next - Map Data (Japan) (3-25) (Data Pack).zip</path>
		<name>Sd Gundam G Next - Unit And Map Collection</name>
		<desc>An expansion set for SD Gundam GNext on the Super Famicom, which requires the original game to play. Includes additional missions and units, nowadays this would be considered a DLC.</desc>
		<releasedate>19960329T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Bandai</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Strategy</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./SD Gundam G Next - Unit &amp; Map Collection (Japan) (ROM) (CRC32 60B1B7E0).zip</path>
		<name>Sd Gundam G Next - Unit And Map Collection</name>
		<desc>An expansion set for SD Gundam GNext on the Super Famicom, which requires the original game to play. Includes additional missions and units, nowadays this would be considered a DLC.</desc>
		<releasedate>19960329T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Bandai</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Strategy</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Shanghai - Banri no Choujou (Japan).zip</path>
		<name>Shanghai - Banri No Choujou</name>
		<desc>Shanghai: Banri no Choujou is a view-limited Downloadable game for the Satellaview that was broadcast between November 15, 1998 and November 28, 1998.</desc>
		<genre>Asiatic board game</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Sonic Blast Man (Japan).zip</path>
		<name>Sonic Blast Man</name>
		<desc>You take on the role of Sonic Blast Man, a superhero, in this side-scrolling shooter, fighting against various forms of evil. While you have the typical punch, jump, and kick moves, the Sonic Blast Man also has two special power moves: Dynamite Punch and Screw Bomb. You travel through five different stages and fight enemies ranging from local ruffians to robots and even aliens from outer space.
</desc>
		<releasedate>19920101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Taito</developer>
		<publisher>Taito</publisher>
		<genre>Beat'em Up</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Sound Journal for Lovers - Valentine Special Vol. 1 (Japan) (SoundLink) [b].zip</path>
		<name>Sound Journal For Lovers - Valentine Special Vol. 1</name>
		<desc>Sound Journal for Lovers comprises a set of text and images meant to smoothly accompany the music that played during the St.GIGA broadcast hour. The majority of the contents are screens displaying an artist listing and lyrics scrolling upwards. Of the minor interactions available to the player, a toggle option changes the lyrics from English to a Japanese translation. The artists featured are Stevie Wonder, Paul Simon, Phil Collins, The Bee Gees, and numerous others.</desc>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Special Tee Shot (Japan).zip</path>
		<name>Special Tee Shot</name>
		<desc>BS Special Tee Shot is a game that was planned to be released on the SNES, though eventually was just made exclusively for the Super Famicom's Satellaview service. The game was later retooled and made into the game that is known as Kirby's Dream Course. It is unknown why the game was remade to feature Kirby characters, though it's presumed that it as because Nintendo thought that the game would prove more successful with a well known brand behind it.
The Satellaview video game had unique characters rather than already developed ones. Overall, however, the player character was uninspiring as it was simply just a red sphere that bounced around. Despite the fact that the game would be remade to feature Kirby characters, there are dramatic differences between the two titles, including the overall gameplay concept and levels. For example, in this game, the goal was simply to shoot the ball in the hole, while in the Kirby game you want to crash into enemies to destroy them. However, despite this, the games still share many similarities, such as graphics and the overall way the player controls the ball.

Interestingly, Special Tee Shot was featured not only in magazines but also on the back of SNES packages as advertisements before ultimately being cancelled and brought back with Kirby characters. It should also be noted that before being titled Kirby's Dream Course, the game was officially called Kirby's Tee Shot.</desc>
		<releasedate>19990425T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>HAL Laboratory</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Spriggan Powered BS - Dai-3-wa (Japan) (SoundLink).zip</path>
		<name>Spriggan Powered Bs - Prelude</name>
		<desc>A demo of the Spriggan Powered Super Famicom game. It countains only the first level of the retail game (which can be replayed multiple times) and some story- and manualtext with background pictures as a intro. Also, the game gives the player a password for the score after each playthrough of the first level, which was probably connected to a highscore contest. This is a soundlink game (the music was streamed live via the service) so there is no other music but SFX present in the preserved rom.</desc>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Spriggan Powered BS - Prelude (Japan) (SoundLink).zip</path>
		<name>Spriggan Powered Bs - Prelude</name>
		<desc>A demo of the Spriggan Powered Super Famicom game. It countains only the first level of the retail game (which can be replayed multiple times) and some story- and manualtext with background pictures as a intro. Also, the game gives the player a password for the score after each playthrough of the first level, which was probably connected to a highscore contest. This is a soundlink game (the music was streamed live via the service) so there is no other music but SFX present in the preserved rom.</desc>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Star Soldier - 2 Minute Mode (Japan) (En).zip</path>
		<name>Star Soldier - 2 Minute Mode</name>
		<desc>A Satellaview port of the Famicom game "Star Soldier", specifically its 2-minute long Caravan mode. Not much is known about this release, nor if there were a lot of other 8-bit games broadcasted on the service.</desc>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Super Aleste (Japan).zip</path>
		<name>Bs Super Aleste</name>
		<desc>The game's thrilling speed is its most attractive feature. The enemy movements are fast. Your shots and the enemies' shots are fast. Finally, the scrolling is fast. The screen filled with battle action just overflows with high speed shooting excitement. On top of that there is the Shot Control System operated with the "R" button. You can attack the enemy in a multitude of ways with a weapon using this system. Naturally, the features of the Super Famicom such as rotation, enlarging, and shrinking functions are used to their fullest and huge enemies never before possible are packed into this exciting MEGA game!</desc>
		<releasedate>19960101T000000</releasedate>
		<genre>Shooter / Plane</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Super Bomberman (Japan) (En).zip</path>
		<name>Super Bomber Man</name>
		<desc>North of the City of Peace (Bomberman city), located in the modern metropolis of Diamond City, the evil Carat Diamond and his court, along with the scientist Dr. Mok, have assigned a group of robots with offensive capabilities. Intending to steal Bomberman's advanced fighting abilities, Diamond created a fake Bomberman to go to the City of Peace and kidnap the real Bomberman.

Realising the situation, Black Bomberman prepares to take on the fake Bomberman alone, but ends up being defeated and having his castle taken. However, Black Bomberman escapes and finds refuge with White Bomberman and warns him of the danger ahead. Soon after the wave of enemy robots begins to advance towards the City of Peace, the two heroes must join forces to defeat this evil.</desc>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Super Bomberman 2 (Japan).zip</path>
		<name>Super Bomber Man 2</name>
		<desc>Five evil cyborgs, called the "Five Dastardly Bombers" are bent on taking over the universe. On planet Earth, they capture the original Bomberman, take him back to their base, and place him into a prison cell. He awakens in the dungeon of Magnet Bomber, and must fight his way to a final showdown with Magnet Bomber himself. In the following four worlds, Bomberman will challenge Golem Bomber, Pretty Bomber, Brain Bomber, and their leader, Plasma Bomber in an effort to save himself and free the Earth of these alien invaders.</desc>
		<developer>Hudson</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<players>1-4</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Super E.D.F. (Japan).zip</path>
		<name>Super Earth Defense Force</name>
		<desc>An evil organization, named AGYMA, threatens the 200 years of peace the galaxy has enjoyed.  From their base on the far side of the moon they have infiltrated many important locations on Earth.  Working for the Earth Defense Force, you are the lone pilot of a special craft designed to fight off AGYMA: the XA-1.

The game is a side-scrolling shoot 'em up with 6 levels, and a total of 8 state of the art weapons with which to fend off the attacks and thwart AGYMA's plot to destroy Earth and disrupt peace throughout the cosmos.
</desc>
		<developer>Jaleco</developer>
		<publisher>Jaleco</publisher>
		<genre>Shoot'em Up</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Super Famicom Wars BS Ban - Hagoromo-jima (Japan).zip</path>
		<name>Super Famicom Wars</name>
		<desc>Super Famicom Wars BS Ban is a view-limited Downloadable game for the Satellaview that was broadcast in April, 1998.</desc>
		<releasedate>19980501T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Intelligent Systems</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<players>1-4</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Super Famicom Wars BS Ban - Tsukinowa-jima (Japan).zip</path>
		<name>Super Famicom Wars</name>
		<desc>Super Famicom Wars BS Ban is a view-limited Downloadable game for the Satellaview that was broadcast in April, 1998.</desc>
		<releasedate>19980501T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Intelligent Systems</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<players>1-4</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Super Fire Pro Wrestling (Japan).zip</path>
		<name>Super Fire Pro Wrestling</name>
		<desc>A Satellaview broadcast of the wrestling game Super Fire Pro Wrestling. One of Goichi Suda's (Suda 51) early works, it features a rich story mode, something unusual at the time for wrestling games.</desc>
		<genre>Sports / Wrestling</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Super Formation Soccer (Japan).zip</path>
		<name>Super Formation Soccer</name>
		<desc>A Satellaview broadcast of Human's Super Famicom version of its soccer franchise, Formation Soccer. The game was praised upon release for its revolutionary top-down view, making great use of the mode 7 zoom and perspective capabilities.</desc>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Super Mahjong Taikai (Japan).zip</path>
		<name>Super Mahjong Taikai</name>
		<desc>The game implements various rules of Japanese mahjong, including nine Dan and Dora. The 21 available computer-controlled opponents have background music and character dialogue that can include puns. The players in the game each start out with $100 and the goal of attaining $10,000. The game modes are Suzumesho mode and mahjong tournament mode. If a player becomes bankrupt or attains $10,000.00, the game starts over with each player having $100 each.
</desc>
		<releasedate>19970629T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Koei</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Mahjong</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Super Ninja-kun (Japan).zip</path>
		<name>Super Ninja-kun</name>
		<desc>A Satellaview-exclusive from Jaleco, Super Ninja-kun is a platformer featuring, funnily enough, ninjas. Unlike other ninja games like Shinobi or Ninja Gaiden, this one adopts a cartoonish artstyle, witch chubby characters running around Kirby-reminiscent levels. The plot appears to be something involving a bad guy who has kidnapped the nice girl, and is flying away at great speed.</desc>
		<releasedate>19970629T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Jaleco</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Super Soukoban (Japan) (Standalone Fix).zip</path>
		<name>Super Soukoban</name>
		<desc>Super Soukoban (or Sokoban) is a puzzle game in which the player must push crates around a maze to their designated storage area, ensuring they do not accidentally push a crate into a position where it cannot be recovered. The intro establishes that the eponymous Sokoban (japanese for warehouse worker), must perform enough box-pushing puzzles to earn enough cash for a flashy new car so that he might finally impress the girl of his dreams. An added wrinkle is that each stage has a fixed move limit, and so the player must not only push the boxes in the right order but do so with maximum efficiency.</desc>
		<developer>Thinking Rabbit</developer>
		<publisher>Pack-In-Video</publisher>
		<genre>Puzzle-Game</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Super Tsumeshougi 1000 (Japan).zip</path>
		<name>Super Tsumeshougi 1000</name>
		<desc>A Satellaview broadcast of a shogi game also released on the Super Famicom. Rather than standard matches, Super Tsumeshogi poses special shogi problems that can be solved with the limited number of pieces offered.</desc>
		<genre>Shougi</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Super Volley II (Japan) (12-10).zip</path>
		<name>Super Volley II</name>
		<desc>Super Volley II (Hyper V-Ball in the US) is a slow-paced volleyball game (figure that out!) which pits your four players against another team of four players. Can you bump, set and spike your way to victory?</desc>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Sutte Hakkun - 98 Fuyu Event Version (Japan).zip</path>
		<name>Sutte Hakkun - 98 Fuyu Event Version</name>
		<desc>Sutte Hakkun BS Version 2 is a platform/puzzle game that was released in 1998 in Japan. As the game's title implies, it is a sequel of sorts to the earlier Sutte Hakkun (Nov. 1997) and Sutte Hakkun Event Version (Oct. 1997). A later titles in the same series, Sutte Hakkun '98 (Dec. 1998) followed a month after the broadcast of Sutte Hakkun Version 2</desc>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Sutte Hakkun - BS Version 2 (Japan) (6-3).zip</path>
		<name>Sutte Hakkun - Bs Version 2</name>
		<desc>Sutte Hakkun BS Version 2 is a platform/puzzle game that was released in 1998 in Japan. As the game's title implies, it is a sequel of sorts to the earlier Sutte Hakkun (Nov. 1997) and Sutte Hakkun Event Version (Oct. 1997). A later titles in the same series, Sutte Hakkun '98 (Dec. 1998) followed a month after the broadcast of Sutte Hakkun Version 2</desc>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Table Game Daisyugo!! Shougi Mahjong Hanafuda (Japan).zip</path>
		<name>Table Game Daisyugo!! Shougi Mahjong Hanafuda</name>
		<desc>Table Game Daishuugou!! ("Table Game Large Set!!) is a board game compilation for the Super Famicom published by Varie with some of the game's programming contracted out to Natsu System. It features five distinct games: mahjong, shogi, "two side" (reversi), and two games played with hanafuda cards. Each game offers the same selection of five AI opponents, each progressively more intelligent.</desc>
		<genre>Hanafuda</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Tamori no Picross (Japan) (8-13) [b].zip</path>
		<name>Tamori No Picross</name>
		<desc>This Super Famicom version of the popular picture crossword game was originally released only in Japan and features hundreds of relaxing yet challenging brainteasers.

Each Picross puzzle consists of a numbered grid of tiles which reveal a picture when correctly chiselled away. In Marios main mode, a wrong move means losing time. However, in the more difficult Wario mode, mistakes are not shown... so be careful! Also, a friend can help by joining in with a second controller.</desc>
		<releasedate>19950613T000000</releasedate>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Puzzle-Game</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Treasure Conflix (Japan) [T-En by Krokodyl v1.1] [req BS-X bios].zip</path>
		<name>Treasure Conflix</name>
		<desc>Half point-and-click adventure, half Mode7 airship action, In treasure Conflix a treasure hunting hero travels the world completing missions which earns the player gold to spend on upgrades for their airship. These power-ups help during missions that progress the story where you're forced to fight hordes of other airships and bosses. This game is exclusive of download service satellaview and never released in cartridge.</desc>
		<releasedate>19960201T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Square</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Tsuri Tarou (Japan).zip</path>
		<name>Tsuri Tarou</name>
		<desc>It plays similarly to Natsume's Legend of the River King series in that the player character must start by catching smaller fish to pay for upgrades to land bigger fish and reach better fishing locales.</desc>
		<developer>Pack-In-Video</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Waiwai Check 3-21 Saihousou + Yuki no Waiwai Kids 3-16 Ban (Japan) [b].zip</path>
		<name>Waiwai Check 3</name>
		<desc>WaiWai Check is a Downloadable Digital Magazine that was broadcast in at least 3 segments for the Satellaview in 1995.</desc>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Wario no Mori - Event Version 2 (Japan).zip</path>
		<name>Wario No Mori - Bakushou Version</name>
		<desc>This puzzle game is a pseudo-sequel to the earlier-broadcasted Wario's Woods and Wario no Mori Futatabi featuring the vocal talents of Japanese comedy duo, Bakushō Mondai.</desc>
		<releasedate>19950401T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Puzzle-Game</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Wario no Mori - Futatabi (Japan) (8-11).zip</path>
		<name>Wario No Mori - Futatabi</name>
		<desc>Wario's Woods is a falling block game where the objective is to clear the playing field of monsters by using bombs, arranging them into rows of matching colors. Unlike other puzzle games such as Tetris, where the player directly manipulates the game pieces, the player controls Toad, who moves around the playing field and arranges them after they have fallen.

This game is a pseudo-sequel to the earlier-broadcast Wario's Woods.</desc>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Puzzle-Game</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Wild Guns (Japan).zip</path>
		<name>Wild Guns</name>
		<desc>Annie &amp; Clint, two gunslingers, arrive at Carson City and get caught up in a gunfight. It's raining bullets and there are explosions everywhere. After an intense battle they enter the saloon where they dispose of every cowboy in sight while redecorating the interior. Our heroes flee the scene by climbing on the roof, but what's that sound? ... it's a HUGE robot!
Wild Guns is a shooter with a western &amp; Sci Fi theme. Gameplay is somewhat similar to the Time Crisis &amp; House of the Dead games, with the exception that the game isn't played from a first-person perspective but from a third-person perspective. You control your on-screen character as well as the aiming crosshair. Select either Clint or Annie and shoot down tons of enemies while dodging bullets and jumping over incoming rockets.
After the Carson City level, the action continues in Desolation Canyon, an ammunition depot, a gold mine and a armored train . Finally there's a showdown with the big bad guy.</desc>
		<releasedate>19950801T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Natsume</developer>
		<publisher>Titus</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Wizardry V - Saika no Chuushin (Japan).zip</path>
		<name>Wizardry 5 - Saika No Chuushin</name>
		<desc>Despite the greatest magic of the ancient High Sages, great floods, earthquakes and famine again pervade the land of Llylgamyn. The great Orb of Llylgamyn, an artifact of remarkable power that has protected the city for ages, is now powerless to halt the scourge.

But now, the Sages have discovered that the hidden reason behind the disasters is more frightening than anyone could have imagined. To save the very world as we know it, you and your party must plunge into the..................Heart of The Maelstrom.</desc>
		<developer>Sir-tech</developer>
		<publisher>ASCII</publisher>
		<genre>Role playing games</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Yoshi no Panepon - BS Ban (Japan) (En,Ja) (7-5).zip</path>
		<name>Yoshi No Panepon - Bs Ban</name>
		<desc>Yoshi no Panepon BS Ban is a Downloadable game for the Satellaview that was broadcast in at least 11 runs between November 3, 1996 and June 30, 2000. Yoshi no Panepon BS Ban is based on the puzzle/casual game of Panel de Pon and is a localization of the English-language release Tetris Attack.</desc>
		<releasedate>19961103T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Intelligent Systems</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Puzzle-Game</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Zelda no Densetsu - Kamigami no Triforce (Japan) (5-21).zip</path>
		<name>Zelda No Densetsu - Kamigami No Triforce</name>
		<desc>Zelda no Densetsu: Kamigami no Triforce is a view-limited Downloadable game for the Satellaview that was broadcast in at least 10 distinct runs between March 2, 1997 and May 29, 2000. Unlike BS Zelda and Inishie no Sekiban, Kamigami no Triforce did not use SoundLink narration or an enhanced orchestral score. Apart from its physical form and the addition of Satellaview headers to the code, the game is identical to the hardware version released for the Super Famicom on November 21, 1991.</desc>
		<releasedate>19950806T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>St. GIGA</publisher>
		<genre>Action / Adventure</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Super Nazo Puyo Tsuu - Rulue no Tetsuwan Hanjouki (Japan).zip</path>
		<name>Super Puyo Puyo Tsuu</name>
		<desc>A falling block game in which the goal is the combine four or more blocks of the same color which then disappear. The remain blocks will fall down and can produce combos which can cause special blocks (can only be destroyed by eliminating adjunct blocks) to appear at the enemies field.

This game includes a story mode, in which Arle (the main character) fights against computer enemies, a vs player mode, a four player mode (SNES only), and an endless mode (SNES only).</desc>
		<releasedate>19951208T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Compile</developer>
		<publisher>Compile</publisher>
		<genre>Puzzle-Game</genre>
		<players>1-4</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Bakushow Mondai no Totsugeki! Star Pirates - Dai-1-wa (Japan) (SoundLink).zip</path>
		<name>Bakushow Mondai No Totsugeki! Star Pirates -</name>
		<desc>Bakusho Mondai no Totsugeki! StarPirates is a Downloadable 4-part Soundlink game for the Satellaview that was broadcast in at least 2 distinct runs between June 22, 1997 and November 29, 1997. The game features voice narration by the Japanese comedy duo, Bakushō Mondai.</desc>
		<releasedate>19970622T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>St.GIGA</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Various</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Bakushow Mondai no Totsugeki! Star Pirates - Dai-3-wa (Japan) (SoundLink).zip</path>
		<name>Bakushow Mondai No Totsugeki! Star Pirates -</name>
		<desc>Bakusho Mondai no Totsugeki! StarPirates is a Downloadable 4-part Soundlink game for the Satellaview that was broadcast in at least 2 distinct runs between June 22, 1997 and November 29, 1997. The game features voice narration by the Japanese comedy duo, Bakushō Mondai.</desc>
		<releasedate>19970622T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>St.GIGA</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Various</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./BS Shin Onigashima - Dai-1-wa (Japan) (SoundLink).zip</path>
		<name>Bs Shin Onigashima</name>
		<desc>BS Shin Onigashima is a Downloadable 4-part Soundlink game for the Satellaview that was broadcast in at least 2 distinct runs between September 29, 1996 and January 31, 1996. It was a remake sequel to the earlier Shin Onigashima. The major difference between the two games relate to the SoundLink elements that were introduced for the Satellaview broadcasts. The plot of BS Shin Onigashima comes from the original Shin Onigashima, however it is presented from the perspective of the three animal helpers (dog, monkey, and pheasant) who join the heroes as NPCs during the original game. The game was divided into 4 chapters which were retained for the later Nintendo Power and SFC remake. BS Shin Onigashima makes use of an expanded orchestral score that was broadcast via satellite radio, and in-game narration in the voice of the main-character, Ittaisan, was broadcast via SoundLink between chapters to advance the storyline. The game employs command menu gameplay just as in Shin Onigashima, however in BS Shin Onigashima the option to change character mid-game was removed. Other differences included the addition of platform-style action scenes, and time limits associated with making certain commands.</desc>
		<releasedate>19960929T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>St.GIGA</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./BS Shin Onigashima - Dai-2-wa (Japan) (SoundLink).zip</path>
		<name>Bs Shin Onigashima</name>
		<desc>BS Shin Onigashima is a Downloadable 4-part Soundlink game for the Satellaview that was broadcast in at least 2 distinct runs between September 29, 1996 and January 31, 1996. It was a remake sequel to the earlier Shin Onigashima. The major difference between the two games relate to the SoundLink elements that were introduced for the Satellaview broadcasts. The plot of BS Shin Onigashima comes from the original Shin Onigashima, however it is presented from the perspective of the three animal helpers (dog, monkey, and pheasant) who join the heroes as NPCs during the original game. The game was divided into 4 chapters which were retained for the later Nintendo Power and SFC remake. BS Shin Onigashima makes use of an expanded orchestral score that was broadcast via satellite radio, and in-game narration in the voice of the main-character, Ittaisan, was broadcast via SoundLink between chapters to advance the storyline. The game employs command menu gameplay just as in Shin Onigashima, however in BS Shin Onigashima the option to change character mid-game was removed. Other differences included the addition of platform-style action scenes, and time limits associated with making certain commands.</desc>
		<releasedate>19960929T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>St.GIGA</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./BS Shin Onigashima - Dai-3-wa (Japan) (1-27) (SoundLink).zip</path>
		<name>Bs Shin Onigashima</name>
		<desc>BS Shin Onigashima is a Downloadable 4-part Soundlink game for the Satellaview that was broadcast in at least 2 distinct runs between September 29, 1996 and January 31, 1996. It was a remake sequel to the earlier Shin Onigashima. The major difference between the two games relate to the SoundLink elements that were introduced for the Satellaview broadcasts. The plot of BS Shin Onigashima comes from the original Shin Onigashima, however it is presented from the perspective of the three animal helpers (dog, monkey, and pheasant) who join the heroes as NPCs during the original game. The game was divided into 4 chapters which were retained for the later Nintendo Power and SFC remake. BS Shin Onigashima makes use of an expanded orchestral score that was broadcast via satellite radio, and in-game narration in the voice of the main-character, Ittaisan, was broadcast via SoundLink between chapters to advance the storyline. The game employs command menu gameplay just as in Shin Onigashima, however in BS Shin Onigashima the option to change character mid-game was removed. Other differences included the addition of platform-style action scenes, and time limits associated with making certain commands.</desc>
		<releasedate>19960929T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>St.GIGA</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./BS Shin Onigashima - Dai-4-wa (Japan) (2-1) (SoundLink).zip</path>
		<name>Bs Shin Onigashima</name>
		<desc>BS Shin Onigashima is a Downloadable 4-part Soundlink game for the Satellaview that was broadcast in at least 2 distinct runs between September 29, 1996 and January 31, 1996. It was a remake sequel to the earlier Shin Onigashima. The major difference between the two games relate to the SoundLink elements that were introduced for the Satellaview broadcasts. The plot of BS Shin Onigashima comes from the original Shin Onigashima, however it is presented from the perspective of the three animal helpers (dog, monkey, and pheasant) who join the heroes as NPCs during the original game. The game was divided into 4 chapters which were retained for the later Nintendo Power and SFC remake. BS Shin Onigashima makes use of an expanded orchestral score that was broadcast via satellite radio, and in-game narration in the voice of the main-character, Ittaisan, was broadcast via SoundLink between chapters to advance the storyline. The game employs command menu gameplay just as in Shin Onigashima, however in BS Shin Onigashima the option to change character mid-game was removed. Other differences included the addition of platform-style action scenes, and time limits associated with making certain commands.</desc>
		<releasedate>19960929T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>St.GIGA</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./BS Zelda no Densetsu - Dai-1-wa (Japan) (Rerun) (SoundLink).zip</path>
		<name>Bs Zelda No Densetsu</name>
		<desc>BS Zelda no Densetsu is a Downloadable 4-part Soundlink game for the Satellaview that was broadcast in at least 5 distinct runs between August 6, 1995 and January 4, 1997. A program called BS Zelda no Asobikata was also broadcast in the half-hour prior to broadcasts of BS Zelda. This program seems to have been a radio tutorial teaching players how to play BS Zelda. The gameplay draws directly from The Legend of Zelda. The plot of BS Zelda varies considerably from the plot of the original due in great part to the fact that the hero of the game is not Link (the hero of The Legend of Zelda). Instead, BS Zelda is closely associated with the story presented in the BS-X interface cartridge, with the Hero of Light actually representing the BS-X avatar according the the BS Zelda storyline. Another major factor in the plot of BS Zelda is the fact that the story is most closely related to the story given in The Legend of Zelda: A Link to the Past. Both plots take up after the conclusion of Kamigami no Triforce - a fact that for Inishie no Sekiban produces one of the many plot inconsistencies/contradictions for which the series has become noted.</desc>
		<releasedate>19950806T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Action / Adventure</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./BS Zelda no Densetsu - Dai-4-wa (Japan) (Rerun) (SoundLink).zip</path>
		<name>Bs Zelda No Densetsu</name>
		<desc>BS Zelda no Densetsu is a Downloadable 4-part Soundlink game for the Satellaview that was broadcast in at least 5 distinct runs between August 6, 1995 and January 4, 1997. A program called BS Zelda no Asobikata was also broadcast in the half-hour prior to broadcasts of BS Zelda. This program seems to have been a radio tutorial teaching players how to play BS Zelda. The gameplay draws directly from The Legend of Zelda. The plot of BS Zelda varies considerably from the plot of the original due in great part to the fact that the hero of the game is not Link (the hero of The Legend of Zelda). Instead, BS Zelda is closely associated with the story presented in the BS-X interface cartridge, with the Hero of Light actually representing the BS-X avatar according the the BS Zelda storyline. Another major factor in the plot of BS Zelda is the fact that the story is most closely related to the story given in The Legend of Zelda: A Link to the Past. Both plots take up after the conclusion of Kamigami no Triforce - a fact that for Inishie no Sekiban produces one of the many plot inconsistencies/contradictions for which the series has become noted.</desc>
		<releasedate>19950806T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Action / Adventure</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Konae-chan no Dokidoki Penguin Kazoku - Event-ban (Japan) (1-7).zip</path>
		<name>Konae-chan No Dokidoki Penguin Kazoku</name>
		<desc>Konae-chan no DokiDoki Pengin Kazoku is a Downloadable Event Game developed by Pax Softnica for the Satellaview. It stars Konae and was distributed as a tie in to the Radio Program "If Tomorrow Comes...".</desc>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Kouryaku Casino Bar Nichiyoubi - Roulette (Japan) [b].zip</path>
		<name>Kouryaku Casino Bar Nichiyoubi - Roulette  G</name>
		<desc>A casino game, split into two Satellaview broadcasts. This is the Roulette version of the game.</desc>
		<genre>Casino / Cards</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Ryouma de Yuku - Kanaderu Score (6-30) + Ryouma de Yuku - Kanaderu Score (8-4) (Japan) (Data Pack) [b].zip</path>
		<name>Ryouma De Yuku</name>
		<desc>A role-playing game that is a parody of “Ryōma ga Yuku”, which seems to be a highly renowned piece of japanese literature, using RPG Tsukuru (RPG Maker) and written by Hikari Ōta of the Bakushō Mondai comedy duo.</desc>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Sound Novel Tsukuru Data - Okirakukouza (Japan) (Data Pack) [b].zip</path>
		<name>Sound Novel Tsukuru</name>
		<desc>Sound Novel Tsukuru is a Super Famicom graphic novel game where players can either read or create interactive fiction on their own console systems. Stories can be saved either on a battery or through a satellite connection.

The game comes with a previously created graphic novel about exploring an old house. Due to the limitations in the game's engine, it can only show shadows of non-player characters that the player meets on his journey. Settings can range from a modern day train to a rural house and even wilderness can be included in various stages of wildness.</desc>
		<releasedate>19960531T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Success</developer>
		<publisher>ASCII Corporation</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Waiwai Check 3-7 Gou + Waiwai Check 3-7 Gou + Waiwai Check 3-14 Gou (Japan) [b].zip</path>
		<name>Waiwai Check 3</name>
		<desc>WaiWai Check is a Downloadable Digital Magazine that was broadcast in at least 3 segments for the Satellaview in 1995.</desc>
	</game>
</gameList>
