<?xml version="1.0"?>
<alternativeEmulator>
	<label>Dolphin (Standalone)</label>
</alternativeEmulator>
<gameList>
	<game>
		<path>./Disaster - Day of Crisis (Europe) (En,Fr,De,Es,It).nkit.gcz</path>
		<name>Disaster: Day of Crisis</name>
		<desc>It had started as any other day for Raymond Bryce... but a simple phone call was to change everything... Forced to leave the tranquillity of his office, this ex-Marine was asked to join a team whose mission was to thwart a terrorist cell desperate to steal a nuclear warhead. But nothing was to go according to plan, and the situation took a frightening turn for the worse. Now the survival of the entire human race hangs in the balance over the next 24 hours... You'll guide Ray through a day in hell: volcanic eruptions, tsunamis, earthquakes, floods and hurricanes... not to mention a vengeance-hungry terrorist organisation with the means to cause an unprecedented cataclysm.</desc>
		<releasedate>20080925T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Monolith Software</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Fire Emblem - Radiant Dawn (USA) (Rev 1).nkit.gcz</path>
		<name>Fire Emblem: Radiant Dawn</name>
		<desc>The sequel to 2005 s Path of Radiance and the tenth game in the Fire Emblem series, Radiant Dawn takes place three years after the defeat of the Daein kingdom by Crimea.

Unlike other Wii games, the main method of control is either through the classic controller or GameCube controller, since the action is wholly turn-based tactical combat, largely the same as the previous nine games. The game consists of 44 chapters and uses the same engine as Path of Radiance. There are three new weapon and magic types: Knife, Dark Magic and Strike.

The player must lead a band of heroes against the Begnion Empire s oppression of the defeated Daein, along with help from many of the heroes from Path of Radiance. The members of the Dawn group are the main heroes of the game, with a major role for Sothe, who was a child thief from the previous Fire Emblem game.</desc>
		<releasedate>20071105T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Intelligent Systems</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Role playing games</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Kirby's Epic Yarn (USA) (En,Fr,Es).nkit.gcz</path>
		<name>Kirby's Epic Yarn</name>
		<desc>While walking through Dream Land, Kirby discovers a tomato and decides to eat it. Yin-Yarn, the evil sorceror who possessed the tomato (revealed to be a Metamato), appears and magically banishes Kirby into Patch Land, a world completely made of fabric, via the sock carried around his neck. In Patch Land, Kirby s body transforms into yarn, rendering his power to inhale useless. Instead, Kirby is granted the ability to transform by the magic of the Metamato, which he uses to rescue a boy being attacked by a monster. The boy, named Prince Fluff, explains that Yin-Yarn has separated Patch Land into pieces, which was tied together by magic yarn. Kirby decides to help Prince Fluff collect all seven pieces of the yarn and restore Patch Land.

Meanwhile, Yin-Yarn captures King Dedede and Meta Knight and places them under his control. Kirby is forced to fight Dedede and Meta Knight after they ambush him in Patch Land. When Kirby and Prince Fluff finally collect all the Magic Yarn, Meta Knight, no longer under the sorceror s influence, informs Kirby that Yin-Yarn is turning Dream Land into fabric. Prince Fluff produces the second sock, its magic fully restored, and uses it to transport Kirby and himself to Dream Land; now completely made of yarn. Kirby confronts and defeats Yin-Yarn, breaking the spell and returning Dream Land and himself back to normal. Prince Fluff parts with Kirby, stating that he can visit Patch Land anytime via Yin-Yarn s magic sock.</desc>
		<releasedate>20101017T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Good-Feel</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Metroid - Other M (USA) (En,Fr,Es) (Rev 1).nkit.gcz</path>
		<name>Metroid: Other M</name>
		<desc>Metroid: Other M is reminiscent of 2-D side-scrollers, but players can switch the perspective into 3-D at any time as they explore the twisting passages of a derelict space station and delve deep into a cinematic, never-before-told story of bounty hunter Samus Aran's past.

This new approach uses a new control scheme in which players use the Wii Remote controller held sideways to battle enemies and navigate the expansive, gorgeous environments in classic Metroid fashion, then aim at the screen with the Wii Remote pointer to blast foes in first-person and hunt the world for clues and hidden passages.</desc>
		<releasedate>20100831T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Team Ninja</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Sonic Colors (USA) (En,Ja,Fr,De,Es,It).nkit.gcz</path>
		<name>Sonic Colors</name>
		<desc>A brand new high speed action adventure in which Sonic the Hedgehog races through incredible theme park inspired worlds to rescue a colourful alien race from the clutches of Dr Eggman. An extraordinary amusement park has been seen orbiting around the home planet of Sonic the Hedgehog, and rumours are spreading that an alien race of Wisps, who have a unique colourful energy, are being held captive there by the evil Dr Eggman. Soon after arriving at the amusement park Sonic discovers he is able to use these mysterious alien forces to help the Wisps escape! Sonic Colours for the Wii seamlessly combines both 3D and classic 2D game play perspectives.</desc>
		<releasedate>20101112T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Sonic Team</developer>
		<publisher>SEGA</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Super Mario Galaxy (USA) (En,Fr,Es).nkit.gcz</path>
		<name>Super Mario Galaxy</name>
		<desc>Mario takes to the skies and beyond in another outing to save the Princess. As the Mushroom Kingdom prepares to celebrate the arrival of a comet that appears in the skies every hundred years, Princess Peach sends Mario an invitation to attend. As Mario arrives, Bowser and minions attack the Kingdom and once again kidnap the Princess... and her entire castle. Mario gives chase but is lost as the ship leaves the atmosphere and ends up on a space station built on the visiting comet overseen by the mysterious Rosalina. It's up to Mario to brave new galaxies, find the elusive Power Stars, and bring his friends home.

Super Mario Galaxy plays similarly to Super Mario 64, as Mario explores his latest 3D world defying gravity, crossing various terrains, and even running upside down across the planet surfaces. Bouncing from planet to planet, Mario must collect Star Bits and coins, using his usual jump attacks and spins (now controlled with movement from the Wii Remote). The Wii Remote is also used to collect out of reach Star Bits and also can be controlled by a second player.

In addition, Mario can find new suits (similar to Super Mario Bros. 3) that give him the ability to turn into the ghostly Boo Mario, the high-flying Bee Mario, launch fireballs as Fire Mario and skate across frozen lakes as Ice Mario. New challenges also await Mario including ray surfing, balancing on a high-speed ball, floating inside bubbles, and other challenges in his quest to get all 120 stars. Even Luigi lends a hand in the search, making valuable contributions to the adventure.

Players can also take a snapshot of the worlds they've completed along with their best record times and send them to their friends via Wi-Fi.</desc>
		<releasedate>20071112T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo EAD</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Super Mario Galaxy 2 (USA) (En,Fr,Es).nkit.gcz</path>
		<name>Super Mario Galaxy 2</name>
		<desc>Mario returns to the stars as the everlasting villain Bowser has kidnapped Princess Peach once more. This time while she was baking a cake...
Once again Mario is determined to fight Bowser and free Princess Peach. 

The basic goal of each level is to collect the golden star. The environment is still a mixture of standard Mario stages and miniature planetoids with their own orbital gravity. Throughout the game the perspective is changed at some stages, switching from 3D to 2D. The 2D part is similar to New Super Mario Bros. Wii.

Super Mario Galaxy 2 features a further improved experience over its predecessor, with two new suits for Mario and the return of Yoshi. Mario's first new suit is the Cloud Suit, which allows him to create three safe but temporary platforms. The second new suite is the Rock Suit. While wearing it, Mario can roll up into a ball which will be necessary to complete some challenges.
For the first time in the franchise Yoshi will be able to wear a suit as well. By finding it, he will become "Light Yoshi" that allows him to see certain platforms that are otherwise invisible.

Like in the original Super Mario Galaxy a second player can join the experience by pointing the Wii Remote on the screen to collect coins. What is new to the game however, is that the second player now also can collect items that are out of the reach of Mario.

To aid the entry for people new to the franchise, the game features an introduction to the game play and controls of the game.</desc>
		<releasedate>20100523T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo EAD</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Super Paper Mario (USA) (Rev 2).nkit.gcz</path>
		<name>Super Paper Mario</name>
		<desc>In this action-platformer, Bowser and Peach find themselves at the wedding altar, forced into marriage by the evil Count Bleck. With this union, a void will engulf the entire universe as foretold by the book, the Dark Prognosticus. Before Luigi can stop Count Bleck, the villain escapes with an item known as the Chaos Heart. However, there is another book, called the Light Prognosticus, which can counteract the Dark Prognosticus. The Light Prognosticus foretells of a hero dressed in overalls. This hero is believed to possess the power to stop certain destruction of the universe.

Mario, joined by Peach, Bowser, and a new group of friends, must travel through eight worlds in search of Pure Hearts. Each character has a special ability, which can help the player solve the game's many puzzles. Mario can flip between the second and third dimensions in order to find items, secret pathways, and pound enemies. Peach can use her parasol to float long distances and to defend against enemy attacks. Bowser uses his fire breath to light things and to fry enemies.

Super Paper Mario does not fully depart from its RPG roots. For instance Mario and friends receive points from baddies. These points allow Mario and company to level up. Items can also be used to attack enemies or gain lives. Players collect coins to pay for more items.

Players can shake the Wii remote after jumping on bad guys but before hitting the ground to gain extra experience points. Players use Tippi, a Pixl, allowing them to point the remote at the screen to find secrets. Other Pixls, who help in other ways, can be found along the way. Pixls besides Tippi can be used by pressing the 1 button.</desc>
		<releasedate>20070409T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Intelligent Systems</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Role playing games</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Tatsunoko vs. Capcom - Ultimate All-Stars (USA).nkit.gcz</path>
		<name>Tatsunoko vs. Capcom: Ultimate All-Stars</name>
		<desc>From Capcom's 30-year history comes characters like Ryu and Chun-Li from the Street Fighter series, Morrigan from Darkstalkers and company mascot Mega Man Volnutt from Mega Man Legends. Tatsunoko's near half-century of Japanese animation excellence is represented by the likes of Ken the Eagle and Jun the Swan from the Science Ninja Team Gatchaman anime (known in Europe as Battle of the Planets or G-Force), cybernetic warrior Casshan and comedic action hero Yatterman No. 1. All together, there are more than 20 colourful combatants to choose from in order to form the ultimate tag team combination. Gameplay will instantly set fighting game fans' fingers twitching, combining elements from Capcom games like Street Fighter and previous entries in the VS series, TATSUNOKO VS. CAPCOM ULTIMATE ALL-STARS is a fun fighting game designed for all levels of players.</desc>
		<releasedate>20081211T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Fight</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Zack &amp; Wiki - Quest for Barbaros' Treasure (USA).nkit.gcz</path>
		<name>Zack &amp; Wiki: Quest for Barbaros Treasure</name>
		<desc>Zack is a new pirate on a quest to become the greatest pirate ever. In this puzzle adventure game he and his magical monkey sidekick search for treasure as they help the skeleton of the legendary pirate Barbaros.

Zack &amp; Wiki: Quest for Barbaros  Treasure is presented as a series of stages where the player directs Zack to perform a number of actions to let him collect the treasure. The player must deduce what actions will have the desired effect without triggering traps or attracting the attention of the enemies. Using most of the tools causes the game to switch to a first-person point of view, and the player is expected to hold and manipulate the Wii remote as if it were the item on the screen.</desc>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Metroid Prime 3 - Corruption (USA).nkit.gcz</path>
		<name>Metroid Prime 3: Corruption</name>
		<desc>If you think you knew what it felt like to be the bounty hunter behind the visor, think again. Take aim at evil with Nintendo's revolutionary controller.

Players control Samus by moving with the Nunchuk controller and aiming with the pointer, allowing for a level of immersion unlike anything they have ever experienced. Through the eyes of Samus, players experience a quantum leap in first-person control as they wield the Wii Remote, the ultimate device for the first-person shooter genre.
Samus will employ well-known power-ups like the Grapple Beam and Morph Ball, as well as a bunch of new surprises, to help her survive her coming trials.</desc>
		<releasedate>20080306T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Retro Studios</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<altemulator>PrimeHack (Standalone)</altemulator>
	</game>
</gameList>
