<?xml version="1.0"?>
<alternativeEmulator>
	<label>FinalBurn Neo</label>
</alternativeEmulator>
<gameList>
	<game>
		<path>./jojoba.zip</path>
		<name>Jojo's Bizarre Adventure</name>
		<desc>Based on the Japanese manga/animé of the same name, JoJo's Bizarre Adventure is a 2D fighting game from Capcom. Take on the role of one of 18 characters and compete with your friends or take on the role of Jotaro "JoJo" Kujo and his friends in the SUper Story Mode as they race to defeat the evil vampire, Dio Brando, and save the world!</desc>
		<releasedate>19990101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Fight / Versus</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./jojo.zip</path>
		<name>JoJo's Venture</name>
		<desc>JoJo's Venture is a 2D fighting game based off of the hit Japanese manga series JoJo's Bizarre Adventure (famous for over-the-top violence, an intricate plot, and numerous Western rock music references).</desc>
		<releasedate>19980101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Fight / Versus</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./redearth.zip</path>
		<name>Red Earth</name>
		<desc>Red Earth take place in the year 1999 of an alternate Earth, follow the adventures of four heroes as they take on an army of mythical monsters unleashed by Scion to bring about the destruction of the world. Take your pick from Leo the Lion King, Mai-Ling the Martial artist, Tessa the Witch, or Kenji the Ninja as they fight their way across the globe in order to defeat Scion the iron giant.</desc>
		<releasedate>19960101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Fight</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./sfiii2.zip</path>
		<name>Street Fighter III 2nd Impact : Giant Attack</name>
		<desc>Street Fighter III - 2nd Impact: Giant Attack is the sequel to "Street Fighter III - New Generation". Joining the existing Street Fighter III cast are Hugo, Urien and recurring character Akuma (Gouki in the Japanese version). Other improvements include a speed increase, new moves and several damage-related tweaks.</desc>
		<releasedate>19970101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Fight</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./sfiii3.zip</path>
		<name>Street Fighter III 3rd Strike : Fight for the Future</name>
		<desc>3rd Strike increased the character roster by adding five new characters, notably including the legendary Chun-Li. New characters Remy, Makoto, Q, and Twelve were also added, bringing the total number of playable fighters to twenty. Also re-introduced was the fan-favourite 'Destroy the Car' bonus stage. 

One of the new gameplay mechanics introduced in "3rd Strike" is the Guard Parry, also known as the 'Red Parry', which allows players to parry during guard stun, providing the timing is correct. Another new feature is after-match player evaluations in which the winner of a two-person match is graded in Offense, Defence, Tech and Extra. In single-player Arcade mode the player will always be evaluated, even in event of a loss. The grades range from E (lowest) to MSF, or Master Street Fighter (highest).</desc>
		<releasedate>19990101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Fight</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./sfiii.zip</path>
		<name>Street Fighter III : New Generation</name>
		<desc>A New Generation of Street Fighters! Features larger characters sprites than previous Street Fighter games with the smoothest, most detailed 2-D animation ever made at the time of its release, a level of quality that is yet to be matched by any other 2-D game outside of the Street Fighter III series as of 2004; some complain that too many things are animated and each animation contains too many frames, slowing down the pace of the game.</desc>
		<releasedate>19970101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Fight</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
</gameList>
