<?xml version="1.0"?>
<gameList>
	<game>
		<path>./Addams Family, The (USA).chd</path>
		<name>The Addams Family</name>
		<desc>Based on the Addams Family movie, this game is quite different from the other Addams Family variants. The player is cast in the role of Tully Alford, the crooked lawyer of the Addams family. He finds out that somewhere in the family mansion, a great treasure is stored in a vault. He decides to venture into the mansion and retrieve the treasure. Naturally, this is going to be anything but easy, as the insane Addams family members and a legion of ghosts and monsters are there to make sure the lawyer fails...

Like most other Addams Family incarnations, this is a side-scrolling action game. Tully Alford's only weapon is an umbrella that fires energy shots at enemies. Tully can also jump and duck to avoid enemy blows. The game world consists of a "hub" area, the hall of Addams Family mansion, and many rooms, most of which are locked in the beginning of the game. The gameplay consists mainly of exploring the accessible rooms and collecting keys that are needed to open other doors in the process. Some of the rooms contain treasure and power-ups, while others are infested by monsters or require the player to defeat a boss enemy in order to advance.</desc>
		<releasedate>19910101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>ICOM Simulations</developer>
		<publisher>NEC</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Advanced V.G. (Japan).chd</path>
		<name>Advanced V.g.</name>
		<desc>The story of Advanced V.G. follows a similar template as those of the previous  Variable Geo games: the strongest young women in the country hold a tournament, which is sponsored by various restaurant chains, which in turn ask the competing girls to pose as waitresses working in said restaurants, for promotional purposes. The girls of the Jahana group who starred in the previous games return, with the new main protagonist being the young martial artist Yuka Takeuchi, who has been training in a secluded forest area before joining the competition. 

Like its predecessors, Advanced V.G. is a fighting game, with the basic "kick" and "punch" moves, while the various special attacks are executed by pressing combinations of buttons. There are three modes in the game, "Normal", "Vs.", and "Story". The normal mode is basically training matches between the player character and an AI-controlled girl. Vs. mode allows two-player mode, as well as demo "computer vs. computer" gameplay, with the possibility to choose any of the stages. Any of the nine heroines is available as a playable character in these modes (Yuka Takeuchi, Chiho Masuda, Jun Kubota, Manami Kusunoki. Kaori Yanase, Reimi Jahana, Satomi Yajima, Ayako Y?ki, and Erina Goldsmith). The story mode, on the other hand, allows the player to control Yuka Takeuchi only, and follow her story. Cut scenes advance the story between matches. 

The SNES received a stripped-down version, Super V.G., without the Story Mode and all explicit hentai elements. Hybrids (pair of bosses in Advanced V.G.) were also removed.</desc>
		<releasedate>19940722T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>GIGA</developer>
		<publisher>Technical Group Laboratory</publisher>
		<genre>Fight / 2D</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Ai Chou Aniki (Japan) (SADS).chd</path>
		<name>Ai Cho Aniki</name>
		<desc>The sequel to the first Cho Aniki (Super Big Brother) game, this is very Japanese in its bizarreness. It's a shoot ?em up, with the player taking the role of an almost nude muscle-man (Adon) or his brother (Samson) in a 2 player game. Their main weapon is a ball of energy that grows over a hole in their heads and shoots out towards any advancing enemies. Other, more powerful shots are achieved by a combination of back-forward-fire, down-up-fire etc on the pad. Through the levels you will encounter all manner of nasties out to get you, but you are aided by a woman in blue that flies around and drops power-ups conveniently for you. Also, levels vary from the standard left-to-right to vertically scrolling.</desc>
		<releasedate>19950224T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Masaya Games</developer>
		<publisher>NCS Corporation</publisher>
		<genre>Shoot'em Up</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Asuka 120% Maxima - Burning Fest. Maxima (Japan).chd</path>
		<name>Asuka 120% Maxima Burning Fest</name>
		<desc>Welcome to the "Ryouran Private School for Women" which educates the daughters of the upper echelons of society. Here, the high class clubs annually hold a martial arts tournament: the "Club Rivalry Budget Contest Mega Fight." Each character employs a different fighting style; techniques are unique to each club.</desc>
		<releasedate>19950728T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Fill in Café</developer>
		<publisher>NEC</publisher>
		<genre>Beat'em Up</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Beyond Shadowgate (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Beyond Shadowgate</name>
		<desc>This is a sequel to the adventure game Shadowgate. You control Prince Eric, the descendant of the hero of the first game. You return to your home country, only to discover that your father was murdered. You should become the new king, but the minister of the late king has other plans, frames you for killing your own father, and throws you into jail, where your adventure begins.

Unlike the first Shadowgate, this is a platform game - not an action game, but a classical point-and-click adventure viewed from a platform perspective. You can move your hero around, examine, manipulate, and take objects. You can also duck and have a "punch" command. Find the correct solutions to the game's puzzles, otherwise a gruesome death awaits you!</desc>
		<releasedate>19930101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Turbo Technologies, Inc.</developer>
		<publisher>ICOM Simulations</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Bishoujo Senshi Sailor Moon (T-En + Honorifics).chd</path>
		<name>Bishoujo Senshi Sailor Moon</name>
		<desc>Sailor Moon was the title of a video game released in Japan in 1994 for the PC-Engine console. The game was an interactive story, including characters and voice actors from the anime as well as some original characters.
The songs "Koisuru Otome wa Makenai" and "Onaji Hoshi ni Umareta Futari Dakara" were written specifically for this game. A shortened version of each song appeared in the game, while full versions were available on the single "Sailor Moon: PC Engine Theme Songs".</desc>
		<releasedate>19940805T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Banpresto</developer>
		<publisher>Banpresto</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Bonk III - Bonk's Big Adventure (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Bonk III : Bonk's Big Adventure</name>
		<desc>Bonk's Big Adventure is the third instalment in the side-scrolling platformer series. As in previous games, the player assumes the role of a caveman named Bonk who headbutts his way through various enemies in order to defeat King Drool. Familiar moves include swinging on trees, bouncing off walls, breaking blocks and climbing walls with his teeth. Compared to the previous games, he walks and moves a little faster.</desc>
		<releasedate>19930101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Hudson</developer>
		<publisher>Turbo Technologies, Inc.</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Castlevania - Rondo of Blood (T-En + Arranged Audio).chd</path>
		<name>Akumajou Dracula X - Chi No Rondo</name>
		<desc>In the days of old, the people thrived on peace and prosperity. Indeed, fears of unrest were not among their thoughts...

But, ever-present, beneath the veneer of tranquility, evil lurks. Evil, which spurns prosperity and disdains peace.

Gather they did, those who wished to summon the powers of darkness and cleanse the decadence of the world. And, with smiling countenance, they anxiously awaited the coming of their era.

A hundred years had past, and he was resurrected. Able to become bat, wolf, or mist at will, he lived in the night. He drank the blood of young maidens and lived an eternal life. The lord of Castlevania, the god of evil, Count Dracula was reborn.</desc>
		<releasedate>19931029T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Konami</developer>
		<publisher>Konami</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Chiki Chiki Boys (Japan).chd</path>
		<name>Chiki Chiki Boys</name>
		<desc>This platform-based action game is set in the land of Alurea. The idyllic life of the Alurean people was shattered when the King is killed by a dragon, and a range of nasties inhabit the lands. Fortunately his twin sons have come to the rescue, and you must take control of one or the other to put the world right.

The boys have differing skills - one is more skilled in sword-fighting (which you are always armed with), the other in magic (available in limited amounts on each level). You collect coins as the game goes on, and spend these in the shop on extra magic, extra lives and enhanced swords.

There are 3 levels on offer - Earth, The Heavens and The Sea, and these can be tackled in any order. The first is straight platform action, the second involves jumping across clouds, and the third sees your characters swim. After those are completed, you must venture into the Monster Castle and finally slay the dragon.</desc>
		<releasedate>19940715T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>NEC</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Chou Aniki (Japan) (FAAT, FACT).chd</path>
		<name>Cho Aniki - Super Big Brothers</name>
		<desc>The odd world in this shooter made for quite the conversation piece in its day. Players control either Idaten or Benten, celestial warriors out to bring an end to the tyrannical rule of the emperor of Planet Builder, who holds muscular prowess to be the supreme virtue of the universe. Aided by able-bodied muscle-head options Adon and Samson, they must battle to defeat the emperors army across five stages. Use the buttons to fire away and lay into the Builder forces! Power up your character and options with protein from defeated enemies to have them "bulk up" with a yell, and take their macho battle to the next level!</desc>
		<releasedate>19921225T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Masaya Games</developer>
		<publisher>NCS Corporation</publisher>
		<genre>Shoot'em Up</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Cosmic Fantasy 2 (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Cosmic Fantasy 2</name>
		<desc>Van is a young boy who lives on the planet Idea, a place where technology has not yet reached a high level. One day his sweetheart Laura gets kidnapped by an unknown villain. Van soon discovers that Laura possesses mysterious powers that may grant immortality to the one who marries her. That is exactly what the evil wizard Galam has in mind. Van sets off to rescue Laura, on a quest that involves intergalactic journeys and travel through time.

Cosmic Fantasy 2 is a sequel to Cosmic Fantasy: B?ken Sh?nen Yuu, and the only installment in the series to have been released in the West. Though initially not directly related to its predecessor story-wise, the game features several common characters and themes. 

Like the previous game, it is a Japanese-style RPG set in a mixed sci-fi and medieval world. The game has random enemy encounters and simple turn-based combat mechanics. Player-controlled characters can learn and use various offensive and healing spells; however, enemies are restricted to physical attacks. Characters join and leave the party frequently, as dictated by the plot; the party may contain up to four active combatants. Story progression and overworld exploration is linear; dungeons are usually fairly complex and maze-like. Full-screen anime-style cutscenes with voice-overs advance the story of the game.</desc>
		<releasedate>19920609T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Shin-Nihon Laser Soft</developer>
		<publisher>Working Designs</publisher>
		<genre>Role playing games</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Death Bringer - The Knight of Darkness (Japan).chd</path>
		<name>Death Bringer - The Knight Of Darkness</name>
		<desc>A powerful wizard, yearning for even more power, has found a sacred book that granted him command over armies of demons and men. Possessed by the desire to conquer and to destroy, he orders his armies to set cities on fire, massacring the citizens. But one nameless hero, the protagonist of this game, has to stand up against the evil. Leaving Soron, his home village, the hero embarks on a journey to find companions and to face together the forces of darkness.
Despite being a Japanese game, Death Bringer is more similar to Western RPGs of the time than to their Japanese counterparts, even though it has anime-style character graphics. It is less event-oriented than Japanese games and focuses on exploration. The gameplay is somewhat similar to Pandora's RPG of the same name, even though the two games are unrelated. Both friendly and hostile areas are pseudo-3D, maze-like environments, like in Bard's Tale games</desc>
		<releasedate>19900427T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Renovation Products</developer>
		<publisher>Telenet</publisher>
		<genre>Role playing games</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Doukyuusei (Japan) (Rev 4).chd</path>
		<name>Doukyuusei</name>
		<desc>In Doukyuusei, the player takes on the role of a schoolboy in a Japanese town. His parents have just moved into a large mansion in a good neighbourhood. The boy has to go to his new school, but his mind is preoccupied with just one subject: pretty girls. Instead of studying seriously, Takurou decides to explore the town and learn more about its female inhabitants.
Doukyuusei is more interactive than most other Japanese adventure games, using the point-and-click interface (with contextual icons for talking, touching, etc.) and offering free navigation up and down through the city and the school building. The hero can enter restaurants, shops, cafés and more. You can also take a train to another part of the city to explore.</desc>
		<releasedate>19951123T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Elf Corporation</developer>
		<publisher>NEC</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Down Load 2 (Japan).chd</path>
		<name>Download 2</name>
		<desc>Download 2 is an horizontal shooter. Nec Avenue certainly acknowledged that the game's best asset was the unique and innovative ability to jack-in and dive into computerized cyber-space worlds. This sequel follows the same formula but also features probably one of most electrifying storyline ever written for a video game. The brain of Adolf Hitler has been digitized inside a computer mainframe by terrorists and Syd, an elite cyber-diver and protagonist of the game, embarks on a perilous journey to stop and destroy the incoming threat. On board his ship and helped by the cute Deva, Syd flies through nine enemy infested areas and dives into abstract and challenging cyber worlds. Four different weapons are available to him at the press of a button - multiway Vulcan-gun, wide laser-beams, spread homing-lasers and a short-range lightning gun. Each weapon can be powered-up a grand total of three times by collecting "P" pods that appear on the screen whereas "S" pods increase the overall speed of the ship. Other special items are available throughout the game such as smart-bombs and protective shields.</desc>
		<releasedate>19910329T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Alfa System</developer>
		<publisher>NEC</publisher>
		<genre>Shoot'em up / Horizontal</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Downtown Nekketsu Koushinkyoku - Soreyuke Daiundoukai (Japan).chd</path>
		<name>Downtown Nekketsu Koushinkyoku - Soreyuke Daiundoukai</name>
		<desc>Another day at Nekketsu High, another gang tournament... but this time its different! A wealthy school principal has placed a challenge for all the school gangs to compete in a special obstacle course composed of 4 different challenges that you and your team must overcome. First in line is a race across the city streets (and rooftops), next is an obstacle course filled with dangerous hazards, then a jumping challenge in which you have to break a series of metal balls, and finally an all-out fighting tournament.

The game uses the same engine and basic gameplay mechanics featured in other Nekketsu High games, with the only change being the goals you must complete to clear each stage. Seeing as how the characters are gang members, fighting and beating your opponents can be a viable way of winning the challenges, so several weapons and power-ups can also be found in the courses </desc>
		<releasedate>19921211T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Technos Japan Corp.</developer>
		<publisher>Naxat Soft</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1-4</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Downtown Nekketsu Monogatari (Japan).chd</path>
		<name>Downtown Nekketsu Monogatari</name>
		<desc>Brothers Ryuichi and Ryuji arrive at the Reihou Academy, located near Nekketsu High. After a short amount of time, nearby schools have begun fallen under the control of Ryuichi and Ryuji, who rumor has it have dubbed themselves the Double Dragons.

Riki Samejima of Hanazono High has never seen eye to eye with Kunio, and in fact, they seem to always compete to be the best.

But one day, Mami Shimada, Riki's girlfriend, is kidnapped and held at Reihou Academy. The issue is challenged to Riki, come save your girlfriend!

Riki's heart is burning with fury, and he flies out of the gates and seeks out his rival Kunio to help take on all opposing gangs. But one man awaits them at Reihou Academy that will shock Kunio!</desc>
		<releasedate>19931224T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Technos Japan Corp.</developer>
		<publisher>Naxat Soft</publisher>
		<genre>Beat'em Up</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Dragon Ball Z - Idainaru Son Gokuu Densetsu (Japan) (FABT).chd</path>
		<name>Dragon Ball Z - Idainaru Son Gokuu Densetsu</name>
		<desc>Idainaru Son Goku Densetsu features Gohan telling Goten of the battles of their deceased father, Goku, along with other characters. The game illustrates Goku's seven greatest battles: fighting Mercenary Tao, challenging Tien Shinhan at the World Martial Arts Tournament, destroying King Piccolo, fighting Piccolo at the 23rd World Martial Arts Tournament, protecting Earth from Vegeta, saving Namek from Frieza, and sacrificing his life to save the world from Perfect Cell.

The game does not let the player completely control Goku, instead choosing whether he is on the offense, defense, powering up, or running. There are also cutscenes that may happen in the middle of battle, triggered by certain actions from the series, such as Goku breaking Tao's sword with the Power Pole.</desc>
		<releasedate>19941111T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Bandai Namco</developer>
		<publisher>Bandai Namco</publisher>
		<genre>Fight</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Dragon Half (Japan).chd</path>
		<name>Dragon Half</name>
		<desc>Mink is a young girl who discovers that she has dragon blood, and is destined to seal away the evil demon Azetodeth. The only way to do that is use the sacred Gourd, which, in its turn, can be made only after having acquired three sacred artifacts. Together with her friends Lufa, Pia, and Princess Vina, Mink embarks on a quest for the artifacts, hoping to defeat Azetodeth once and for all!

This interpretation of Ryuusuke Mita's manga Dragon Half is entirely different from the  computer version. It is a combination of a board game and an RPG. Up to 4 players can compete, each controlling a party of characters from the manga. The navigation takes place on a large board, and is controlled by dice rolls. The player can advance only as many steps as the number on the dice; however, most of the board has many different paths and crossroads, which allows certain freedom of movement and planning. 

Different spots on the board have a variety of effects on the party. Red-colored spots lead to turn-based enemy encounters. The player must press a button in time to choose an attack by a specific party member, and also to determine its strength. Experience points are rewarded after battles, and the characters level up in a fashion similar to other Japanese RPGs.

Other places on the board include damage traps, shops, trigger meetings with other characters, lead to healing spots such as pools and hotels.</desc>
		<releasedate>19930101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Studio Hard</developer>
		<publisher>Microcabin</publisher>
		<genre>Board game</genre>
		<players>1-4</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Dragon Knight &amp; Graffiti (Japan).chd</path>
		<name>Dragon Knight And Grafitti</name>
		<desc>Dragon Knight &amp;amp; Graffiti is the remake of the  first game in the  Dragon Knight series.

The remake has the same story (the wandering knight Takeru has to defeat a demon who threatens a town populated only by women) and core gameplay (explore a huge dungeon full of monsters, return to the only town to buy better weapons and equipment), but features better graphics, more convenient battle interface, and voice acting.

Despite the abundance of pretty girls, there are no explicit sex scenes in this game.

As the name implies, the remake also has a "graffiti mode" (accessible from the main menu), which lets the player view all the hand-drawn pictures of the game - those of pretty girls or any other kind.</desc>
		<releasedate>19950331T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Elf Corporation</developer>
		<publisher>NEC</publisher>
		<genre>Role playing games</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Dragon Knight II (Japan).chd</path>
		<name>Dragon Knight 2</name>
		<desc>Strawberry Fields - a magic country populated almost exclusively by beautiful young girls (that is, if we don't count the Wise Old Man and a couple of other male exceptions). All went well in this peaceful place, until the evil witch Mesaana abducted some of the country's lovely inhabitants and placed a curse upon them, turning them into hideous monsters. Enter Takeru Yamato (whom you might know as Desmond, the hero of Knights of Xentar), a young adventurer who happens to be in Strawberry Fields at that time. Takeru is told that in order to remove the curse one has to find three sacred writings, buried deep within three dangerous dungeons. Looks like a job for our adventurer - especially because the rescued girls will probably be very grateful!</desc>
		<releasedate>19920807T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Elf Corporation</developer>
		<publisher>NEC</publisher>
		<genre>Role playing games</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Dragon Knight III (Japan).chd</path>
		<name>Dragon Knight 3</name>
		<desc>This version of Dragon Knight III is based on the earlier computer release, known in the West as Knights of Xentar. While retaining the story, the graphical style, and the basic location layout of the computer version, this release has substantial gameplay differences.

Unlike in the computer version, the battles are not real-time, but turn-based, and utilize a different perspective; randomly encountered enemies are fought in a first-person, Dragon Quest-like traditional Japanese RPG style. Enemy design is also quite different; many of the monsters from the original version have been replaced with female characters. The graphics in the top-down areas have been slightly enhanced.

This version also censors the adult content. The scenes are still suggestive, but there is no explicit nudity in them any more. Some of the cutscenes have been completely re-drawn, eliminating even implicit sexual activity.</desc>
		<releasedate>19940722T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Elf Corporation</developer>
		<publisher>NEC</publisher>
		<genre>Role playing games</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Dragon Slayer - The Legend of Heroes (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Dragon Slayer : The Legend of Heroes</name>
		<desc>Dragon Slayer: The Legend of Heroes is a RPG for PC Engine. You play as Prince Selios/Logan. During a test intended to make you a warrior, the kingdom of your father is attacked by savage monsters. Betrayed on all sides by your former allies, you must recruit companions to liberate your country.</desc>
		<releasedate>19921201T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nihon Falcom</developer>
		<publisher>Hudson</publisher>
		<genre>Role playing games</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Dungeon Explorer II (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Dungeon Explorer II</name>
		<desc>This CD sequel to Dungeon Explorer plays exactly the same as the first game. You chose your character from a variety of fantasy stereotypes and set forth in a Gauntlet-esque adventure. The CD format allows a greater quantity and variety of levels to compliment the storyline, with new areas and characters becoming open to you as you progress.</desc>
		<releasedate>19930326T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Atlus</developer>
		<publisher>Hudson</publisher>
		<genre>Role playing games</genre>
		<players>1-5</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Dungeon Master - Theron's Quest (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Dungeon Master : Theron's Quest</name>
		<desc>Terrifyingly brutal beasts! Monstrous mazes! Treacherous pits of evil! The adventure of a lifetime is here....Theron's Quest!!

The Monastery at Ya-Brodin has fallen to the Cult of Deaths and the Brotherhood of Enlightenment, the true keepers of Magic, have been slaughtered. The Seven Great Treasures now lie in the hands of foul beings who will stop at nothing to hold onto their massive powers. But Theron, with a courage beyond belief, has decided to seek out the Cult of Deaths and win back the Treasures. If he succeeds, he will become a High Lord. If not, the land will see eternal darkness.</desc>
		<releasedate>19920918T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>FTL - Faster Than Light</developer>
		<publisher>Victor Entertainment</publisher>
		<genre>Role playing games</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Dynastic Hero, The (USA).chd</path>
		<name>The Dynastic Hero</name>
		<desc>The Dynastic Hero is a slightly re-branded version of Wonder Boy in Monster World for the Turbo Duo.The game features palette-swapped visuals, new insect-themed graphics for main characters (and insects' natural predators as bosses), a Red Book audio soundtrack which is completely different from the Wonder Boy original, and anime-style cutscenes at the intro and ending. Shion was renamed Dyna and was modeled after a Hercules Beetle, and the final boss was changed to a giant lizard king. An English-language version was also produced, but both were built off of the Japanese version of Wonder Boy in Monster World. They feature the same difficulty and mechanics as the Japanese original.</desc>
		<releasedate>19910101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Westone</developer>
		<publisher>Hudson</publisher>
		<genre>Role playing games</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Exile (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Exile : Wicked Phenomenon</name>
		<desc>The world of Chaltar is at stake and Sadler returns as the main protagonist and titular character of the series. Nearly, as his first task is to look for his friends in the nearby towns. Unlike the previous episodes of the series, Sadler is here one of several possible playable characters - the cute but lethal Rumi, the strong Kindi and the mystic Fakhyle follow our hero in his quest and can be controlled. The game follows the same formula laid out by its predecessors and alternates between fighting and exploring. The first part gets Sadler to walk around towns, talk to villagers or purchase new equipment. The fighting phases are classic hack-and-slash action scenes set in countless hostile locations - there the player fight enemies, bosses and earn precious experience points and gold coins.</desc>
		<releasedate>19930731T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Alfa System</developer>
		<publisher>Nihon Telenet</publisher>
		<genre>Role playing games</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Exile - Wicked Phenomenon (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Exile : Wicked Phenomenon</name>
		<desc>The world of Chaltar is at stake and Sadler returns as the main protagonist and titular character of the series. Nearly, as his first task is to look for his friends in the nearby towns. Unlike the previous episodes of the series, Sadler is here one of several possible playable characters - the cute but lethal Rumi, the strong Kindi and the mystic Fakhyle follow our hero in his quest and can be controlled. The game follows the same formula laid out by its predecessors and alternates between fighting and exploring. The first part gets Sadler to walk around towns, talk to villagers or purchase new equipment. The fighting phases are classic hack-and-slash action scenes set in countless hostile locations - there the player fight enemies, bosses and earn precious experience points and gold coins.</desc>
		<releasedate>19930731T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Alfa System</developer>
		<publisher>Nihon Telenet</publisher>
		<genre>Role playing games</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./F1 Circus Special - Pole to Win (Japan) (FABT).chd</path>
		<name>F1 Circus Special - Pole To Win</name>
		<desc>F1 Circus Special is a Formula 1 racing game. Players can choose between a world championship mode, which follows the path of one driver through the game's available courses in a linear fashion; a test drive mode, which allows players to choose any course as well as change rules and conditions (e.g. the amount of damage inflicted); and a time attack mode for competing against each other.</desc>
		<releasedate>19920626T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nichibutsu</developer>
		<publisher>Nichibutsu</publisher>
		<genre>Sports / Running trails</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./F1 Team Simulation - Project F (Japan).chd</path>
		<name>F1 Team Simulation - Project F</name>
		<desc>Project F is a managerial simulation that puts the player in the role of the owner of a Formula 1 company. The player is responsible for paying salary to managers, mechanics, and other members of the staff; it is possible to raise or lower the salary, which may lead to various consequences depending on the employee's personality. Then the player makes contract with one or more drivers, selecting them from a list. Car customization plays an important role. Gasoline, engines, chassis, wheels, tires, brakes, and other components must be purchased from manufacturers of the player's choice. 

The racing competition itself is non-interactive. Tournament events follow depending on its schedule, and the player simply watches how the race unfolds and ends according to the participants' parameters. Brand and player names in the game resemble real ones, but have been slightly altered for copyright reasons.</desc>
		<releasedate>19920911T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Shin-Nihon Laser Soft</developer>
		<publisher>Shin-Nihon Laser Soft</publisher>
		<genre>Simulation</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Fantastic Night Dreams - Cotton (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Cotton : Fantastic Night Dreams</name>
		<desc>Cotton: Fantastic Night Dreams plays in a similar way to other scrolling shooter video games such as R-Type. What distinguishes Cotton: Fantastic Night Dreams from other games of a similar ilk is its bright colourful graphics and its lead character, Cotton. The game also takes place in a fantasy dream-like world instead of space like many other shooting games. The game can be compared to other fantasy Shoot 'em up games like Parodius. It bears most similarities in style to the Chariot game on Three Wonders.

The player controls Cotton, a young witch on a broomstick. The player must blast various monsters and avoid being shot. The player can collect power-ups to enhance their weaponry and unleash a more powerful attack on the enemy. The player has lives represented by an arrow. The player has three lives and is only allowed one hit per life.</desc>
		<releasedate>19930212T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Success</developer>
		<publisher>Hudson</publisher>
		<genre>Shoot'em up / Horizontal</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Faussete Amour (Japan).chd</path>
		<name>Fausseté Amour</name>
		<desc>A young girl named Koruku lived in her home village, enjoying a peaceful life with her sister and her friends. But it all changed when an evil demon known as the Goatbone appeared. With his powers of mind control and shape-shifting, he possessed Koruku's friends, turning them into terrifying monsters, kidnapped her sister, and burnt down the village. A mysterious old man approaches the desperate Koruku and bestows her with a wonderful armor, weapon, and magic powers. The young girl is ready to venture into Goatbone's lair and liberate her sister... but will she be able to defeat her own friends who now obey the word of their dark master?</desc>
		<releasedate>19930326T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>AIM</developer>
		<publisher>Naxat Soft</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Fighting Street (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Fighting Street</name>
		<desc>Deep inside you there lurks a warrior. Let him loose! And test him against the martial arts champions of 5 nations. Grit your teeth, pump up and take after Retsu and Geki from Japan. Most worthy opponents! But watch out for the baddest - Adon and Sagat, a couple of Thai's. Mike and Joe (USA), Birdi and Eagle (UK), Lee and Gen (China) all have their own special "tricks." Be quick and strong, or be gone!</desc>
		<releasedate>19891204T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>NEC</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Fight</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Final Zone II (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Final Zone II</name>
		<desc>Final Zone II is a top down shooter in which you controls a soldier on some levels and vehicle on other levels. As a soldier you don a "New Age Power Suit" and have a choice of playing several different characters, though it is only a one player game.

The object of the game is to fight an enemy army led by "ZOD" who is a mass murderer and killed some of your commando friends. There are various armaments and shields that you can pick up along the way. There are several manga-style animation sequences in the game.

This is the sequel to a Mega Drive game called Final Zone which was released in 1990 also.</desc>
		<releasedate>19900323T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Renovation Products</developer>
		<publisher>Telenet</publisher>
		<genre>Shoot'em up / Vertical</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Forgotten Worlds (USA) (En,Ja).chd</path>
		<name>Forgotten Worlds</name>
		<desc>Forgotten Worlds features two characters known as The Nameless Ones, who both look like Arnold Schwarzenegger, one even has a mohawk. It's their job to rid the planet of the attacking aliens. 

Guiding your character around the screen as they fly with jet-packs, guns on full auto, you control a satellite which you rotate around your character for the direction in which your gun is firing. At the end of each level is a boss which needs to be killed to progress.

Enemies that have been killed drop money. At the end of every level is a shop where you can buy weapons, armour, items and first-aid packs.</desc>
		<releasedate>19920101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Turbo Technologies</publisher>
		<genre>Shoot'em Up</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Formation Soccer 95 della Serie A (Japan).chd</path>
		<name>Formation Soccer 95 Della Serie A</name>
		<desc>Formation Soccer 95 della Serie A is a soccer (football) game that re-creates a season in the top football league of Italy, including licensed players and teams. There is no management element in the game; players simply have to choose one or more (for tournament mode) teams and participate in either exhibition or Serie A (Italian Championship) games. Teams can be controlled by human players or computer AI; it is also possible to select the "watch" mode and view the game unfolding with both teams being controlled by the computer. Practice mode for corner, free, and penalty kicks is included as well. Rules and conditions can be changed (e.g. it is possible to play without injuries).</desc>
		<releasedate>19950407T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Hunex</developer>
		<publisher>Human</publisher>
		<genre>Sports / Soccer</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Fushigi no Umi no Nadia - The Secret of Blue Water (Japan).chd</path>
		<name>Fushigi No Umi No Nadia - The Secret Of Blue Water</name>
		<desc>Fushigi no Umi no Nadia: The Secret of Blue Water is one of the several games based on the anime series of the same name. The game assumes familiarity with the story of the anime, taking the player directly into the time frame of late episodes, where Grandis and the jewel thieves have already joined Jean and Nadia on their travels with Captain Nemo on his submarine "Nautilus". Following a dramatic scene that reveals more about Electra's past, the crew is stranded on a mysterious island. Jean, Nadia, Marie, and the lion cub King decide to explore it, and discover an ancient civilization in the process.

The game plays mostly like an interactive comic book or a visual novel, though it does contain adventure elements such as verb commands. However, these commands are usually very sparse, and there are no sub-menus with objects or people to interact with. The game advances linearly, and the player's input is for the most part reduced to choosing between several locations to explore first. There is also a separate quiz mode where the player answers trivia questions asked by characters from the series.</desc>
		<releasedate>19930129T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Hudson</developer>
		<publisher>Hudson</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Gate of Thunder + Bonk's Adventure + Bonk's Revenge (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Gate Of Thunder</name>
		<desc>A side-scrolling shoot-'em-up, Gate of Thunder asks players to take control of the space-craft "Hunting Dog". You fly left-to-right mostly, with occasional vertically-scrolling sections, and use several different weapon styles to defeat your many foes. Along with Esty in her ship the "Wild Cat", you must defeat the forces of General Don Jingi, who has plans of taking energy from the star of Aries.

Playing as the pilot Hawk, players must avoid collisions and weapon-fire from the General's "Obellon" army. Consisting of many different types of enemy, the army has a massive, sprawling force of guns, turret, ships, battle-stations and mech-type units. Their fire-power is immense and you are the single opposing force!

Gate of Thunder allows players to choose in real-time from three weapon-fire types. A blue-coloured electrical fire, a green-coloured wave-fire, and a red-coloured quake-type fire. Along with this, players obtain homing-missiles and the assistance of the "Wild Cat" which orbits the ship separately. Gate of Thunder also features a critically acclaimed soundtrack that remains a talking-point to this day.</desc>
		<releasedate>19921010T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Red Company</developer>
		<publisher>Hudson</publisher>
		<genre>Shoot'em Up</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Genocide (Japan).chd</path>
		<name>Genocide</name>
		<desc>Life became more and more complicated in the 22th century. Humans have constructed a super-computer known as MESIA, entrusting it with the task of monitoring everything that happens on the planet. However, the computer grew increasingly megalomaniac, and eventually decided to conquer the Earth with deadly machines of its own production. In the middle of the 23rd century, humanity engages in a decisive battle against MESIA. Their hopes lie with Ken Ryugasaki, who pilots the powerful mecha Tracer on his journey to the super-computer's lair.

Genocide is a side-scrolling action game. The player controls Tracer, who can fight with a sword-like melee weapon and jump. Later in the game Tracer acquires "Betty", a powerful weapon that can shoot in eight directions. The gameplay is fairly straightforward; there are no power-ups, and the bulk of the game consists of surviving continuous onslaughts of enemies.</desc>
		<releasedate>19920626T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Zoom</developer>
		<publisher>BrainGrey</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Ginga Fukei Densetsu Sapphire (Japan).chd</path>
		<name>Ginga Fukei Densetsu Sapphire</name>
		<desc>In the future, time travel became a regular commodity. Criminal organizations began using advanced science in order to escape into different time periods to avoid capture. To counter that, a special police unit called "Burning Rabbits" was formed, consisting of four young ladies who bravely pilot their fighter craft through time and space.

Ginga Fukei Densetsu: Sapphire is a vertically-scrolling shoot-em-up. The player can choose between four different female characters, each piloting a different ship: Sapphire has balanced strength is speed; Charlotte is the fastest, but also the weakest; Helen is the slowest and the strongest; Jasmine is the second-strongest and the second-slowest. The ships are also distinguished by their weapon properties. Each ship can collect red, green, or blue power-ups; collecting a power-up of the same color enhances the currently equipped weapon, while a differently-colored power-up changes weapon properties while retaining whatever enhancements the ship might have had with the previous weapon. The actual properties of each weapon is different for each ship, and include various combinations of lasers, beams, missiles, piercing and homing weapons.

Each ship also has two pods on the sides that fire simultaneously. If the player releases the fire button for five seconds, the pods will charge up and damage enemies with electricity during the next shot. In additions, the ships can also drop bombs that heavily damage all the enemies on the screen; up to two bombs can be carried at the same time. The stages include various themes such as medieval, feudal China, ancient Egypt, etc., all with a strong sci-fi angle. The player can continue up to nine times from the same spot if the protagonist runs out of lives, and additional continues are granted when the player gathers a sufficient amount of points.</desc>
		<releasedate>19951124T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>CAProduction</developer>
		<publisher>Hudson</publisher>
		<genre>Shoot'em up / Vertical</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Godzilla (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Godzilla</name>
		<desc>This interpretation of the famous giant monster from the Japanese cinematic industry takes form of a fighting game, only instead of the usual brave martial artists the players control horrifying monsters from the traditional  Toho lineage: the titular beast itself, Rodan, Anguirus, Ghidorah, and others. The game has two modes: Normal and Vs. The latter is essentially a two-player mode, which allows the players to engage in giant monster battles in a variety of scenarios. Most of the monsters, however, are locked in the Vs. mode before the player has completed the Normal mode.

The Normal mode puts the player in control of Godzilla, who has to go through five stages before reaching the final boss. Each stage has two battles against two different creatures in two different locations, from which the player has to complete only one in order to proceed to the next stage. Depending on the player's performance, points are awarded; in order to be able to compete against different final bosses, the player has to accumulate more points. If the player only has the minimum required points, only one final boss will be available.

The combat system is similar to other fighting games, with various combinations of buttons executing different moves. Naturally, the normal "punch-kick" scheme is modified to suit the monsters' shapes and biological peculiarities. For example, monsters with tails can use tail spin attacks; fire-breathing monsters have a range fire attack, etc. Most of the monsters (including Godzilla) have a move when they hold the opponent and suck its blood. </desc>
		<releasedate>19930101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Hudson</developer>
		<publisher>Toho Company</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Golden Axe (Japan).chd</path>
		<name>Golden Axe</name>
		<desc>Golden Axe is an arcade beat-'em-up game that puts players in the shoes of one of three heroes, each with his own reason for trying to overthrow the evil rule of Death-Adder, who - along with his forces of darkness - kidnapped and imprisoned the King and his daughter and stole the legendary Golden Axe.

This is a horizontal fighting game, where you basically take one of the three characters (the barbarian Ax Battler, a dwarf named Gilius Thunderhead or the amazon Tyris Flare) and bash everything which stands between you and Death Adder himself. Each character has a special magical ability that can be charged by kicking small blue creatures that drop a potion. There is also a green variety off this creature that drops food that replenishes your health. Some enemies ride dragons and a scorpion like creature. The enemies can be knocked off and you can mount the creature yourself and attack the enemies with it.

The game allows to play up to two players on a same screen, however in the C64 version this option has not been implemented. C64 version was also stripped off in the other areas, such as: only one enemy can engage the player at a time or there are only two types of dragons instead of three.</desc>
		<releasedate>19900316T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Renovation Game</developer>
		<publisher>Telenet</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Gradius II (X68k FM+MT-32 OST).chd</path>
		<name>Gradius 2 - Gofer No Yabou</name>
		<desc>Gradius II is a sequel to Gradius and Life Force, and is a horizontal space shooter composed of seven levels. Like in its predecessor, it is possible to collect power-ups from enemies and choose which type to use and when. This time, this system is enhanced with the option of choosing between four different power-up sequences, allowing the player to use different types of weapons against enemies. There is also the possibility to gain options, which are mysterious balls of fire that follows the player-controlled spaceship closely and mimic all its movements (including shots). While the player only could have two of them in the NES version of Gradius, it is now possible in all versions to have up to four.</desc>
		<releasedate>19921218T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Konami</developer>
		<publisher>Konami</publisher>
		<genre>Shoot'em up / Horizontal</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Hatsukoi Monogatari (Japan) (Rev 2).chd</path>
		<name>Hatsukoi Monogatari</name>
		<desc>An ordinary Japanese student finds a floppy disk on the street; using his computer to load data from it, he miraculously summons Foltjunia, an intergalactic warrior who fights evil in her robotic armor with three companions. However, Foltjunia has lost her powers and as a result stays with the hero, giving him advice as to how to conquer the love of a schoolmate.

Following a brief prologue with adventure-like gameplay,  the bulk of Hatsukoi Monogatari consists of managerial simulation along the lines of Princess Maker games, though with more limited options and no RPG elements. The player manages the hero's daily schedule, divided into two segments: school and home. Activities include studying, having conversations with students or teachers, taking part-time jobs, resting, talking on the phone, shopping, buying presents, etc. Each activity increases or decreases some of the hero's parameters. The overall level can be evaluated on a special screen, and the goal is to raise it by balancing the stats with various activities.</desc>
		<releasedate>19940428T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Tokuma Shoten</developer>
		<publisher>Tokuma Shoten</publisher>
		<genre>Simulation</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Hellfire S - The Another Story (Japan).chd</path>
		<name>Hellfire S - The Another Story</name>
		<desc>Hellfire S is a Shoot-'Em-Up game, developed by Bits Laboratory and published by NEC International, which was released in Japan in 1991.</desc>
		<releasedate>19910412T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Toaplan</developer>
		<publisher>NEC</publisher>
		<genre>Shoot'em up / Horizontal</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Human Sports Festival (Japan).chd</path>
		<name>Human Sports Festival</name>
		<desc>Human Sports Festival is a compilation that contains three previously unreleased sports games:
Fine Shot Golf is a golf game for up to four players with an exhibition, tournament, and practice mode. It is possible to choose club types and (in the practice mode) golf course. The game is played from a first-person perspective, and requires the player to stop a moving bar at the correct moment to regulate the strength of the short.
Formation Soccer: Human Cup '92 is a top-down soccer (football) game that allows the player to choose an international team out of several available European and American ones. Formation and goaltender behavior can be customized; however, no detailed player management is present. The championship mode allows one or two players to compete against the computer.
Final Match Tennis Ladies is similar in style to Final Match Tennis, but with notable female tennis players (their names are slightly altered). It is possible to choose one of the three available tennis court types, as well as go through the Australian Open tournament controlling one competitor in a cup system.</desc>
		<releasedate>19920228T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Human</developer>
		<publisher>Human</publisher>
		<genre>Compilation</genre>
		<players>1-4</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Hyper Dyne - SideArms Special (Japan).chd</path>
		<name>Hyper Dyne Sidearms Special</name>
		<desc>Hyper Dyne Side Arms Special is an Action game, developed by Capcom and published by NEC Interchannel, which was released in Japan in 1989.</desc>
		<releasedate>19891215T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>NEC</publisher>
		<genre>Shoot'em Up</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./ImageFight II - Operation Deepstriker (Japan).chd</path>
		<name>Imagefight 2 - Operation Deepstriker</name>
		<desc>An enemy armada approaches Earth bent on the destruction of the human race. In this sequel to Image Fight, players take control of the most advanced spaceship in the fleet. Destroy "POW" cases for items and special weapons. Obtain Red and Blue Pods to equip your ship. Red Pods fire the opposite way your fighter is moving, and Blue Pods only fire forward. You can also change the speed of your ship, to adjust to different battle conditions. Defeat the alien invaders once and for all and bring peace back to the Galaxy.</desc>
		<releasedate>19921218T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Irem</developer>
		<publisher>Irem</publisher>
		<genre>Shooter / Vertical</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./It Came from the Desert (USA).chd</path>
		<name>It Came From The Desert</name>
		<desc>It Came from the Desert is a remake of the the original 1989 Amiga game of the same name, but with a vast amount of changes and improvements. The basic setting was kept identical. It is a mix of action and adventure elements, largely inspired from cult-horror B-Movies of the 50's and 60's, and the 1954 film Them in particular. The player plays the part of Dr. Greg Bradley, a geologist and the newest resident in town. Eager to satisfy his scientific mind, Bradley sets out to examine the crash-site of a mysterious meteor, but what he finds is not at all what he had been looking for.</desc>
		<releasedate>19890101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Cinemaware</developer>
		<publisher>Mirrorsoft</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./J. B. Harold Murder Club (USA) (En,Ja).chd</path>
		<name>J.B. Harold Murder Club</name>
		<desc>From a gameplay point of view, Murder Club is a "Digital Comic". The player controls the private detective J.B. Harold, who must investigate the murder of a wealthy businessman named Bill Robbins and bring the murderer to justice. The player must: find clues, gather evidence, interview suspects, establish a motive for the crime and finally, ensure that the case holds up in court. At the heart of the game system is a map with all the possible destinations, with new ones being added as the investigation progresses. In each of these locations there is usually one or more people, whom you can question at your leisure via sober and efficient text menus. If certain statements seem suspicious, you are free to ask your superior for a warrant to search the premises and collect any evidence.</desc>
		<releasedate>19910101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Riverhillsoft</developer>
		<publisher>NEC</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Jim Power in Mutant Planet (Japan).chd</path>
		<name>Jim Power In Mutant Planet</name>
		<desc>Jim Power was a hero who one day while travelling through the forest, encountered a dimensional rift into a strange new world. Luckily Jim always travels armed and now he'll need to fight his way past several monsters into a monster stronghold to find his way back home.

Jim Power is a side-scrolling platform game, a side-scrolling shooter and a top-view shooter game depending on the level. Jim Power for the most part can jump and has an upgradable gun weapon. He must find fight enemies, bosses and obtain various keys to progress through the levels. Jim also has a "Smart Bomb" power attack which can clear the screen of enemies. In shooter levels, Jim's spaceship only has the ability to shoot and move around the screen avoiding obstacles.</desc>
		<releasedate>19930319T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Digital Concept</developer>
		<publisher>Micro World</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Last Alert (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Last Alert</name>
		<desc>In the near future, a cabal of 4 very evil, powerful men known as The Force is planning world domination through the use of a Super Weapon known and Indra. You are Guy Kazama, a general-purpose bad-ass soldier who can stop these guys.  You must take out each of the conspirators one by one and destroy the Indra before it becomes fully operational.

Last Alert is a shoot-em up played from a top-down perspective.  You move Guy around more than 20 levels and shoot everything that stands in your way.</desc>
		<releasedate>19900101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Shin-Nihon Laser Soft</developer>
		<publisher>NEC</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Legend of Xanadu - Kaze no Densetsu Xanadu (Japan).chd</path>
		<name>Kaze No Densetsu Xanadu</name>
		<desc>In Legend of Xanadu, the player controls a young adventurer named Areios. Monsters attack his homeland, and he is forced to flee. After traveling by ship and arriving at the town Bolda, Areios finds out that strange things have been happening in the North Cave near the town. His first mission will be to venture to the North Cave and investigate the matter. Of course, soon Areios finds himself involved in a battle against sinister forces, and commences the longest and most dangerous adventure of his life!

The game is an action RPG set in the Dragon Slayer universe, with a gameplay style similar to  Falcom's other popular series, Ys. Controlling Areios, the player explores the top-down world, visiting towns and fighting monsters in vast outdoor areas and dungeons. Like in Ys series, it is sufficient to "bump" into a monster in order to inflict damage. Areios gains hit points and becomes stronger by sustaining damage from enemies and resting. His weapons and armor can gain experience and level up. In many areas, companions will join Areios and help him in combat, controlled by the computer AI.

The game is divided into chapters; the final stage of each chapter is a side-scrolling/platform level, which Areios has to navigate in order to reach the boss enemy, defeat him, and end the chapter. In such stages, the combat turns into a more familiar action-oriented style, with the player being required to press buttons in time in order to execute attacks and jump.

There is a day/night cycle in the game, manifested not only in graphical changes, but also in the schedules of townspeople: when it's dark, people will return to their homes and go to sleep, etc.</desc>
		<releasedate>19940218T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nihon Falcom</developer>
		<publisher>Nihon Falcom</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Legend of Xanadu - Kaze no Densetsu Xanadu II (Japan).chd</path>
		<name>Kaze No Densetsu Xanadu 2</name>
		<desc>Legend of Xanadu II continues the story of the first game. Once again, the player controls the adventurer Areios, who emerged victorious after the final battle in the end of the first game. Together with his friend Daimos, Areios is looking for their other friend, who has disappeared. On the way, their ship is attacked by the evil Dragon Riders. It seems the search won't be as easy as they have thought, as Areios gets involved in a dangerous adventure again.

The sequel is very similar to the first game gameplay-wise. The player explores towns, vast outdoor areas, and dungeons, engaging enemies in real-time combat. Damage is inflicted upon the enemies simply by running into them, without any special attack button. There are various weapons to equip, and they level up in proficiency the more the player uses them. Areios gains additional hit points depending on the damage he receives. Party members help him in battles, controlled by the AI. The day and night cycle of the previous game has been removed.

Like in the previous game, there are side-scrolling segments which lead to boss battles at the end of each chapter. Compared to the first game, these stages are noticeably shorter, each containing only the boss fight itself, omitting platforming sections with regular enemies. Bosses must be fought using conventional action gameplay, attacking by pressing a button and jumping to avoid their attacks. It is also possible to defend actively and perform attacks in different directions. The player may opt to fight the bosses alone or select one of the available companions, either AI-controlled or in two-player mode.</desc>
		<releasedate>19950530T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nihon Falcom</developer>
		<publisher>Nihon Falcom</publisher>
		<genre>Role playing games</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Loom (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Loom</name>
		<desc>Loom was the fourth game to use the SCUMM scripting language. The game follows Bobbin Threadbare as he learns how to use his magical powers through his distaff and as he eventually saves the world from the Lord of Chaos, who was unraveling the Loom (the source of power for the members of the weaver's guild).

Loom is an adventure game that sets itself apart from other titles in the genre through its unique gameplay system: the player character does not carry items around, but rather manipulates objects through the use of spells (called "drafts" in the game). The drafts themselves are woven by playing magical notes on a special instrument called "distaff". All the puzzles in the game are solved by learning and correctly applying these drafts. 

Although the PC Engine version is CD based, it isn't a port of the PC CD-ROM version. Instead, it features mixed visuals from the 16- and 256-color versions adapted to the PC Engine's color palette and enhanced CD soundtrack with no spoken dialogue.</desc>
		<releasedate>19921204T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Turbo Technologies, Inc.</developer>
		<publisher>LucasArts</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Lords of the Rising Sun (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Lords Of The Rising Sun</name>
		<desc>Japan, 12th century. After your father has been murdered, you set out on a quest to become Shogun to restore the honor of your family.

You'll have to defeat all your enemies - including your brother.

Most of the time, you'll move your troops through the big map of Japan - as soon as something happens, you'll have to fight your enemies in action sequences, such as a Gauntlet-like fortress attack or defending against a Ninja assassin. If two troops collide, a battle might ensue in which you'll have to use all your strategical wits to guide your men to victory.

In the CD-i version the informative sequences include life actor FMVs and voice acting as well as new background art.</desc>
		<releasedate>19920101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Cinemaware</developer>
		<publisher>NEC</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Lords of Thunder (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Lords of Thunder</name>
		<desc>Lords of Thunder is a side-scrolling shooter that has you take on the role of a legendary warrior, blasting enemies to heavy-metal tunes. Your enemies are plotting to revive Zaggart, "The Dark One," who was sealed beneath the six continents of Mistral. It's up to Landis, descendant of the heroic Dyu, to stop them. Choose the order in which to attack the six stages. Before each stage, select one of four magic armors and use crystals you've collected during your battles to buy items. Then get ready to face awesome enemies like a fire-spewing sea serpent or a giant insect.</desc>
		<releasedate>19930101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Red Company</developer>
		<publisher>Hudson</publisher>
		<genre>Shoot'em Up</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Mad Stalker - Full Metal Force (Japan).chd</path>
		<name>Mad Stalker - Full Metal Force</name>
		<desc>Mad Stalker: Full Metal Force is a Japanese beat 'em up video game originally produced by Fill-in-Cafe and published and distributed by FamilySoft for the Sharp X68000. The music was composed by Keishi Yonao.</desc>
		<releasedate>19940915T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Fill in Café</developer>
		<publisher>NEC</publisher>
		<genre>Beat'em Up</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Magical Dinosaur Tour (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Magical Dinosaur Tour</name>
		<desc>The Magical Dinosaur Tour is an extensive dinosaur database.

Several modes may be accessed from the main menu, most of which lead to visual presentations and descriptions of various dinosaurs. Individual dinosaur data can be accessed by viewing geological periods and geographical areas (e.g. China of the Cretaceous period) and selecting dinosaurs appearing on the screen; browsing a dinosaur list alphabetically; viewing a genealogical tree; and finally viewing dinosaurs by phylum and family.

Most areas can be scrolled to the sides and some of the dinosaurs present themselves with voice-overs. There is also a variety section that allows viewing various dinosaur-related records and specifications (such as the tallest dinosaurs, inhabitants of cold areas, etc.). Another section is dedicated to animated sequences depicting various locations and dinosaurs.</desc>
		<releasedate>19900824T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Fun Project, Inc.</developer>
		<publisher>Victor Entertainment</publisher>
		<genre>Educational</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Mamono Hunter Youko - Makai kara no Tenkousei (Japan).chd</path>
		<name>Mamono Hunter Youko - Makai Kara No Tenkousei</name>
		<desc>Makai kara no Tenk?sei is based on the anime series Devil Hunter Yohko. The anime focuses on Yohko Mano, a Japanese high school student who discovers that she is the 108th Devil Hunter, destined to fight supernatural evil beings in accordance with her legacy. The game puts the player in the role of Shoma, a new exchange student who meets Yohko and her best friend Chikako at his new school. Miraculously, the three are teleported into a parallel dimension, and the reluctant hero discovers, to his amazement, that its inhabitants seem to be familiar with him.

The game plays like a typical Japanese-style adventure, with a menu of verb commands (Look, Talk, Think, and Move) at nearly every screen, some leading to object lists. It is often necessary to go through the commands several times to unlock a new one or trigger events. Limited menu-based navigation is also present. </desc>
		<releasedate>19920313T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>TamTam</developer>
		<publisher>Masaya Games</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Martial Champion (Japan).chd</path>
		<name>Martial Champion</name>
		<desc>Martial Champion is a versus fighting game similar in concept to Street Fighter II. There are ten characters to choose from, each representing his or her own country. The main protagonist is a Japanese martial artist named Jin; others include his countryman Zen, a kabuki fighter; a Chinese kung-fu expert and a vampire from Hong-Kong; an Egyptian princess; a scimitar fighter from Saudi Arabia; a spear-wielding Kenyan warrior; a French weapons specialist; and two North Americans - an eyepatched soldier and a blonde female ninja-like fighter. 

There are three modes in the game: a tournament mode, in which these characters compete against each other before facing the final boss; a versus mode; and a group fighting mode, in which each player selects several fighters to represent in a series of one-on-one battles. The fighting scheme resembles that of Yie Ar Kung Fu, though with a simplified handling of high, medium, and low attacks. Some of the characters use weapons in battles; it is possible to knock these weapons out of their hands and use them against their owners.</desc>
		<releasedate>19931217T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Konami</developer>
		<publisher>Konami</publisher>
		<genre>Fight / 2D</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Megami Paradise (Japan).chd</path>
		<name>Megami Tengoku - Megami Paradise</name>
		<desc>In a magical country where only women dwell, young girls study in a magic school to become powerful and benevolent goddesses. One day, four magical orbs fell into the hands of a student named Rin-Rin. The clumsy girl managed to lose all of them, without understanding what this could lead to:  nobody knows what will happen if the orbs fall into wrong hands - those of the dark goddesses! Aided by a little fairy named Pop, Rin-Rin has to gather the legendary goddesses and to find a way to retrieve the orbs.

Megami Tengoku is based on an anime of the same name (translated as Megami Paradise). It plays like a traditional top-down Japanese RPG with turn-based combat. Rin-Rin uses magical spells to fight enemies. An unusual feature of the game is the ability to change clothes, and the fact that every dress changes the graphical appearance of the character.</desc>
		<releasedate>19940930T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>A.I</developer>
		<publisher>NEC</publisher>
		<genre>Role playing games</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Metal Angel (Japan).chd</path>
		<name>Metal Angel</name>
		<desc>Metal Angel is a managerial simulation game that takes place in the futuristic society of 2014, where battles between fighters in mechanized suits have become a major sports event. The player takes control of a coach who must train five young women of different backgrounds, all of which aspire to become a professional fighter. The coach's statistics are generated by answering a series of questions in the beginning of the game. Each of the girl also has her own statistics that must be carefully monitored. With the exception of automatized events, the game consists of creating schedules for all the girls for one week in advance, and then watching how their attributes change. Activities include battle training, gymnastics, running, resting, etc. All the activities are displayed as small animated segments on the same screen.</desc>
		<releasedate>19930924T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Radical Plan Corp.</developer>
		<publisher>Pack In Video</publisher>
		<genre>Simulation</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Metal Angel 2 (Japan).chd</path>
		<name>Metal Angel 2</name>
		<desc>The follow-up to Metal Angel is, like its predecessor, a managerial simulation in which the player character trains young girls to become champions of a fighting championship where participants don mechanized power suits. The player controls a manager rather than a coach in this installment, and must keep an eye on the finances as a result. Also, instead of training all the five girls from the first game, the player's answers to the questions posed by the assistant in the beginning of the game determine the choice of the trainee among the same five characters.

The player must make schedules for the fighter, which include various training and recreational activities. The manager can hire coaches with their own programs, or input activities individually. The battles themselves allow little input, with the player being able to choose between various types of attacks by selecting them from a menu; the outcome of the battle largely depends on training and individual statistics. </desc>
		<releasedate>19950120T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Radical Plan Corp.</developer>
		<publisher>Pack In Video</publisher>
		<genre>Simulation</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Might and Magic III - Isles of Terra (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Might and Magic III : Isles of Terra</name>
		<desc>Emerging from the depths of the nebulous void, there came four lords. To each lord, a dominion: fire, water, air, and earth. But each lord lusted for more - to be the ultimate ruler of the void. The four lords of the elements descended into a hideous conflict that unleashed a raging storm.</desc>
		<releasedate>19930101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>New World Computing's</developer>
		<publisher>Hudson</publisher>
		<genre>Role playing games</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Monster Lair (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Monster Lair</name>
		<desc>Feeling more like the first Wonder Boy than the second, Monster Lair is a fast-paced auto scrolling platform game. The levels are split into two stages, the first being a platform stage, the second a shoot 'em up stage which ends in a boss. During the game your energy counts down, so you must keep picking up fruit to replenish yourself. There are a variety of weapons to collect - lasers, spread shots, spinning shields and so on, but these are also on a timer and do not last long, so weapon switching is frequent to avoid being left with your basic short range sword shot. The game is single or two player simultaneous.</desc>
		<releasedate>19900101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Alfa System</developer>
		<publisher>Hudson</publisher>
		<genre>Shoot'em Up</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Moonlight Lady (Japan).chd</path>
		<name>Moonlight Lady</name>
		<desc>Hiwako, the daughter of a convenience store owner in a little Japanese town, is just an ordinary Japanese teenager - actually a bit of a spoiled brat. Or so she thought, until one day, a talking bird named Nike (like the Greek goddess of victory, not like the footwear brand) told her that she possessed unique powers that made her transform into the glorious lady warrior Artemis. No, Hiwako didn't stop being a spoiled brat; but as Artemis, it is now her duty to protect her home town from a demonic invasion, and she does not intend to give up.

Moonlight Lady can be called a "pseudo-RPG"; its top-down view and town exploration make it look like a representative of the Japanese branch of this genre, but in reality, it is an action game with light adventure elements and no true role-playing system. 

Throughout most of the game, the player controls Artemis and two other heroines (Aquarius and Minerva). Attacking is performed by pressing a button for the lead character's attack, and another for a simultaneous attack by the two other girls. The player can switch the leader at any time. The girls can also charge their attacks to execute more powerful ones.

Regular enemies populate the dungeons, but there is no reward (in the role-playing sense of this word) in defeating them; in fact, the player can try to avoid them altogether and head straight to the boss battle.

A few items can be found and used throughout the game, but there is no real weapon and armor management, nor a financial system of any kind.</desc>
		<releasedate>19930326T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Shin-Nihon Laser Soft</developer>
		<publisher>NEC</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Motoroader MC (Japan).chd</path>
		<name>Motoroader Mc</name>
		<desc>Motoroader MC is, like its predecessor, an overhead racing game with car combat. Gameplay mechanics, however, are different: players can only control regular-looking cars, which are presented as small sprites. Each car is equipped with two types of firearms, which can be used against opponents to win the race. Every course only occupies one screen, and the player has to complete laps faster than AI-controlled cars or race against time. Multiplayer (for two or four players) is also available. 

Time attack mode allows the player to select any course from twenty-five available ones, thematically grouped in five categories: Circuit (resembling racing tracks), City (urban locations), Nature (field, beach, desert, etc.), Märchen (colorful fairy tale-like courses), and Special (unorthodox designs, e.g. a giant ape overlooking a road). Courses usually include various hazards that slow down or trap cars, as well as turbo fields that speed them up. Some courses also have entrances and exits, which teleport cars to another location on the screen.</desc>
		<releasedate>19890223T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>NCS Corporation</developer>
		<publisher>Masaya Games</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1-4</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Motteke Tamago (T-En).chd</path>
		<name>Motteke Tamago</name>
		<desc>Motteke Tamago was included in the second volume of the Super PC Engine Fan Deluxe magazine. It is an action game similar in concept to Bomberman. The game consists of three "worlds", each with ten screens; on every screen, four ducks are competing against each other in collecting eggs and delivering their babies home. The ducks can be controlled by human players or by computer AI. Eggs are being dropped into the maze-like stage; the goal is to collect as many of them as possible. Once collected, an egg follows the duck, and after a while a baby would hatch and return home safely.

Each duck tries to sabotage the work of other ducks by placing fried eggs on their paths. In addition, various hazards and enemies keep appearing, trying to impede the ducks' progress. Ducks can be knocked down, paralyzed, and robbed of their eggs.</desc>
		<releasedate>19970416T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Naxat Soft</developer>
		<publisher>Tokuma Shoten</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1-4</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Mugen Senshi Valis - The Legend of a Fantasm Soldier (Japan).chd</path>
		<name>Mugen Senshi Valis - The Legend Of A Fantasm Soldier</name>
		<desc>Yuko Ahso is an ordinary Japanese teenager with an ordinary life - until one day she is attacked by a monster on the street. Out of nowhere, a sword appears in her hands. She fights the monsters who have suddenly invaded the city, and is summoned to the parallel world known as Vecanti, which is ruled by a cruel tyrant named Rogles, whose actions disrupt the balance of the the worlds. Wielding the legendary Valis sword, Yuko must defeat Rogles and restore the balance.

Valis has the same story and basic genre (platform action) as the  original first game in the  series; however, it is a different game with different locations, regular enemies and bosses, new cutscenes, etc.  Defeating the numerous enemies populating the game world requires precise usage of jumping and ducking abilities, and attack timing. Yuko can jump very high and attack while jumping. Various power-ups are scattered through the game, many of which enhance the performance of Yuko's sword. Acting as a melee weapon in the beginning, it can be customized with power-ups and turn into a medium-range weapon, firing shots at the enemies - with proper power-ups, also in different directions. Boss enemies typically have different attack patterns and require different strategies to defeat them.</desc>
		<releasedate>19920319T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Riot</developer>
		<publisher>Telenet</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Palladion - Auto Crusher Palladium (Japan).chd</path>
		<name>Palladion - Auto Crusher Palladium</name>
		<desc>Auto Crusher Palladium is a game that simulates construction of battle robots ("mechs"). The player is able to construct robots using various parts: body, limbs, computer AI, weapons, etc. The result can be a combination of any forms and components, with the limitation being the overall weight of the robot, which must not exceed a specified amount. Robots can be humanoid, machine-like, rolling on wheels, able to fly or transform into different forms, etc.

After a robot has been created, the player sends it to fight other robots. The battles look like those of a fighting game, with side-scrolling view and HP bars; however, they are non-interactive. The entire gameplay focus in on creating a robot in such a way that it would be able to defeat a particular enemy; the battles themselves allow no control from the side of the player.

A "league mode" is also available, where the player(s) choose various models of robots and have them compete against each other in a tournament.</desc>
		<releasedate>19940425T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Office Koukan</developer>
		<publisher>Pack In Video</publisher>
		<genre>Simulation</genre>
		<players>1-5</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Pomping World (Japan).chd</path>
		<name>Buster Bros</name>
		<desc>Your goal is to destroy the balloons which bounce around the playfield. To accomplish this, you can shoot hooks which travel upwards, and blow up any balloon they touch. Depending on their size, they either split on two smaller ones, or evaporate if they're at their minimum size. Apart from balloons, some levels also have barriers that have to be destroyed with your hooks, since they often block your access to balloons. There are also some barriers which cannot ever be destroyed. Your character has the ability to climb ladders, but cannot jump.</desc>
		<releasedate>19910531T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Hudson</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Pop'n Magic (Japan).chd</path>
		<name>Pop'n Magic</name>
		<desc>A static screen action game in the style of Bubble Bobble or Don Doko Don, Pop 'n Magic allows you to trap enemies by firing your wand at them, then pick them up and throw them across the screen to destroy them. The bubbles they are trapped in are specific colours and care must be taken not to throw two of the same colour together as this will release the (now quite upset) creatures inside.</desc>
		<releasedate>19920724T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Riot</developer>
		<publisher>Telenet</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./PopfulMail (Japan).chd</path>
		<name>Popful Mail</name>
		<desc>The cute bounty hunter known as Popful Mail looks like she would have no trouble making a living slashing bad guys with her sword. In reality Mail is having a hard time making ends meet. One day, however, she learns about a magician who has gone rogue and has a hefty bounty on his head. Her adventure begins as Popful fights her way through a new adventure, and makes new friends along the way.

Popful Mail is a platform action game with very light RPG elements. As the heroine makes her way through the stages she collects money from slain foes. This money can be used in shops to buy weapons, armor, health, and so on. The game features interaction with many characters through both on-screen dialog and fully animated sequences. Some of these characters become playable as the player progresses through the game.

This release has the same story and general gameplay style as the earlier version, but otherwise was made from scratch.</desc>
		<releasedate>19940812T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Hunex</developer>
		<publisher>NEC</publisher>
		<genre>Role playing games</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Prince of Persia (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Prince Of Persia</name>
		<desc>While the Sultan of Persia is fighting a war in a foreign country, his Grand Vizier Jaffar orchestrates a coup d'état. His way to the throne lies through the Sultan's lovely daughter. Jaffar kidnaps her and threatens to kill her if she refuses to marry him. Meanwhile, the man the Princess loves is thrown into the dungeon. He has only one hour to escape from his prison, defeat the guards on his way, and stop Jaffar before the terrible marriage takes place.

Prince of Persia is a 2D platformer that is commonly regarded as a progenitor of the cinematic platform genre. Rather than following the more common jump-and-run mechanics, it focuses on careful advancement through fairly complex levels, emphasizing the protagonist's vulnerability and survival aspect. Rotoscoping technique is used to give more realism to the animation of the characters' movements.

The protagonist must avoid deadly traps, solve some simple jumping and environmental puzzles (such as stepping on pressure plates to raise portcullis), and engage in sword fights with the guards. The player character has an infinite amount of lives, but has to restart at the beginning of a level each time he dies, and must complete the game within an hour. The hero starts with three units of health, which can be replenished with small health potions or permanently increased with large jars.

The Game Boy Color and SNES versions of the game feature additional levels and new enemies. The Genesis version has a new intro, an altered set of graphics and four new levels.</desc>
		<releasedate>19921001T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Argent</developer>
		<publisher>Turbo Technologies</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./R-Type Complete CD (Japan).chd</path>
		<name>R-type Complete Cd</name>
		<desc>R-Type Complete CD combines part I and part II of the japanese PC Engine HuCard releases. It also adds remixed music, fully voiced cut scenes, an extra boss fight, and some other minor changes.
An alien race called the Bydo attacks humanity without mercy. The prototype space fighter R-9 must stop the Bydo and save the human race.</desc>
		<releasedate>19911220T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Irem</developer>
		<publisher>Irem</publisher>
		<genre>Shoot'em up / Horizontal</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Rainbow Islands - The Story of Bubble Bobble 2 (Japan).chd</path>
		<name>Rainbow Islands</name>
		<desc>Sequel to Bubble Bobble, Rainbow Islands sees Bub and Bob (in 2 player mode), who are now curiously small boys rather than dinosaurs, attempting to rid the Rainbow Islands of bad guys.

Using the power to cast rainbows, trapping anything underneath, the boys must ascend vertically 4 levels each island, with a big, bad boss at the end of each.

By trapping beasts under your rainbows, then jumping on them to break them you can collect seven different colored gems, and there are also power-ups for extra speed and rainbows.</desc>
		<releasedate>19930630T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Taito</developer>
		<publisher>NEC</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Ranma 1-2 (Japan).chd</path>
		<name>Ranma 1/2</name>
		<desc>Based on the popular manga/anime series of the same name, Ranma 1/2 follows the story of an aspiring martial artist who accidentally turns into a young woman by bathing in a cursed spring. He can revert to his natural form by touching hot water; however, contact with cold water will turn him into a girl again. Most of the original manga story is dedicated to semi-comical situations, based on the fact that Ranma is trying to conceal his predicament, which leads to misunderstandings, confusion, and romantic complications in his high school life.

This interpretation of the license follows a part of the initial manga story, starting with the curse and going through Ranma's first conflicts with schoolmates and rival martial artists. The game is mostly structured like a "beat-'em-up" side-scroller, though there are also several boss fights that are more reminiscent of a one-on-one fighting game. The Vs. mode allows the player to recreate these boss fights using different characters. 

Ranma's curse becomes a gameplay feature in the game: cold and hot water turn Ranma into a girl and a boy, respectively. Female Ranma is quicker and can jump higher, but her attack and defense are lower. Anime-style cut scenes advance the story between the levels.</desc>
		<releasedate>19901207T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>NCS Corporation</developer>
		<publisher>Masaya Games</publisher>
		<genre>Fight</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Ranma 1-2 - Datou, Ganso Musabetsu Kakutou-ryuu! (Japan).chd</path>
		<name>Ranma 1/2 : Datou Ganso Musabetsu Kakutou-ryuu!</name>
		<desc>Like most games based on the  Ranma 1/2 manga and anime series, Dat?, Ganso Musabetsu Kakut?-Ry?! is a fighting game. Unlike the  earlier Ranma 1/2 iteration by the  same company, this game does not follow the main manga/anime story, and does not include any other gameplay elements beside one-on-one fighting. However, the game is still rich on story-telling; fully voiced anime-style cut scenes appear after each battle and serve to put Ranma in various situations and set the stage for battles against familiar character from the manga and anime, such the old pervert Happousai, Mousse, Ryuga, etc.  

The Vs. mode allows two-player gameplay; the players can choose any combinations of the characters who appear in the game to test their skills. As Ranma, the player can revert to his female form (this time at will, simply by pressing a button); the female Ranma is more agile but less powerful. The combat system includes characteristic fighting game mechanics, with punches, kicks, jumps, combinations of buttons to execute specific moves, and powerful special attacks, which can be executed after charging the power.</desc>
		<releasedate>19921002T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Klon</developer>
		<publisher>Masaya Games</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Ranma 1-2 - Toraware no Hanayome (Japan).chd</path>
		<name>Ranma 1/2 : Toraware no Hanayome</name>
		<desc>Based on the  Ranma 1/2 manga and anime series, Toraware no Hanayome consists of several chapters, which are similar to episodes of a TV show: each one has its own story and theme, but all the chapters have recurrent characters from the Ranma 1/2 universe. As in the original manga and anime, the story focuses on the young martial artist and high school student Ranma, who was cursed after bathing in a sacred Chinese spring: contact with cold water turns him into a woman, while hot water restores him to his original masculine form. Most of the story in the game is dedicated to Ranma's relationships with his schoolmates and other characters, often involving comic and/or romantic situations, as well as Ranma's attempts to get rid of the curse: in the first chapter, he tries to win a contest that would allow him to travel to China and find a way to turn him into a man permanently.

Unlike most other Ranma 1/2 iterations, this game is a so-called "digital comic", which is the same as Japanese-style adventure. Controlling Ranma, the player interacts with the environment by selecting verb commands ("Look", "Talk", etc.) and objects from sub-menus. The navigation is also menu-based. Animated cut scenes appear frequently to advance the story.</desc>
		<releasedate>19911206T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>TENKY Co. Ltd.</developer>
		<publisher>Masaya Games</publisher>
		<genre>Various</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Rayxanber II (Japan).chd</path>
		<name>Rayxanber 2</name>
		<desc>The game resembles R-Type, particularly in art style and gameplay. The plot and setting uses the same trope as games like R-Type and Gradius; it concerns an ongoing war between mankind and a race of invading aliens belonging to the Zoul Empire, and the player's primary enemy consists of bioships and enormous organic fortresses.</desc>
		<releasedate>19910607T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Datawest</developer>
		<publisher>Datawest</publisher>
		<genre>Shoot'em up / Vertical</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Rayxanber III (Japan).chd</path>
		<name>Rayxanber 3</name>
		<desc>Rayxanber II sequel. Absolutely everything has been reviewed for the better, while simultaneously staying true to the style of the previous two games. To start, someone finally fixed the mechanics of the board, so now it really works and is easily controlled. As before, there is a temperature bar, so if it turns red it must cool down before running again, but now it is much easier to regulate the duration of your run without resorting to a turbo button. The level structure and the attack patterns of the enemy are also much more balanced to take into account the use of the board: you are no longer forced to throw yourself headlong into a phalanx of enemies because something is chasing your tail. It has legitimately become a useful tool in your arsenal.</desc>
		<releasedate>19920626T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Datawest</developer>
		<publisher>Datawest</publisher>
		<genre>Shoot'em up / Horizontal</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Riot Zone (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Riot Zone</name>
		<desc>The police is afraid to deal with a criminal organization known as the Dragon Zone. Street punks and leaders of Chinese crime syndicates dominate the area where its headquarters are supposedly located. The young fighter Hawk has his own score to settle with the Dragon Zone: they have kidnapped his girlfriend Candy. Together with his friend, the punk Tony, Hawk enters the dangerous districts and is determined to rescue his sweetheart and put an end to the organization.

Riot Zone (Crest of Wolf in Japan) is a rather simple brawler in which the player can choose to control either Hawk or Tony. Hawk is faster, but doesn't hit quite as hard as Tony. Both characters fight entirely unarmed, using kicks and punches to deal with the enemies; both also possess a powerful all-screen attack that depletes a portion of their health bar. Each stage culminates with a boss battle as Hawk and Tony gradually defeat the "wanted" criminals of the city.</desc>
		<releasedate>19930226T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Westone</developer>
		<publisher>Hudson</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Road Spirits (Japan).chd</path>
		<name>Road Spirits</name>
		<desc>Road Spirits is an arcade-style racing game, similar to  Rad Racer. The player controls a car from an "into the screen" 3rd person perspective, racing through the 17 pseudo-3D courses (named after various geographical locations, e.g. "West Coast" etc.). There are other cars on the road, which can slow down the player-controlled car by colliding with it, but the race is against time rather than against these cars. The player is given a time limit for each course, and an indicator shows how close the car is to the completion. Should the car run out of time, the race is lost, and the player has to replay it before tackling the next one.

The car can be controlled with two buttons only; collisions do not damage the car, but merely make it stop; though the player can change a car model and gear system, no realistic gear-based driving is used in the game. All this contribute to the overall arcade feeling of the races.</desc>
		<releasedate>19910322T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Arc</developer>
		<publisher>Pack In Video</publisher>
		<genre>Race 3rd Pers. view</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Ryuuko no Ken (Japan) (En,Ja,Es) (FACT).chd</path>
		<name>Ryuuko No Ken</name>
		<desc>Yuri Sakazaki has been kidnapped! Her big brother Ryo Sakazaki and Robert Garcia, his best friend, go search for her on the streets of South Town. As they go deeper and deeper they will find clues as to who ordered the kidnapping, the Sakazaki family's relation to the mob, and a person from their past.

The gameplay differs from most fighting games. In this game, you have a Spirit meter. A Spirit meter is in the game and will decrease as you perform special moves. It can be recharged, but doing so leaves you open to attack. When your health is almost gone, you can perform a secret combination that will unleash a deadly attack on your opponent - provided you have a full Spirit meter.

The arcade version doesn't allow you to play as Mr. Big and the elusive Mr. Karate.</desc>
		<releasedate>19940326T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Hudson</developer>
		<publisher>Hudson</publisher>
		<genre>Fight / 2D</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Seirei Senshi Spriggan (Japan).chd</path>
		<name>Seirei Senshi Spriggan</name>
		<desc>Another top-down shooter from Compile staged in a fantasy world that mingles traditional sci-fi elements with a feudal Japan setting.

As the game starts a struggle for total control over elemental powers is about to begin between two warring nations. As the best mecha pilot in the good guy's army it's your task to repel the invasion and win the war by dealing with the enemy armada in standard shooter fashion. But surprise surprise! You won't be alone this time, as other AI-controlled mecha pilots will join you in the fray at key moments. Only you can command the magical powers that can be added to your mecha by collecting several color-coded orbs though, so most of the fight is still going to be up to you.</desc>
		<releasedate>19910712T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Compile</developer>
		<publisher>Naxat Soft</publisher>
		<genre>Shoot'em Up</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Shadow of the Beast (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Shadow Of The Beast</name>
		<desc>While very young, Aarbron was kidnapped and enslaved by the Priests of the Beast Lord. He grew up on drugs made to destroy his own will and turn him into the Beast Messenger, a powerful creature serving Maletoth, The Beast Lord himself. He did his job, until one day he noticed a man about to be sacrificed in a ritual, his face triggering ancient memories. As the sacrificial knife descended into the man's body, Aarbron recognizes his father's face. As his father dies in the altar, memories of his childhood and tormented past at the hands of the Beast Lord emerged, and as feelings of hate over his captors took over him, he swore revenge and fled the temple, knowing the road to avenge his father and redemption would be hard.

Shadow of the Beast is a side-scrolling platformer. The player has to navigate through several areas filled with enemies and traps, collecting keys and activating triggers than open new areas or give Aarbron the means to overcome a sub-boss. The number of moves the player has at disposal is limited: duck, jump and only two attacks: punch and a flying kick. While most enemies die with just one hit, the player must time each attack accurately. However, there are also traps of objects that cannot be destroyed, and these require the player to jump, duck or move according the sequence. The player has only one life with 12 hit points that can be replenished by collecting some objects hidden in the level (like an off-route location or a under a megalith), which also contributes to the difficulty level.</desc>
		<releasedate>19920101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>DMA Design Limited</developer>
		<publisher>Psygnosis</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Shape Shifter (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Shape Shifter</name>
		<desc>The Dark Ones have captured the Ring of Five and imprisoned the wizards that guard it. A barbarian named Lykos has the power to transform into different creatures. He needs to rescue the wizards and the Ring of Five from the Dark Ones before they invade his home, Krellion.

Shape Shifter is a side-scrolling action game with platforming and light role-playing elements. Much of the game consists of traversing hostile areas, fighting regular enemies on the way and defeating bosses. The game's "hub" area is a town where Lykos can replenish his health and buy any of the three available weapons (axe, mace, or bow). These weapons can be upgraded by enchanting them or picking up power-ups.

After Lykos rescues a wizard he gains access to a transformation power. Transformations require special gems and cannot be performed if Lykos runs out of them. There are four transformations in the game: the panther can jump over large gaps; the shark can swim; the golem can jump higher; and the golden dragon can fly. Each of these forms can also collect power-ups that unlocks a few other attack abilities.

The game's stages are interconnected, but usually a new form must be acquired before Lykos can access a new area. Lykos has eight lives consisting of smaller health units (hearts). The game can only be saved in the town.</desc>
		<releasedate>19920101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>ICOM Simulations</developer>
		<publisher>Turbo Technologies, Inc.</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Sherlock Holmes - Consulting Detective (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Sherlock Holmes : Consulting Detective : Vol. I</name>
		<desc>In this game, the player is cast into the roles of Sherlock Holmes, the greatest fictional detective of all times, and his friend and partner Dr. Watson, as they have to investigate and successfully solve three criminal cases:
The Mummy's Curse deals with the horrifying death of three men, which were apparently murdered by an ancient mummy;

The Mystified Murderess involves a woman who has been convicted for murdering her beloved one, but cannot seem to recall anything of what had happened to her;

The Tin Soldier concerns the murder of an old general, whose past must be investigated in order to find the killer.Sherlock Holmes: Consulting Detective can be described as a hybrid of adventure game and simulation. Gameplay process involves traveling to various locations in London, interrogating suspects, gathering clues, checking out the newspapers, and eventually presenting all the evidence to the judge; if the latter finds the circumstances incriminating, he will accept the results of the investigation, and the case will be considered solved. Though the basic gameplay is rather typical for adventure games, the amount of real detective work and the focus of the game on purely case-related actions rather than exploration and manipulation of items makes it comparable to a simulation of a criminal investigation.

The game is notable for being one of the earliest "multimedia" titles, having been released on a CD ROM and featuring rather long (though windowed) video sequences with live actors as introductions and cutscenes, which frequently occur when the heroes investigate suspects.</desc>
		<releasedate>19910726T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>ICOM Simulations</developer>
		<publisher>Victor Entertainment</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Sherlock Holmes - Consulting Detective - Volume 2 (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Sherlock Holmes : Consulting Detective : Vol. II</name>
		<desc>"What they said about Sherlock I, you'll say about Sherlock II"...reads the advert in the box, based on the nice critics about Volume I.

- The same video technology (this is 1992), keeps offering true interactive environment: actually letting you "feel" the traffic in the streets of the old London?

- The same structure brings a familiar look, inviting to channel all attention to the task of solving mysteries: your intelligence, skills and patience are required to find clues by listening to people, observing details, or even reading the London Times - but don't let yourself be misguided by a wrong hint.

- The same number of cases: 3

But, each situation is completely different: ?The Two Lions? involving the murder of circus lions, ?The Pilfered Paintings? just bought by The National Gallery...and ?The Murdered Munitions Magnate?, where hints reveal different possible motives...have nothing in common, except the detective in charge: you?</desc>
		<releasedate>19930528T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>ICOM Simulations</developer>
		<publisher>Victor Entertainment</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./SimEarth - The Living Planet (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Sim Earth : The Living Planet</name>
		<desc>SimEarth puts you in charge of an entire planet throughout its 10 billion year lifespan. Your ultimate task is to guide the planet?s inhabitants into the stars, from its humble single-celled roots.

The main threats you face include pollution, disease, famine, war and global warming. The controls available to you include the chance to move mountains and continents, creating different levels of species, and unleash tidal waves and earthquakes so as to reshape your planet. All of these things take from your limited energy, which must be replenished.
</desc>
		<releasedate>19930114T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Maxis Software</developer>
		<publisher>Hudson</publisher>
		<genre>Simulation</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Sol Bianca (Japan).chd</path>
		<name>Sol Bianca</name>
		<desc>The game is based on the anime movie of the same name. In 24th century, piracy is still an issue, but no more in seas and oceans, sailing ordinary ships - the pirates are in space! The most dangerous pirate crew is the one of Sol Bianca - April, Janny, May, June, and Feb. No, those are not names of months, but five beautiful ladies, who can handle some high-tech weaponry and who think only about treasure. But the five lovely pirates are not evil - whenever some tyrant threatens a planet, they are there to help.

The gameplay of  Sol Bianca is that of a traditional Japanese-style RPG. The player controls the five girls as a party, each one having individual statistics. The party of heroines visits planets, travels on the world map, and engages randomly appearing enemies in first-person perspective, turn-based combat.</desc>
		<releasedate>19900629T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>NCS Corporation</developer>
		<publisher>Masaya Games</publisher>
		<genre>Role playing games</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Splash Lake (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Splash Lake</name>
		<desc>Splash Lake is an action strategy puzzle game.  Each round consists of a single screen play area composed of tiles suspended over a lake.  You control an Ostrich that can crack the tiles and cause them to fall into the water.  Your goal is to use this ability to make all the bad guys on the screen fall into the water. The game features more than 60 levels, a simultaneous two-player mode, and humorous cutscenes every 10 levels.</desc>
		<releasedate>19920101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Bits Laboratory</developer>
		<publisher>Turbo Technologies, Inc.</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Star Parodier (Japan).chd</path>
		<name>Fantasy Star Soldier</name>
		<desc>Move fast and blast! It's a nonstop explosion of fire power and you're streaking through space, right in the middle of it! The Brains Cult you once defeated is back, badder than ever. But your finger's on the trigger of an incredible new techno-attack! Scorch the Scorpion with a nuclear a sting. Fire your heat-seeking sidewinders. Then power-up to launch your doomsday Super Bomb! Blow those Brains out and save the galaxy. Then challenge your friends with a special competition time mode to prove who the Super Star really is!</desc>
		<releasedate>19920424T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Inter State</developer>
		<publisher>Hudson</publisher>
		<genre>Shoot'em up / Vertical</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Strider Hiryuu (Japan).chd</path>
		<name>Strider Hiryuu</name>
		<desc>The year is 2048 AD. In Russia, the evil Grand Master Meio has begun his insane plot to take over the universe. A lone figure drops from a stealth glider into Meio's base. He is Hiryu, Super A-Class Strider. His mission is to defeat the Grand Master and put an end to his plotting once and for all.

Strider lets the protagonist run, jump, perform acrobatics and climb walls and overhangs. He wields a plasma sword, called a Cypher, through five levels fighting robots and guards, with mid- and end-level bosses.</desc>
		<releasedate>19940922T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>NEC</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Platform / Fighter Scrolling</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Super Air Zonk - Rockabilly-Paradise (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Super Air Zonk : Rockabilly Paradise</name>
		<desc>After the success of PC Denjin, our hero leaps onto CD with a whole new game and a whole new soundtrack. Flying over the various landscapes (you get to choose which order to play the first four levels in), you come up against tidal waves, giant robots and a general array of nasty but cute bad guys as you would expect. The plants from the original PC Kid games are still here to provide such joys as extra firepower, fountains of smiley faces or the tiny-denjin which makes dodging bullets that little bit easier. Another handy little trick is that your boots also pack a punch, so backing into an enemy is more likely to dispose of them than do you any permanent damage. Part way along each of the levels you get the chance to rescue a friend who then joins with you, giving you a specific extra ability. These friends are pre-set one per level and cannot be chosen, and they allow things like rapid-sushi-fire and handy rear shots.</desc>
		<releasedate>19930730T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Red Company</developer>
		<publisher>Hudson</publisher>
		<genre>Shoot'em Up</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Super Daisenryaku (T-En v0.99).chd</path>
		<name>Super Daisenryaku</name>
		<desc>Super Daisenryaku is one of the many titles in SystemSoft's long-running war strategy series. The game mechanics are based on Daisenryaku II, but many of the included maps are unique to this release, including several based on Phantasy Star in Sega's console version. There is no campaign mode, and any of the included maps can be played. Some maps are for two players, some for four, and any map can be played with any combination of human and computer players. The computer versions also feature an editor.
The game is played on a large map made up of hexagonal spaces, each of which consists of one of the included terrain types. Each player controls a number of units (bought with money), which each take up one space on the grid. The unit types are for the most part based on real-life military equipment from around the time the game was released, what is available to the player depends on the chosen faction.</desc>
		<releasedate>19900427T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Systemsoft</developer>
		<publisher>Microcabin</publisher>
		<genre>Strategy</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Super Darius (Japan).chd</path>
		<name>Super Darius</name>
		<desc>Super Darius is a port of Darius for the PC Engine CD-ROM, and the only attempt at an accurate port of the game for many years; it even uses recordings of music and sound effects straight from the arcade PCB! Its other claim to fame is the introduction of all 26 bosses from the original draft for Darius, some of which were earlier seen on promotional material.</desc>
		<releasedate>19900316T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Taito</developer>
		<publisher>NEC</publisher>
		<genre>Shooter / Horizontal</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Super Darius II (Japan).chd</path>
		<name>Super Darius 2</name>
		<desc>Super Darius II is a updated Darius II released for the TurboGrafx-CD featuring an entirely new set of bosses, major changes to levels, and a fully arranged soundtrack including new songs.</desc>
		<releasedate>19931224T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Taito</developer>
		<publisher>Taito</publisher>
		<genre>Shooter / Horizontal</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./SydMead's TerraForming (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Syd Mead's Terra Forming</name>
		<desc>In Terraforming, the human race has fled into the depths of space after Earth has become uninhabitable.  As a result, they travel from planet to planet in an attempt to find a planet suitable enough to terraform into a new Earth.  Along the way they encounter alien races which they must destroy in an attempt to survive and continue the human race.

The gameplay is a basic side-scrolling shooter, shooting down enemy space ships, picking up power-ups and health icons and upgrading main and secondary weapons along with the obligatory huge stage bosses.  The most notable feature of the game is the work done by Syd Mead, a special effects artist for such films as Star Trek: The Motion Picture, Blade Runner, Aliens, 2010 and as recent as Mission Impossible III.</desc>
		<releasedate>19930101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Right Stuff Corp.</developer>
		<publisher>NEC</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Todd's Adventures in Slime World (Japan).chd</path>
		<name>Slime World</name>
		<desc>While flying your spaceship, you crash land on a planet covered entirely in slime.  You and a friend explore the labyrinthine planet of slime, armed with a water pistol and all manner of gadgets you find along the way in an effort to find your way back out.  The game world is a giant maze with quirky hidden areas and plenty of original layout ideas.  Depending on the game mode, you are either cooperating or competing with your "friend" to find and get to an exit first.  Due to the massive sizes of the slime worlds (about 6 entries to choose from), games often take several hours to complete.

The basis of the game is exploration, with varying game modes further focusing on competition, puzzle solving, speed, exploration, or cooperation.</desc>
		<releasedate>19921009T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Epyx</developer>
		<publisher>Micro World</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Tokimeki Memorial (Japan).chd</path>
		<name>Tokimeki Memorial</name>
		<desc>In the first installment of the  Tokimeki Memorial series, the player takes the role of a male student at the Kirameki High School in modern-day Japan, whose goal is to win the heart of one of his female school mates.

Tokimeki Memorial is a dating simulation game. There is a schedule in the game, which includes school-related and free-time activities. The player characters has various statistics that can be raised by performing certain activities (such as studying to increase intelligence, etc.). The gameplay is dedicated almost entirely to planning schedules, getting the maximum out of the date with the chosen girl. A date is not necessarily automatic success - neglecting a girl for a long time will lead to gossip and eventually may destroy the relationship. There is also a "rival" in the game, a male student who might succeed with one of the girls if the player is not careful enough.</desc>
		<releasedate>19940527T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Konami</developer>
		<publisher>Konami</publisher>
		<genre>Simulation</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Valis II (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Valis 2</name>
		<desc>Valis II has the same basic plot as its computer counterpart: Rogles, the tyrant of the magical world Vecanti, was defeated, and a new emperor named Megas is terrorizing its inhabitants. It's up to the Japanese schoolgirl Yuko to take on her persona of the Valis Soldier and vanquish Megas.

Gameplay-wise, this version differs from the computer releases significantly. Though it has six stages that end with the same boss enemies, its level design, layout, and many regular enemies are different. This release also completely removes two key gameplay features of the computer version: the ability to equip different weapons and armor, and the flying side-scrolling shooter stages. </desc>
		<releasedate>19900101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Shin-Nihon Laser Soft</developer>
		<publisher>NEC</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Valis III (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Valis 3</name>
		<desc>After Yuko has defeated the evil Rogles, peace descended upon Earth and the magical world of Vecanti. But a new threat has arisen: an enigmatic man named Glames from the Dark World, possessor of a sword named Leethus, is planning to conquer both Earth and Vecanti, convinced that there is no other way to save his world from imminent destruction. A young girl from the Dark World named Cham escapes from Glames, and asks Yuko to help her stop him with the aid of her Valis sword.

Like its predecessors in the series, Valis III is a side-scrolling platform action game. Unlike the previous installments, the player can control three characters in the game: Yuko, Cham (who uses a whip and fights similarly to Castlevania protagonists), and princess Valna from Vecanti, who is weaker physically, but can cast more powerful magic. Each of the characters can equip different weapons and has access to her own magic spells.</desc>
		<releasedate>19900907T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Shin-Nihon Laser Soft</developer>
		<publisher>Telenet</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Valis IV (Japan).chd</path>
		<name>Valis IV</name>
		<desc>King Asfal from the Dark World had a son named Galgear, who inherited a magic ring from him and grew insane as a result. The prince was imprisoned, but managed to break free, kidnap Valna, the queen of Vecanti, and install himself as the Dream Land's new ruler. Cham, the leader of the resistance against Galgear, hears the voice of Yuko, the former Valis soldier who has now become a goddess, telling her that one of the resistance members, a girl named Lena, is the heir to the Valis sword. Lena and her sister Amu decide to rescue Valna and find a way to stop Galgear.

Like its predecessors, Valis IV is an action platformer. It is similar to the previous game in allowing the player to control three different characters: Lena, Amu, and Asfal. Each of the characters wields a unique weapon (Valis sword for Lena, boomerang for Amu, and lance trident for Asfal) and has access to their own elemental spells (thunder for Lena, fire for Amu, ice for Asfal). Each one also has a special ability: Lena can slide through narrow passages, Amu can double-jump, and Asfal is immune to certain traps. Along with recovery and spell-enhancing (up to three levels) items, characters can also acquire special spheres that increase the overall count of their hit- and magic points.</desc>
		<releasedate>19910823T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Shin-Nihon Laser Soft</developer>
		<publisher>Shin-Nihon Laser Soft</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Vasteel (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Vasteel</name>
		<desc>The governing planet of the Vasteel Solar System is called Belose. Emperors of the Faracia dynasty have been ruling the planet for hundreds of years. However, the last emperor turned out to be rather unpopular with the people, and they began talking about changing the government system. Unexpectedly, the emperor becomes gravely ill and dies soon thereafter. His elder son, Faliall, is proclaimed the heir. However, Faliall's younger brother, Stefan, cares for the wishes of the simple folk, and is willing to change things. Hence, the bloody war between the two brothers for power and justice begins...

Vasteel is a hex-based war strategy game in its core. The story mode takes the player (who controls either Stefan's or Faliall's armies) through various top-down maps, on which the two armies will try to annihilate each other, advance to a better position, conquer enemy cities, etc. There is also a versus mode, which allows two-player gameplay, as well as access to all the maps regardless of the story.

The armies of the two princes are entirely robotic; even tanks, cannons, and spaceships are shaped like "transformer" robots. Both armies have factories, which can produce new robots, even several times per turn; each such productions costs money, of which there is limited amount. The player navigates the robots in turn-based fashion over the map. Combat ensues when two robots are on the same grid.

Unlike in most games of this kind, the actual battles in Vasteel are interactive and action-based. The players must quickly move their robots and shoot at each other. Same applies to robots which enter factories and cities with the intention to destroy their protective mechanisms; the defending side uses stationary turrets to fire at the robot, while the latter tries to avoid them and get to the core before being destroyed.</desc>
		<releasedate>19930101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Human</developer>
		<publisher>Working Designs</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Virgin Dream (Japan).chd</path>
		<name>Virgin Dream</name>
		<desc>A "Pretty Girl Contest" is held, which is more than just a regular beauty competition: within a year, a young girl should become a star. Beauty matters, but so does skill. As the manager of one of the young girls who wants to participate in the contest, the player has to do everything in his/her power to attain the goal, and help the disciple reach stardom!

Virgin Dream is what is commonly called life simulation, a genre popularized by games such as the  Princess Maker series. The player manages the life of the young girl with a specific goal in mind, which must be chosen from the main menu. The girl can strive to become a singer, a photo model, a school teacher, etc. The player then tries to alter her statistics accordingly to achieve the goal.

The main activities on work days are divided into three groups: training, working, and learning. The learning category is the smallest one, but is also necessary for continuing the girl's normal school life. Training includes singing, arts, body building, sports, etc. Part-time jobs such as waitress, cook, private tutor, and even construction worker are available; the pay varies greatly, but so are the changes in parameters.

On holidays, the girl is able to venture outside and explore the top-down city, which contains various shops, boutiques, offices, etc. Clothes and other accessories can be purchased. It is also possible to talk and bond with other girls, potential rivals, who live in the same dormitory. All this influences the heroine's parameters, for good and for bad. </desc>
		<releasedate>19960531T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>C-lab.</developer>
		<publisher>Tokuma Shoten</publisher>
		<genre>Simulation</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Where in the World Is Carmen Sandiego (Japan) (En,Ja).chd</path>
		<name>Where In The World Is Carmen Sandiego</name>
		<desc>You start out as a rookie detective whose job is to track down a crop of thieves stealing the world's most precious treasures. After each assignment briefing, you'll be given a deadline to capture the thief that stole the artifact using clues dealing with your knowledge of geography. 

The game is an updated version of the original Where in the World is Carmen Sandiego?, featuring enhanced graphics, sound effects, and additional control schemes, such as joystick support for computer platforms.</desc>
		<releasedate>19900330T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Brøderbund Software</developer>
		<publisher>Pack In Video</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Xak III - The Eternal Recurrence (T-En - De-Japanization).chd</path>
		<name>Xak 3 - The Eternal Recurrence</name>
		<desc>The great hero Latok, the descendant of the war god Duel, has returned to his hometown Fearless, where he lives peacefully with his mother. But one day, a messenger brings terrible news: the castle of Farland was attacked, the king, the princess, and countless soldiers brutally slain. Zomu Dizae, the third and the final demon commander of the dark world Zekisis (Latok has defeated the other two, Badu and Gospel), has arrived. He is aided by the treacherous Necromancer, who turned the soldiers of Farland into monsters. Will Latok be able to defeat the evil once again?

Xak III: The Eternal Recurrence is an action RPG, similar in gameplay style to its  predecessors, but also incorporating some elements first introduced in  Tower of Gazel, such as the ability to jump and having companions (although this feature is much more limited here). Jumping ability is crucial in many cases, as there are obstacles that can only be avoided by jumping over them. Latok starts at level 50, but still can gain experience points and become stronger. A new (and very useful) feature is hit points restoration, which occurs when Latok is standing still. To counter that, enemies can re-spawn, which means that there aren't many completely safe areas in the game.</desc>
		<releasedate>19940930T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Microcabin</developer>
		<publisher>NEC</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Ys Book I &amp; II (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Ys Book I &amp; II</name>
		<desc>Ys: Book I &amp;amp; II contains enhanced remakes of two games: Ys: The Vanished Omens and its sequel, Ys II: Ancient Ys Vanished - The Final Chapter. The enhanced versions were not released separately.

The players controls a young red-haired hero named Adol Christin, whose task is to find the six books of Ys, an ancient paradise-like land that mysteriously disappeared long time ago. It is said that whoever possesses the six books can gain access into Ys. In the first game, Adol is on the quest to find the books and to enter Ys. The second game takes place in Ys itself, and Adol must defeat an even greater evil and liberate the land.

This release features enhanced CD-quality sound, higher-quality graphics, and new anime-style cutscenes.</desc>
		<releasedate>19890101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nihon Falcom</developer>
		<publisher>NEC</publisher>
		<genre>Role playing games</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Ys III - Wanderers from Ys (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Ys III : Wanderers from Ys</name>
		<desc>Adol Christin's long-time friend, Dogi, wishes to return to his home town of Redmont after hearing about strange disturbances that are happening there.  Always looking for an adventure, Adol joins him and soon finds out the cause of this new evil.

Ys III: Wanderers from Ys breaks away from the "bumping into enemies" battle system of the first two games, allowing Adol to control his sword in a variety of directions. Beside changing the battle system, the game's perspective switches to a side-scrolling view, as opposed to the top-down one of the previous games. Adol also has the ability to jump now.  New to the series is the use of magical rings, which give Adol different powering-up abilities such as healing and shielding. The game also uses various key items found along the way to solve minor puzzles and progress the story.</desc>
		<releasedate>19910101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nihon Falcom</developer>
		<publisher>NEC</publisher>
		<genre>Role playing games</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Ys IV - The Dawn of Ys (T-En v0.95).chd</path>
		<name>Ys IV : The Dawn of Ys</name>
		<desc>The Dawn of Ys is one of two games released under the title of Ys IV, the other being Tonkin House's Ys IV: Mask of the Sun. The two games share the same basic story, but have many differences regarding concrete events, locations, gameplay details, etc. The events of the game take place a short while after those described in Ys II, and before the events of Ys III: Wanderers from Ys.

As the game begins, Adol and his friend return to the town of Minea, where the first game began. The evil Lord Darm has been defeated, and it's time to relax and spend some time with friends - but not for long. A new evil is rising, and Adol decides to set sail for the overseas land of Celceta to investigate these occurrences.

Ys IV returns to the style of play used in the first and second games. The gameplay area is viewed from a top-down perspective, and the player attacks enemies by running into them to cause damage. Combat is slightly more sophisticated than in the first two games, since Adol can now move in eight directions, and attacking enemies diagonally or from the sides is more efficient than bumping into them headstrong. Adol gains experience from defeating enemies, which serves to raise his attack and defense power, like in the previous games. He can equip various swords, armor, shields, and rings to enhance his attributes. The magic system introduced in Ys II is also brought back for this game.</desc>
		<releasedate>19931222T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Hudson</developer>
		<publisher>Hudson</publisher>
		<genre>Role playing games</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Zero 4 Champ II (Japan).chd</path>
		<name>Zero 4 Champ 2</name>
		<desc>Zero4 Champ II is a sequel to Zero4 Champ. This time, a young Japanese street racer has been defeated by an American who claims that Japan's level is not up to par. His feelings hurt, the youth ventures to the United States, trying to earn enough money and participate in races to defend his national pride.

The game is very similar to its predecessor in concept, but offers additional options in the story mode. Part-time jobs now include delivery assignments that play like overhead racing games, as well as tending to dogs of various breeds for money. The security guard assignment plays like a mini-RPG, complete with turn-based combat, experience points, and levels. In addition, it is possible to visit racing tracks and bet money on participants. The versus mode allows players to choose between three courses to compete in, racing against each other (in a top-down mode) or computer AI (first-person).</desc>
		<releasedate>19930305T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Media Rings</developer>
		<publisher>Media Rings</publisher>
		<genre>Race, Driving</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Twinbee Returns (Japan).chd</path>
		<name>Detana!! Twinbee</name>
		<desc>Another top-down shooter in the TwinBee series of "cute'em ups".

Detana!! Introduces for the first time the characters behind the TwinBee &amp; WinBee fighters, Pastel and Light, and chronicles their journey to save Princess Melora from an evil force that threatens the world. Nevertheless its still all about shooting the heck out of surreal and cute enemies through 6 stages of vertically-scrolling action.

Power-ups and upgrades can be gained by shooting the colored bells that some enemies leave behind until they stay the color you want them to, with many combinations possible. A new charge-shot feature has been added to your basic arsenal, and the game features single and 2-player cooperative gameplay.</desc>
		<releasedate>19920228T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Konami</developer>
		<publisher>Konami</publisher>
		<genre>Shoot'em Up</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Mamono Hunter Youko - Tooki Yobigoe (Japan).chd</path>
		<name>Mamono Hunter Youko - Tooki Yobigoe</name>
		<desc>Tooki Yobigoe is a direct sequel to Mamono Hunter Y?ko: Makai kara no Tenk?sei, continuing where the story of the previous game left off. Yohko, Shoma and Setsuna are attacked by demons on the flying ship, and have to use their recently found powers to fend them off. As opposed to the previous game, where Shoma was the protagonist, Yohko is the player character in the sequel.

Gameplay-wise, the puzzle-less Japanese adventure format is further utilized. Verb commands must be selected from a menu and sometimes combined with objects or character names for interaction. It is often necessary to repeat commands several times to trigger the next event. </desc>
		<releasedate>19930108T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Tenky</developer>
		<publisher>Masaya Games</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
</gameList>
