<?xml version="1.0"?>
<gameList>
	<game>
		<path>./Albert Odyssey - Legend of Eldean (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Albert Odyssey : Legend of Eldean</name>
		<desc>The game follows the adventure of Pike, a young boy whose family was murdered by a horde of monsters while still an infant, and is raised by a family of winged humanoids known as Harpies. Ten years later, his adoptive sister is turned to stone by an evil mage. Together with Cirrus, a talking sword housing the spirit of one of the legendary Eldean siblings, Pike travels the world to search for a cure, and discovers a plot by a group of evil magicians to turn the world's races against each other and revive the ancient god Vlag. Together with the help of friends he meets along his journey, Pike must prevent the evil's resurrection.</desc>
		<releasedate>19970724T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Sunsoft</developer>
		<publisher>Working Designs</publisher>
		<genre>Role playing games</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Astal (USA) (3S).chd</path>
		<name>Astal</name>
		<desc>Antowas has created a land of striking beauty and magic, with Astal and his beloved Leda among its happy inhabitants. However, Jerado has set out to destroy it, capturing Leda and forcing Astal to set off to save her.

Astal is a side-scrolling platform game with lots of Anime-esque background detail. You have birds helping you if you can rescue them. Special moves such as a smart bomb can be collected.</desc>
		<releasedate>19950815T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>SEGA</developer>
		<publisher>SEGA</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Burning Rangers (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Burning Rangers</name>
		<desc>As a member of the Burning Rangers, it is your job to put out a range of fires and rescue those trapped in the heat of the blaze.

During each level, your quad leader informs you of the critical areas inside certain buildings, such as multi-level warehouses.
Following his advice, you must use your cybernetic powersuit to put out the flames in each area. Along the way you will also come across boss characters, who are out to light up the town, and you.
Your performance is then rated on your time to complete the objectives, how many lives were saved, and so forth. The better you go, the higher the rating.</desc>
		<releasedate>19980603T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Sonic Team</developer>
		<publisher>SEGA</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Clockwork Knight - Pepperouchau's Adventure (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Clockwork Knight : Pepperouchau's Adventure</name>
		<desc>Sir Tongara de Pepperouchau III ("Pepper" for short) is a toy soldier. He is in love with the Clockwork Fairy Princess, Chelsea, whose voice wakes up the toys of the house every night at midnight. But he is clumsy and something of a laughingstock, especially when compared to his friendly rival Ginger who is also after Chelsea's heart. One night Chelsea is stolen away by an unknown force, which also hypnotizes some of the lesser toys to become fierce minions and stand in the way of anyone who would try to rescue her. If there's no voice to wake them up anymore then the toys will never live again, so Pepper and Ginger head off to find Chelsea before it's too late.</desc>
		<releasedate>19950511T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Team Aquila</developer>
		<publisher>SEGA</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Clockwork Knight 2 - Pepperouchau's Adventure (USA, Brazil).chd</path>
		<name>Clockwork Knight 2 : Pepperouchau's Adventure</name>
		<desc>Clockwork Knight 2 is the second (and to this date, last) game featuring the adventures of Sir Tongara de Pepperouchau III. It maintains the same game style (a mixture of 2D side-scrolling platformer with 3D elements, moderately in the fashion of Sega Saturn's Bug!), colorful music and gameplay of its predecessor. However, your mission will be somewhat different this time (although still related with Clockwork Princess Chelsea), as the ending scene of the first game did not come as good as expected and because of that, you should try to give the best of yourself again in order to completely recover Chelsea for Pepperouchau.</desc>
		<releasedate>19960217T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Team Aquila</developer>
		<publisher>SEGA</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Daytona USA - Circuit Edition (Japan).chd</path>
		<name>Daytona USA : Championship Circuit Edition</name>
		<desc>All of its predecessor and then some. More tracks, many more cars (hidden cars as well), smarter AI, more music (no more lyrics for the in-game race music either), broader 2-player gameplay, more refined arcade physics...and on top of everything else- BETTER GRAPHICS! The first Daytona on the Saturn boasted some hefty visuals, great for displaying the Saturn's power to the masses at the console's birth; but for the Saturn to be revered for everything it was, Sega (and AM2) had to make something a little flashier. All the graphics in the game have been updated...both the cars and tracks have higher polygon count, better texture mapping; the framerate is QUITE noticeably improved, everything is very smooth.</desc>
		<releasedate>19961121T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>SEGA</developer>
		<publisher>SEGA</publisher>
		<genre>Race, Driving</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Dragon Force (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Dragon Force</name>
		<desc>The world of Legendra was ruled by benevolent goddesses, but the last of them, Astea, was challenged by a dark god named Madruk. In order to defeat Madruk, Astea created a powerful dragon, who eventually emerged victorious and was able to seal Madruk away. Years have passed. Legendra is now divided into eight kingdoms. One of them, Fandaria, is ruled by a monarch named Goldark. The other kings have heard rumors that Goldark is planning to take over Legendra by conquering all the other kingdoms. Everyone is preparing for the war, without realizing that the ancient evil is about to raise its head once again... Dragon Force is a real-time strategy game (RTS). The player can choose one of the six monarchs (plus two additional ones that become available once the game is completed) with their unique scenarios. The gameplay is divided into three modes: management, overworld movement, and battle.</desc>
		<releasedate>19961212T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>SEGA</developer>
		<publisher>SEGA</publisher>
		<genre>Strategy</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Dragon Force II (En v1.04).chd</path>
		<name>Dragon Force 2 - Kami Sarishi Daichi ni</name>
		<desc>Dragon Force II: Kamisarishi Daichi ni is a real-time strategy and role-playing and the follow-up to Dragon Force. It is set 500 years after the events of the first game. The player follows a group of monarchs that come together to face a new threat looming over Legendra. The story also delves into what happened to the original Dragon Force after Madruk's defeat. Compared to the first game it adds a laboratory system which lets the player research new skills. It also introduces the capacity to have two separate types of soldiers in the same army, thus allowing ground troops to be aided by air troops, for instance.</desc>
		<releasedate>19980402T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Chime</developer>
		<publisher>SEGA</publisher>
		<genre>Strategy</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Guardian Heroes (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Guardian Heroes</name>
		<desc>Ages ago, the spirits of Earth and Sky waged war on each other. Neither could win, and eventually the Sky Spirits bestowed some humans with their powers, turning them into wizards and allies in the war. The Earth Spirits were banished into darkness; but the Sky Spirits feared the human wizards and cast them underground as well. Years have passed, and a powerful wizard named Kanon escaped from the gloomy prison and turned the human land into a puppet state trembling before his might. 
One legendary sword is said to bring an end to Kanon's reign. Four warriors (Han, Randy, Nicole and Ginjirou) retrieved the sword, but knights sent by Kanon are determined to take it away and destroy it at all costs. Aided by the renegade knight Serena, the four heroes must keep the world safe and protect themselves against the onslaught.</desc>
		<releasedate>19960424T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Treasure</developer>
		<publisher>SEGA</publisher>
		<genre>Beat'em Up</genre>
		<players>1-6</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Langrisser III (Japan) [T-En by Cyber Warrior X v0.2] [i].chd</path>
		<name>Langrisser 3</name>
		<desc>This is a prequel to the two Langrisser games (the first one is known in the US as Warsong). The events of the third game occur thousand years before those described in the first "Langrisser". The story centers around the creation of a holy sword named Langrisser, and the first Descendants of Light, the only people who can wield it. The main character is the knight Diharuto, the ancestor of Leon (Elwin's rival in "Langrisser II"). He must defeat the evil Boser, who is bound to the evil sword Alhazzard. In Langrisser III, you don't control whole armies, but only their generals, whom you move around the battle field. Once two enemy generals meet each other, a 3D battle sequence occurs, during which the two armies fight; the outcome of the battle is decided only by the victory or defeat of the general. The game also features love simulation elements: depending on the main hero's responses to various female characters, you can raise their "love level".</desc>
		<releasedate>19961018T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Masaya Games</developer>
		<publisher>Masaya Games</publisher>
		<genre>Strategy</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Legend of Oasis, The (USA).chd</path>
		<name>The Legend of Oasis</name>
		<desc>The Story of Thor 2, known in Japan as Thor: Seireioukiden and the US as The Legend of Oasis, is video game on the Sega Saturn console. It is the prequel to The Story of Thor: A Successor of the Light/Beyond Oasis on the Sega Mega Drive. The music was composed by Yuzo Koshiro, who is also famous for composing music for the Streets of Rage series.</desc>
		<releasedate>19960731T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Ancient</developer>
		<publisher>SEGA</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Lunar - Silver Star Story (En v1.1.2f).chd</path>
		<name>Lunar - Silver Star Story</name>
		<desc>Lunar: Silver Star Story Complete, originally released in Japan as simply Lunar: Silver Star Story, is a role-playing game developed by Game Arts and Japan Art Media as a remake of 1992's Lunar: The Silver Star. While the overall plot remains true to the original, accommodations are made to the game's story to allow for a larger, richer cast, as well as additional scenarios.</desc>
		<releasedate>19961025T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Game Arts</developer>
		<publisher>Kadokawa Shoten</publisher>
		<genre>Role playing games</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Lunar 2 - Eternal Blue (Japan) [T-En by Mr Conan v0.19b] [i].m3u</path>
		<name>Lunar 2 - Eternal Blue</name>
		<desc>Lunar 2: Eternal Blue is the sequel to Lunar: The Silver Star, a role-playing game for Saturn. The events of Eternal Blue take place 1000 years after those of Silver Star.</desc>
		<releasedate>19980713T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Kadokawa Shoten</developer>
		<publisher>Game Arts</publisher>
		<genre>Role playing games</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./NiGHTS into Dreams... (USA, Brazil).chd</path>
		<name>NiGHTS into Dreams...</name>
		<desc>Immerse yourself in an unparalleled 3D flying experience. NiGHTS truly delivers an amazing virtual world of dreams -- filled with unbelievable real-time effects, fantastic creatures and nightmarish monsters.

* Master a showcase of Sega Saturn's Processing Power.
* Face your worst nightmares in a stunning world of 3D gameplay.
* Dozens of camera angles, never-seen-before effects and 3D positional sound.
* Developed exclusively for Sega Saturn by the creators of "Sonic the Hedgehog."</desc>
		<releasedate>19960823T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Sonic Team</developer>
		<publisher>SEGA</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Panzer Dragoon II Zwei (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Panzer Dragoon II Zwei</name>
		<desc>Flash backwards to several years before the vicious battle against the empire in Panzer Dragoon 1. In the country of Machania, dragons are bred for the exclusive use of the dragoons, or Knights. Dragons with wings are normally executed as they are deemed to be a bad omen by the citizens. In the war with the Empire, Machania has begun to examine the ancient ways rather than to try to fight a futile war using technological advances. The Empire is technologically more advanced. Randy, the hero, and his newfound friend, the dragon he saved, want to turn the tide of battle.</desc>
		<releasedate>19960417T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>SEGA</developer>
		<publisher>SEGA</publisher>
		<genre>Shoot'em Up</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Panzer Dragoon Saga (USA).m3u</path>
		<name>Panzer Dragoon Saga</name>
		<desc>Panzer Dragoon Saga is set in the same universe as the other Panzer Dragoon games, but it differs from the rest of the series by having strong RPG elements.

The hero of the game is Edge, one of the soldiers of the mighty Empire. The Empire has recently ordered some excavations at ancient ruins, trying to discover the secret of an old technology that is much superior to that of present time. During the excavation works, Edge encounters a mysterious young girl. He then witnesses the murder of his captain and other soldiers by Crayden, one of the Empire's officers. Coming into contact with an ancient dragon, Edge begins to roam the world, determined to find Crayden and to avenge the death of his comrades. Nobody helps him but his faithful dragon. But the Empire is also after Crayden, so there appear to be at least three sides in the conflict... or are there more?

"Panzer Dragon Saga" combines elements of shooter and role-playing. You don't have a party in the game: you control only Edge on his dragon, who is in fact the playable character in battles. You move around through the game's fully 3D world by flying on the dragon. In towns and some dungeons you also move on foot. During battles, you can shoot with Edge's gun, or use one of the many special attacks of your dragons. You shoot in real time, and can also move around to attack your enemies from the sides of from the back, or to avoid their attacks. The dragon gets experience points for fighting and also gains levels. You will be able to customize your dragon by assigning to him one of the four available dragon classes, that will determine his attack power, speed, etc.</desc>
		<releasedate>19980430T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>SEGA</developer>
		<publisher>SEGA</publisher>
		<genre>Role playing games</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Radiant Silvergun (Japan).chd</path>
		<name>Radiant Silvergun</name>
		<desc>The story of Radiant Silvergun begins with the end of the world. As the pilot of the starfighter Radiant Silvergun you are sent back in time in search of the key to save the planet. In various time periods you will battle hordes of enemies in search for an alien being knows as the Origin. Only by destroying the Origin can the dark future of the planet be altered.

Radiant Silvergun is a top-down shooter from the Japanese codeshop Treasure (Gunstar Heroes, Silhouette Mirage) released in Japan for the Sega Saturn in 1998. To tackle the swarm of enemies that fill your screen you got three different means of attack. A straight shot, a homing laser and a devastating spread shot.

In 2002 Radiant Silvergun got its spiritual successor in the Dreamcast release of Ikaruga, which would later be converted for the Nintendo Gamecube.</desc>
		<releasedate>19980723T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Treasure</developer>
		<publisher>Treasure</publisher>
		<genre>Shoot'em Up</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Shining Force III (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Shining Force III</name>
		<desc>Set in a world of fantasy and magic, Shining Force III places you in the boots of a young general, fighting to preserve the peace in your world. The story starts out as the Emperor is abducted from within the city of Saraband, and you must go on the run with your king, who is suspected of being the mastermind behind the abduction. Of course, things are not as they seem, and you will be taken through a web of lies and deceit in your quest to prove the King innocent.

The game is very similar in style to the earlier Shining Force titles, so anyone who's played them will be comfortable with the game, though likely they'll also be happy to find the game graphically overhauled, with a 3-D landscape and 3D characters during the battle animations. As ever the main game is controlled like a traditional RPG, with you controlling the main character, talking to NPC's and searching various items. However, the main selling point of the Shining Force series has always been its battle sequences. 

The combat system is amended from the earlier titles, with a new and unique "friendship" system, whereby the more two characters work together (helping each other out, healing each other etc.) the closer they bond, and they will start to give each other bonuses on the battlefield. Other traditional features, such as the rock-paper-scissors nature of the weapons (sword beats axe, axe beats spear, spear beats sword etc.) and the terrain effects (someone hiding in a forest is going to get better protection than someone on an open road) remain fully intact, and anyone who's played the earlier titles in the series will likely be very comfortable with the combat system.

It should be noted that this is actually the western conversion of Shining Force III: Episode I, and was therefore only the first episode in an intended series of three. Unfortunately the other two titles were never released outside of Japan, so most western gamers were only able to experience a third of the storyline.</desc>
		<releasedate>19980731T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Camelot Software</developer>
		<publisher>SEGA</publisher>
		<genre>Role playing games</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Shining the Holy Ark (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Shining the Holy Ark</name>
		<desc>Part of the Shining game universe, "Shining the Holy Ark" is a pure console-style RPG (unlike  Shining Force games, that were strategy/RPG hybrids). You play the role of a young swordsman Arthur, who decided to work as a mercenary for various people needing his services. On his first mission, the King of Enrich sends him to a mine, in order to find and punish a renegade ninja who has escaped from him. However, an accident occurs that makes Arthur realize that he'll have to do much more than his usual mercenary assignment, and that there is a true evil in the world that must be defeated at all costs.

The game features 3D graphics and utilizes first-person perspective for dungeons and battles. The turn-based battles are of a traditional Japanese RPG kind, except the addition of "Pixie System". In various places in the game you can find pixies who can later be used as allies in battles.</desc>
		<releasedate>19970601T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>SEGA</developer>
		<publisher>SEGA</publisher>
		<genre>Role playing games</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Sonic R (USA, Brazil).chd</path>
		<name>Sonic R</name>
		<desc>While on vacation, Tails and Sonic come across a recruiting advertisement for the World Grand Prix race, and when he learns that Dr. Robotnik will participate he decides to enter. Robotnik is only interested in the race as he has located the Chaos Emeralds and now he'll get a chance to beat Sonic while he gets them. Knuckles and Amy join the race as well.
-Grand Prix: You race against the rest of the characters on each of the circuits, and get a chance to race the level's boss to unlock some of the extra playable characters.
-Time Attack: Run on one of the tracks as fast as you can, get 5 balloons or tag 4 characters.
-Multi Player: 4 players on a split-screen or over a network. You can race against up to three players or challenge them on a balloon finding game. The screen can be divided horizontally or vertically for 2 player games.</desc>
		<releasedate>19971031T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>SEGA</developer>
		<publisher>SEGA</publisher>
		<genre>Race, Driving</genre>
		<players>1-4</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Sakura Wars (Japan) [T-En by Sakura Wars Translation Project v2.01] [n].m3u</path>
		<name>Sakura Taisen</name>
		<desc>The gameplay of "Sakura Taisen" is a combination of Japanese-style adventure, "dating simulation", and strategic turn-based combat. Most of the game is spent exploring the theater, to which your military base is disguised. Depending on your decisions - where to go, which girl to look for, how to answer the questions (there is a time limit for responses) - you'll develop different relationships with the girl, which will influence not only further dialogues and the ending, but also their parameters in battles. During combat, you navigate your hero and the girls over the field and attack the enemies physically, or charge for powerful special attacks. Each turn you can perform two different actions, and your walking distance, as well as attack range, is limited and unique to each character. There is no experience points system and also no equipment.</desc>
		<releasedate>19960927T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>NexTech</developer>
		<publisher>SEGA</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Policenauts (Japan) [T-En by JunkerHQ v1.0.1].m3u</path>
		<name>Policenauts</name>
		<desc>In 2010, mankind has built its first space colony, Beyond Coast. After three years have passed, the founders of the colony feel it needs to be protected, and choose five best policemen of Earth to do that: Gatse Becker from Scotland Yard, the Japanese Sadaoki Tokugawa, Salvatore Toscanini from New York, and two policemen from Los Angeles: Jonathan Ingram, the hero of the game, and his best friend Ed Brown. 

One day, during a routine patrol on Beyond Coast, something happens to Jonathan's space suit. He is sucked into space and is presumed dead. But twenty-five years later, he is miraculously discovered in his life pod... alive. He still looks like a young man, but in reality he is 55 years old.

Trying to forget his past, Jonathan opens an investigation agency on Earth. His ex-wife (who has re-married during those twenty-five years) visits him and asks him to find her missing husband. When she leaves the office, her car explodes, and she dies. Determined to fulfill her final request, Jonathan prepares to re-visit Beyond Coast...

This unofficial semi-prequel to  Snatcher is a comic book/anime adventure with some shooting sequences. You click on objects and people you interact with, or move a dot around the screen to aim at your enemies during the shooting parts.</desc>
		<releasedate>19960913T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Konami</developer>
		<publisher>Konami</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
</gameList>
